<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 20:32 Air alarm to Cherkasy district observe further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129468</link><description>游댮 20:32 Air alarm to Cherkasy district observe further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 18:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:32 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129467</link><description>游댮 20:32 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 18:32:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:26 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129466</link><description>游댮 20:26 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 18:26:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:24 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129465</link><description>游댮 20:24 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 18:24:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:04 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129464</link><description>游댮 20:04 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 18:04:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:58 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129463</link><description>游댮 19:58 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 17:58:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:46 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129462</link><description>游댮 19:46 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kirovograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 17:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:26 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129461</link><description>游댮 19:26 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 17:26:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:09 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129460</link><description>游댮 19:09 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 17:09:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:47 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129459</link><description>游댮 18:47 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 16:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:43 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129458</link><description>游릭 18:43 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 16:43:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:14 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129457</link><description>游릭 18:14 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 16:14:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:13 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129456</link><description>游릭 18:13 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the following messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 16:13:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:09 Threat of Artbill! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129455</link><description>游댮 18:09 Threat of Artbill! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 16:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:16 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129454</link><description>游댮 17:16 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 15:16:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:08 Drive alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129453</link><description>游릭 17:08 Drive alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 15:08:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:45 Pleasure the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129452</link><description>游릭 16:45 Pleasure the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 14:45:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 16:44 alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129451</link><description>游리 16:44 alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 14:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 16:44 Alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Kharkiv Territorial Community and Kharkiv Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129450</link><description>游리 16:44 Alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Kharkiv Territorial Community and Kharkiv Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 14:44:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:43 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129449</link><description>游릭 16:43 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the following messages.#Zaporizhzhia_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 14:43:37 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>