<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 10:52 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131145</link><description>游릭 10:52 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 08:52:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 10:52 Drawing of anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marhanetsky Territorial Community- Mirorsk Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervonohrigor Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131144</link><description>游리 10:52 Drawing of anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marhanetsky Territorial Community- Mirorsk Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervonohrigor Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 08:52:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:47 Threat of Artebric! Pokrovskaya Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131143</link><description>游댮 10:47 Threat of Artebric! Pokrovskaya Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 08:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:22 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131142</link><description>游댮 10:22 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 08:22:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:21 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131141</link><description>游릭 10:21 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 08:21:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:19 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131140</link><description>游릭 10:19 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 08:19:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:13 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131139</link><description>游댮 10:13 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 08:13:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:09 Threat of Artebroch! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131138</link><description>游댮 10:09 Threat of Artebroch! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 08:09:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131137</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#KUDYANSKY This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 08:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:56 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131136</link><description>游릭 09:56 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 07:56:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:55 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131135</link><description>游릭 09:55 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Of Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 07:55:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 09:55 Flashing anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131134</link><description>游리 09:55 Flashing anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community#Kharkiv_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 07:55:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 09:55 Failure to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky Territorial Community- Mirorsk Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivska Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131133</link><description>游리 09:55 Failure to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky Territorial Community- Mirorsk Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivska Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 07:55:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:54 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131132</link><description>游릭 09:54 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 07:54:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:38 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131131</link><description>游댮 09:38 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 07:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 09:38 The threat of a shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131130</link><description>游리 09:38 The threat of a shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 07:38:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:37 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131129</link><description>游댮 09:37 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 07:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:36 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131128</link><description>游댮 09:36 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 07:36:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:18 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131127</link><description>游댮 09:18 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 07:18:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:18 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131126</link><description>游댮 09:18 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 07:18:45 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>