<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>🔴 02:35 Air anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142378</link><description>🔴 02:35 Air anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 23:35:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 02:34 Air anxiety in Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142377</link><description>🔴 02:34 Air anxiety in Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.#Kryvyi Rih Ri This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 23:34:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 02:29 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142376</link><description>🔴 02:29 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 23:29:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 02:29 Air anxiety in the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142375</link><description>🔴 02:29 Air anxiety in the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 23:29:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 01:58 Air alarm to the Khmelnytsky region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142374</link><description>🔴 01:58 Air alarm to the Khmelnytsky region follow the following messages.#Khmelnitskaya This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 22:58:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 01:55 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142373</link><description>🔴 01:55 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 22:55:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 01:51 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142372</link><description>🔴 01:51 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporozhye_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 22:51:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 01:27 Air anxiety in the Vinnytsia region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142371</link><description>🔴 01:27 Air anxiety in the Vinnytsia region follow the following messages.#Vinnytsia_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 22:27:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 01:22 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142370</link><description>🔴 01:22 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 22:22:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 01:22 Air alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142369</link><description>🔴 01:22 Air alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.#Nikopol. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 22:22:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 01:22 Air anxiety in Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142368</link><description>🔴 01:22 Air anxiety in Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.#Pavlograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 22:22:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 01:22 Air alarm to Dniprovskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142367</link><description>🔴 01:22 Air alarm to Dniprovskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 22:22:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 01:21 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142366</link><description>🔴 01:21 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 22:21:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 01:21 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142365</link><description>🔴 01:21 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 22:21:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 00:52 Air anxiety in the Zhytomyr Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142364</link><description>🔴 00:52 Air anxiety in the Zhytomyr Oblast follow the following messages.#Zhytomyr This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:52:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 00:36 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142363</link><description>🟠 00:36 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_that_harkivskaya_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:36:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 00:35 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142362</link><description>🔴 00:35 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 00:24 Air anxiety in Uman District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142361</link><description>🔴 00:24 Air anxiety in Uman District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:24:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 00:23 Air alarm in Zvenigorod district to care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142360</link><description>🔴 00:23 Air alarm in Zvenigorod district to care for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:23:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 23:49 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142359</link><description>🔴 23:49 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:49:09 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>