<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 04:30 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130242</link><description>游릭 04:30 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 02:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:30 Driven anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130241</link><description>游릭 04:30 Driven anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 02:30:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:05 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130240</link><description>游댮 04:05 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 02:05:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:05 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130239</link><description>游릭 04:05 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 02:05:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 03:54 Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-mirorsk territorial community-Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130238</link><description>游리 03:54 Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-mirorsk territorial community-Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 01:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:27 Air anxiety in the Zhytomyr Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130237</link><description>游댮 03:27 Air anxiety in the Zhytomyr Oblast follow the following messages.#Zhytomyr This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 01:27:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:09 Dumping anxiety in the Zhytomyr region.Crete on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130236</link><description>游릭 02:09 Dumping anxiety in the Zhytomyr region.Crete on further reports.#Zhytomyr This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 00:09:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 02:08 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130235</link><description>游 02:08 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_that_tha_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 00:08:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:07 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130234</link><description>游댮 02:07 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 00:07:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:33 Driven the alarm in Kyiv. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130233</link><description>游릭 01:33 Driven the alarm in Kyiv. Stop by further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 23:33:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:59 Air alarm to Zhytomyr Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130232</link><description>游댮 23:59 Air alarm to Zhytomyr Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zhytomyr_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 21:59:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:40 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130231</link><description>游댮 23:40 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 21:40:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:23 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130230</link><description>游댮 23:23 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 21:23:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:11 a alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130229</link><description>游릭 23:11 a alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 21:11:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:11 Lock down the threat of use of Cabbaths The threat of application</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130228</link><description>游릭 23:11 Lock down the threat of use of Cabbaths The threat of application This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 21:11:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 22:43 The threat of use of the cope proportion of the use</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130227</link><description>游 22:43 The threat of use of the cope proportion of the use This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 20:43:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:43 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130226</link><description>游댮 22:43 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 20:43:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:20 Air alarm in Zvenigorod District to care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130225</link><description>游댮 22:20 Air alarm in Zvenigorod District to care for further reports.#Zvenigorod_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 20:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:20 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130224</link><description>游댮 22:20 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 20:20:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:16 Air alarm in Kyiv Investigate by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130223</link><description>游댮 22:16 Air alarm in Kyiv Investigate by further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 20:16:09 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>