<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>🔴 00:38 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147490</link><description>🔴 00:38 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 21:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 00:33 Air anxiety in the Zhytomyr Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147489</link><description>🔴 00:33 Air anxiety in the Zhytomyr Oblast follow the following messages.#Zhytomyr_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 21:33:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 00:02 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147488</link><description>🔴 00:02 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.#M_kiiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 21:02:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 23:23 Air alarm to Vinnytsia Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147487</link><description>🔴 23:23 Air alarm to Vinnytsia Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Vinnytsia_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 20:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 23:00 Air Alarm to Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147486</link><description>🔴 23:00 Air Alarm to Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 20:00:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 23:00 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsk District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147485</link><description>🔴 23:00 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsk District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 20:00:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 23:00 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147484</link><description>🟠 23:00 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).#Pologovsky_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 20:00:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 22:29 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147483</link><description>🔴 22:29 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 19:29:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 22:29 Air alarm in Zvenigorod district to care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147482</link><description>🔴 22:29 Air alarm in Zvenigorod district to care for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 19:29:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 22:22 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147481</link><description>🔴 22:22 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 19:22:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 22:14 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147480</link><description>🔴 22:14 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 19:14:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 22:14 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147479</link><description>🔴 22:14 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 19:14:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 22:10 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147478</link><description>🔴 22:10 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 19:10:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 22:10 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147477</link><description>🔴 22:10 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 19:10:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 21:59 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147476</link><description>🟠 21:59 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 18:59:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:59 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147475</link><description>🔴 21:59 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 18:59:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:19 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147474</link><description>🔴 21:19 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 18:19:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:18 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147473</link><description>🔴 21:18 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 18:18:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟡 21:10 PM threats of artebing to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Cont attention, anxiety is still in:- Nikopol district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147472</link><description>🟡 21:10 PM threats of artebing to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Cont attention, anxiety is still in:- Nikopol district#Pokrovskaya_ territorial_ community This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 18:10:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:09 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147471</link><description>🔴 21:09 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 18:09:07 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>