<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 01:05 Air anxiety in the Donetsk region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138367</link><description>游댮 01:05 Air anxiety in the Donetsk region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 22:05:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:55 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138366</link><description>游댮 00:55 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 21:55:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:43 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138365</link><description>游댮 00:43 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 21:43:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:09 Threat of Artebating! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138364</link><description>游댮 22:09 Threat of Artebating! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 19:09:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:00 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. Walk to the shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138363</link><description>游댮 22:00 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. Walk to the shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 19:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:56 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Manganese territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138362</link><description>游댮 16:56 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Manganese territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 13:56:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:00 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138361</link><description>游 14:00 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:28 The threat of artobrats in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138360</link><description>游릭 11:28 The threat of artobrats in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 08:28:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:17 Close the threat of Artobstil to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138359</link><description>游릭 11:17 Close the threat of Artobstil to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 08:17:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:01 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138358</link><description>游 10:01 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 07:01:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:27 Return the threat of artebors to the Mirovskaya Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138357</link><description>游릭 08:27 Return the threat of artebors to the Mirovskaya Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 05:27:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:10 Failure of the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138356</link><description>游릭 07:10 Failure of the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 04:10:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:43 Attention! Droze Dronov-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138355</link><description>游릭 22:43 Attention! Droze Dronov-Kamikadze #M_Nikopol_ti_nikopol_ Territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 19:43:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 22:36 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138354</link><description>游 22:36 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 19:36:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:13 Driven the alarm to the Kiev region. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138353</link><description>游릭 22:13 Driven the alarm to the Kiev region. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 19:13:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:06 Driven the alarm in Kyiv.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138352</link><description>游릭 22:06 Driven the alarm in Kyiv. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 19:06:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:52 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138351</link><description>游댮 21:52 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 18:52:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:51 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138350</link><description>游댮 21:51 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 18:51:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 21:28 Pleasure in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138349</link><description>游릭 21:28 Pleasure in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 18:28:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 21:28 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138348</link><description>游릭 21:28 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 18:28:22 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>