<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 11:21 Attack Dron-Kamikadze! Movement to Port!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151558</link><description>游 11:21 Attack Dron-Kamikadze! Movement to Port! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 08:21:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:21 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151557</link><description>游댮 11:21 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 08:21:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:12 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151556</link><description>游댮 11:12 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 08:12:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:57 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District to follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151555</link><description>游댮 10:57 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District to follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 07:57:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:54 plow alarm to Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151554</link><description>游릭 10:54 plow alarm to Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporozhye This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 07:54:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:54 alarms in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151553</link><description>游릭 10:54 alarms in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 07:54:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 10:52 Fragrant anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151552</link><description>游리 10:52 Fragrant anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 07:52:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:52 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151551</link><description>游릭 10:52 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 07:52:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 10:51 Drawing of anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151550</link><description>游리 10:51 Drawing of anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 07:51:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:51 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151549</link><description>游릭 10:51 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region. Since further reports.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 07:51:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:51 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151548</link><description>游릭 10:51 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region. Salt for further messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 07:51:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:29 Air Alarm to Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151547</link><description>游댮 10:29 Air Alarm to Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Chernihiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 07:29:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:29 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151546</link><description>游댮 10:29 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 07:29:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:29 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151545</link><description>游댮 10:29 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 07:29:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:28 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151544</link><description>游댮 10:28 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 07:28:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:28 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151543</link><description>游댮 10:28 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 07:28:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:28 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151542</link><description>游댮 10:28 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 07:28:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:28 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151541</link><description>游댮 10:28 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 07:28:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:01 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151540</link><description>游릭 10:01 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Of Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 07:01:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:01 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151539</link><description>游릭 10:01 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 07:01:41 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>