<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 11:31 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142193</link><description>游댮 11:31 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:31 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142192</link><description>游댮 11:31 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:31 Air anxiety in the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142191</link><description>游댮 11:31 Air anxiety in the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:31:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:31 Air alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142190</link><description>游댮 11:31 Air alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Cherkasy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:31 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142189</link><description>游댮 11:31 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:31:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:31 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142188</link><description>游댮 11:31 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:31:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:31 Air anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142187</link><description>游댮 11:31 Air anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:31:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:31 Air anxiety in Vinnytsia region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142186</link><description>游댮 11:31 Air anxiety in Vinnytsia region follow the following messages.#Vinnytsia_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:31:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:31 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142185</link><description>游댮 11:31 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:31:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:30 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142184</link><description>游댮 11:30 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:30:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:27 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142183</link><description>游릭 11:27 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:27:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:27 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142182</link><description>游 11:27 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:27:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:27 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142181</link><description>游댮 11:27 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:27:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:39 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142180</link><description>游릭 10:39 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 07:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:39 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142179</link><description>游릭 10:39 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADze #M_Nikopol_ti_nikopol_ Territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 07:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142178</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 07:00:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:45 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Stop after further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142177</link><description>游릭 09:45 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Stop after further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:36 Air anxiety in Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142176</link><description>游댮 09:36 Air anxiety in Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kirovograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:30 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142175</link><description>游댮 09:30 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:30:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:30 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142174</link><description>游댮 09:30 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:30:23 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>