<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 10:45 A. Run in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139013</link><description>游릭 10:45 A. Run in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 07:45:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:44 plowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139012</link><description>游릭 10:44 plowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 07:44:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:38 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139011</link><description>游릭 10:38 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 07:38:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:37 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139010</link><description>游릭 10:37 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region. Since further reports.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 07:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 10:37 Flashing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Manganese and Marganetsky territorial community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139009</link><description>游리 10:37 Flashing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Manganese and Marganetsky territorial community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 07:37:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:20 Dreaming of anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139008</link><description>游릭 10:20 Dreaming of anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creat by further messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 07:20:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 10:17 The threat of a shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Find out, the alarm is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139007</link><description>游리 10:17 The threat of a shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Find out, the alarm is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region#m_nikopol_that_nikopol. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 07:17:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:05 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139006</link><description>游댮 10:05 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 07:05:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:04 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139005</link><description>游댮 10:04 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 07:04:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:04 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139004</link><description>游댮 10:04 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 07:04:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:04 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139003</link><description>游댮 10:04 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kirovograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 07:04:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:04 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139002</link><description>游댮 10:04 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 07:04:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:04 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139001</link><description>游댮 10:04 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139000</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 07:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:57 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138999</link><description>游댮 09:57 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 06:57:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:51 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138998</link><description>游릭 09:51 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 06:51:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:50 Air Alarm to Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138997</link><description>游댮 09:50 Air Alarm to Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Chernihiv_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 06:50:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 9:49</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138996</link><description>游댮 9:49 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 06:49:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:39 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138995</link><description>游댮 09:39 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 06:39:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:03 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138994</link><description>游릭 09:03 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 06:03:36 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>