<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 13:08 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129413</link><description>游댮 13:08 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 11:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:08 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129412</link><description>游댮 13:08 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 11:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:08 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129411</link><description>游댮 13:08 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 11:08:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:08 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129410</link><description>游댮 13:08 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 11:08:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:08 Air alarm to Cherkasy region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129409</link><description>游댮 13:08 Air alarm to Cherkasy region follow the following messages.#Cherkasy_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 11:08:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:08 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129408</link><description>游댮 13:08 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 11:08:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:08 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129407</link><description>游댮 13:08 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 11:08:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:08 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129406</link><description>游댮 13:08 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 11:08:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:08 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129405</link><description>游댮 13:08 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 11:08:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:08 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129404</link><description>游댮 13:08 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 11:08:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:05 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129403</link><description>游댮 13:05 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 11:05:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:34 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129402</link><description>游릭 12:34 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 10:34:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:32 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129401</link><description>游댮 12:32 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 10:32:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:23 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129400</link><description>游댮 12:23 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 10:23:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:22 a alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129399</link><description>游리 12:22 a alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 10:22:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:22 Alarm to Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Kharkiv Territorial Community and Kharkiv Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129398</link><description>游리 12:22 Alarm to Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Kharkiv Territorial Community and Kharkiv Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 10:22:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:15 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129397</link><description>游릭 12:15 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 10:15:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:45 PM threats of artobrats in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129396</link><description>游릭 11:45 PM threats of artobrats in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 09:45:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:39 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129395</link><description>游릭 11:39 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 09:39:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:39 pursuing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Highorivska Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129394</link><description>游리 11:39 pursuing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Highorivska Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 09:39:03 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>