<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 16:22 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129445</link><description>游릭 16:22 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 14:22:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:20 Driven the alarm to the Kherson region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129444</link><description>游릭 16:20 Driven the alarm to the Kherson region. Watch for further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 14:20:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:17 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129443</link><description>游댮 16:17 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kirovograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 14:17:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:17 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129442</link><description>游댮 16:17 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 14:17:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:17 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129441</link><description>游댮 16:17 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 14:17:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:17 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129440</link><description>游댮 16:17 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporozhye_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 14:17:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:10 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129439</link><description>游댮 16:10 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 14:10:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:54 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129438</link><description>游댮 15:54 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 13:54:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:54 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129437</link><description>游댮 15:54 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 13:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:49 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129436</link><description>游릭 15:49 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 13:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:18 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129435</link><description>游댮 15:18 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 13:18:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:39 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129434</link><description>游댮 14:39 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 12:39:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:22 Reduce the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129433</link><description>游릭 14:22 Reduce the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 12:22:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:00 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129432</link><description>游 14:00 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:55 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129431</link><description>游릭 13:55 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 11:55:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:55 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129430</link><description>游릭 13:55 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 11:55:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:54 Draw alarm to Zaporizhzhia region. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129429</link><description>游릭 13:54 Draw alarm to Zaporizhzhia region. Stop by further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 11:54:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 13:54 Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky Territorial Community, Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129428</link><description>游리 13:54 Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky Territorial Community, Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 11:54:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:30 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129427</link><description>游댮 13:30 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 11:30:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:30 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129426</link><description>游댮 13:30 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 11:30:08 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>