<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 09:56 Air Alarm to Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149821</link><description>游댮 09:56 Air Alarm to Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Chernihiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 06:56:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:55 Air anxiety in the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149820</link><description>游댮 09:55 Air anxiety in the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 06:55:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:53 Return the threat of Artobstil to Pokrovskaya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149819</link><description>游릭 09:53 Return the threat of Artobstil to Pokrovskaya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 06:53:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 09:48 plouting anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149818</link><description>游리 09:48 plouting anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 06:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:48 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149817</link><description>游릭 09:48 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 06:48:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:47 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149816</link><description>游릭 09:47 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 06:47:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:47 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149815</link><description>游릭 09:47 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region. Watch for further reports.#Poltava_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 06:47:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:47 Flowing anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149814</link><description>游릭 09:47 Flowing anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 06:47:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:47 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149813</link><description>游댮 09:47 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 06:47:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:25 Dronov-Kamikadze Attack! Movement on the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149812</link><description>游 09:25 Dronov-Kamikadze Attack! Movement on the city#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 06:25:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:24 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149811</link><description>游댮 09:24 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 06:24:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:16 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149810</link><description>游댮 09:16 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 06:16:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:16 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149809</link><description>游댮 09:16 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 06:16:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:16 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149808</link><description>游댮 09:16 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 06:16:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:16 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149807</link><description>游댮 09:16 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 06:16:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:15 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149806</link><description>游댮 09:15 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 06:15:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:15 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149805</link><description>游댮 09:15 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 06:15:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:15 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149804</link><description>游댮 09:15 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 06:15:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:12 Air anxiety in the Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149803</link><description>游댮 09:12 Air anxiety in the Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Chernihiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 06:12:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:06 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149802</link><description>游댮 09:06 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 06:06:59 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>