<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 12:51 Return the threat of artebors in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132819</link><description>游릭 12:51 Return the threat of artebors in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 10:51:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:48 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132818</link><description>游릭 12:48 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 10:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:48 Market threat threats of drums</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132817</link><description>游릭 12:48 Market threat threats of drums This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 10:48:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:38 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132816</link><description>游댮 12:38 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 10:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:23 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132815</link><description>游릭 12:23 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the following messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 10:23:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:23 Drive alarm to the Poltava region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132814</link><description>游릭 12:23 Drive alarm to the Poltava region. Watch for further reports.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 10:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:23 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132813</link><description>游릭 12:23 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 10:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:23 Flashing anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganets Territorial Community- March Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivska Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132812</link><description>游리 12:23 Flashing anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganets Territorial Community- March Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivska Territorial Community This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 10:23:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:23 Drive alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132811</link><description>游릭 12:23 Drive alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 10:23:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:16 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132810</link><description>游 12:16 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"#m_harkiv_that_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 10:16:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:09 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132809</link><description>游리 12:09 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:52 The threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Cont attention, anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132808</link><description>游리 11:52 The threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Cont attention, anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region#Pokrovskaya_T territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 09:52:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:46 Threat of Artbill! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132807</link><description>游댮 11:46 Threat of Artbill! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 09:46:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:38 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132806</link><description>游댮 11:38 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 09:38:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:36 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132805</link><description>游댮 11:36 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 09:36:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:36 Air Alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132804</link><description>游댮 11:36 Air Alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 09:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:36 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132803</link><description>游댮 11:36 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 09:36:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:36 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132802</link><description>游댮 11:36 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 09:36:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:34 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132801</link><description>游댮 11:34 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 09:34:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:28 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132800</link><description>游릭 11:28 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 09:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>