<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 06:54 Driven anxiety in Donetsk Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153952</link><description>游릭 06:54 Driven anxiety in Donetsk Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Donetsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 03:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:53 Driven an alarm to Sinelnikov District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153951</link><description>游릭 06:53 Driven an alarm to Sinelnikov District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 03:53:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:52 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153950</link><description>游릭 06:52 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 03:52:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:13 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153949</link><description>游댮 06:13 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporozhye_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 03:13:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:05 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153948</link><description>游댮 06:05 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.#Sinelnikov. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 03:05:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:00 pm alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153947</link><description>游릭 06:00 pm alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 03:00:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:00 Down the threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153946</link><description>游릭 06:00 Down the threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 03:00:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 06:00 pm alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153945</link><description>游리 06:00 pm alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 03:00:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:00 pm alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153944</link><description>游릭 06:00 pm alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 03:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 05:46 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153943</link><description>游 05:46 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 02:46:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:46 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153942</link><description>游댮 05:46 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 02:46:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:32 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153941</link><description>游릭 05:32 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 02:32:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:32 Run the threat of shock Blividbium threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153940</link><description>游릭 05:32 Run the threat of shock Blividbium threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 02:32:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:25 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153939</link><description>游릭 05:25 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 02:25:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:25 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153938</link><description>游릭 05:25 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 02:25:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:25 Driven the alarm to Kryvyi Rih District. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153937</link><description>游릭 05:25 Driven the alarm to Kryvyi Rih District. Stop by further messages.#Kryvyi Rih Ri This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 02:25:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:25 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153936</link><description>游릭 05:25 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District. Solve for further reports.#Pavlograd_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 02:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:24 Driven anxiety in the Dnieper District.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153935</link><description>游릭 05:24 Driven anxiety in the Dnieper District.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 02:24:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:24 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsk District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153934</link><description>游릭 05:24 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsk District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 02:24:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:24 Axiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153933</link><description>游릭 05:24 Axiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 02:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>