<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 16:00 alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131837</link><description>游릭 16:00 alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 14:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:59 Market threats of percussion bplavidbium threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131836</link><description>游릭 15:59 Market threats of percussion bplavidbium threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 13:59:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:59 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131835</link><description>游릭 15:59 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 13:59:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:59 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131834</link><description>游릭 15:59 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region. Since further reports.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 13:59:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:59 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131833</link><description>游릭 15:59 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Since further reports.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 13:59:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:59 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131832</link><description>游릭 15:59 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Of Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 13:59:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:59 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131831</link><description>游릭 15:59 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region. Watch for further reports.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 13:59:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:28 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131830</link><description>游댮 15:28 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 13:28:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:27 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131829</link><description>游댮 15:27 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 13:27:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:27 Air anxiety in the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131828</link><description>游댮 15:27 Air anxiety in the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 13:27:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:26 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131827</link><description>游댮 15:26 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 13:26:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:26 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131826</link><description>游댮 15:26 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 13:26:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:26 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131825</link><description>游댮 15:26 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 13:26:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:26 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131824</link><description>游댮 15:26 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow further reports.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 13:26:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 15:24 The threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131823</link><description>游 15:24 The threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 13:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:24 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131822</link><description>游댮 15:24 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 13:24:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:23 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131821</link><description>游댮 15:23 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 13:23:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:55 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131820</link><description>游댮 14:55 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 12:55:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:55 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131819</link><description>游댮 14:55 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 12:55:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:42 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131818</link><description>游댮 14:42 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 12:42:18 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>