<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 14:43 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142492</link><description>游댮 14:43 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:43:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:42 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142491</link><description>游댮 14:42 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:42:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:42 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142490</link><description>游댮 14:42 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:42:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:41 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142489</link><description>游댮 14:41 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:41:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:41 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142488</link><description>游댮 14:41 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:41:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:41 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142487</link><description>游댮 14:41 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:41:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 14:41 The threat of a shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142486</link><description>游리 14:41 The threat of a shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:41:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:41 Air anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142485</link><description>游댮 14:41 Air anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow further reports.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:41:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:41 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142484</link><description>游댮 14:41 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:41 WARNING! DROPS DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142483</link><description>游릭 14:41 WARNING! DROPS DRONNES-Kamikadze #M_Nikopol_ti_nikopol_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:41 Air alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142482</link><description>游댮 14:41 Air alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Cherkasy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:41:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:41 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142481</link><description>游댮 14:41 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:41:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:40 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142480</link><description>游댮 14:40 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:40:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:40 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142479</link><description>游댮 14:40 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:40:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:29 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142478</link><description>游댮 14:29 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:29:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:16 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh in the direction of the old part</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142477</link><description>游 14:16 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh in the direction of the old part This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:16:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:15 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142476</link><description>游 14:15 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:15:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:00 Attack of drones-camikadzethip Prayer, traffic in the direction</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142475</link><description>游 14:00 Attack of drones-camikadzethip Prayer, traffic in the direction This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:00:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:00 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142474</link><description>游 14:00 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#KUDYANSKY This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 13:59 Attack of drones-camikadzethip Prayer, movement in the direction</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142473</link><description>游 13:59 Attack of drones-camikadzethip Prayer, movement in the direction This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 10:59:56 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>