<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 17:20 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138550</link><description>游댮 17:20 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 14:20:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:20 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138549</link><description>游댮 17:20 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 14:20:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 17:00 WARNING! Drone-Kamikadze attack continues</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138548</link><description>游 17:00 WARNING! Drone-Kamikadze attack continues This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 14:00:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 16:58 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, traffic in the direction of the lamp</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138547</link><description>游 16:58 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, traffic in the direction of the lamp This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:58:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:56 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138546</link><description>游댮 16:56 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:56:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 16:54 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, traffic in the direction of the old part</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138545</link><description>游 16:54 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, traffic in the direction of the old part This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:54:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 16:52 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138544</link><description>游 16:52 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:52:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:50 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138543</link><description>游댮 16:50 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:50:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 16:44 The threat of use of the copecreal use of managed aviation bombs</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138542</link><description>游 16:44 The threat of use of the copecreal use of managed aviation bombs#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:44:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:43 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138541</link><description>游댮 16:43 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:43:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:43 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138540</link><description>游댮 16:43 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:43:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:40 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138539</link><description>游릭 16:40 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:40:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:27 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138538</link><description>游댮 16:27 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:27:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 16:21 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138537</link><description>游리 16:21 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:21:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:19 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138536</link><description>游댮 16:19 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:19:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:16 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138535</link><description>游댮 16:16 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:16:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:00 Return the threat of a shelling in Marganets and Marhanetsky territorial community. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138534</link><description>游릭 16:00 Return the threat of a shelling in Marganets and Marhanetsky territorial community. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:00:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:58 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138533</link><description>游댮 15:58 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 12:58:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:55 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138532</link><description>游릭 15:55 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 12:55:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:55 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138531</link><description>游릭 15:55 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 12:55:50 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>