<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游리 11:39 pursuing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Highorivska Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129394</link><description>游리 11:39 pursuing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Highorivska Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 09:39:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:29 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129393</link><description>游댮 11:29 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 09:29:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:19 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129392</link><description>游댮 11:19 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 09:19:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:42 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129391</link><description>游댮 10:42 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 08:42:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129390</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 08:00:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:54 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129389</link><description>游댮 09:54 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:54:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:49 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129388</link><description>游릭 09:49 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:49:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:30 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129387</link><description>游릭 09:30 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:30:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:30 Driven the alarm to the Kherson region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129386</link><description>游릭 09:30 Driven the alarm to the Kherson region. Since further reports.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:30:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:28 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129385</link><description>游릭 09:28 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Watch for further messages.#Odessa_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:28:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:22 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129384</link><description>游댮 09:22 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:22:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:22 Air anxiety in the Kherson Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129383</link><description>游댮 09:22 Air anxiety in the Kherson Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:22:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:22 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129382</link><description>游댮 09:22 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:22:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:19 Drive the threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129381</link><description>游릭 09:19 Drive the threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:19:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:03 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Stop after further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129380</link><description>游릭 09:03 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Stop after further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:03:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:53 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129379</link><description>游댮 08:53 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 06:53:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:32 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129378</link><description>游댮 08:32 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 06:32:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:25 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129377</link><description>游릭 08:25 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 06:25:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:21 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129376</link><description>游댮 08:21 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 06:21:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:19 Threat of Artebric! Pokrovskaya Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129375</link><description>游댮 08:19 Threat of Artebric! Pokrovskaya Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 06:19:07 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>