<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 01:34 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Stop after further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144518</link><description>游릭 01:34 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Stop after further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 22:34:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:14 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144517</link><description>游댮 01:14 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 22:14:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:07 Air alarm to the Rivne region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144516</link><description>游댮 01:07 Air alarm to the Rivne region follow the following messages.#Rivne_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 22:07:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:07 Air alarm to the Khmelnytsky region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144515</link><description>游댮 01:07 Air alarm to the Khmelnytsky region follow the following messages.#Khmelnitskaya This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 22:07:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:43 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144514</link><description>游댮 00:43 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 21:43:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:16 Air anxiety in Vinnytsia region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144513</link><description>游댮 00:16 Air anxiety in Vinnytsia region follow the following messages.#Vinnytsia_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 21:16:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:13 Driven anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144512</link><description>游릭 00:13 Driven anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 21:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:13 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144511</link><description>游릭 00:13 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 21:13:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:03 Air anxiety in the Zhytomyr Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144510</link><description>游댮 00:03 Air anxiety in the Zhytomyr Oblast follow the following messages.#Zhytomyr_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 21:03:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:43 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144509</link><description>游릭 23:43 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Watch for further messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 20:43:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:21 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144508</link><description>游댮 23:21 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 20:21:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:21 Air alarm in Zvenigorod District to care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144507</link><description>游댮 23:21 Air alarm in Zvenigorod District to care for further reports.#Zvenigorod_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 20:21:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:07 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144506</link><description>游댮 23:07 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 20:07:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 22:41 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144505</link><description>游 22:41 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 19:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:40 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144504</link><description>游댮 22:40 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 19:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:34 Air alarm to Cherkasy District Survene from further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144503</link><description>游댮 22:34 Air alarm to Cherkasy District Survene from further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 19:34:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:34 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District to follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144502</link><description>游댮 22:34 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District to follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 19:34:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:20 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144501</link><description>游댮 22:20 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 19:20:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:19 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144500</link><description>游댮 22:19 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 19:19:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:08 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144499</link><description>游댮 22:08 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow the following messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 19:08:10 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>