<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 18:50 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135703</link><description>游댮 18:50 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:50:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:50 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135702</link><description>游댮 18:50 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:48 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135701</link><description>游댮 18:48 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:48:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:48 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135700</link><description>游댮 18:48 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporizhia_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:48:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:47 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135699</link><description>游댮 18:47 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:47:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:47 Air alarm to Cherkasy region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135698</link><description>游댮 18:47 Air alarm to Cherkasy region follow the following messages.#Cherkasy_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:47:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:47 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135697</link><description>游댮 18:47 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:46 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135696</link><description>游댮 18:46 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:46:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:45 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135695</link><description>游댮 18:45 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:45 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135694</link><description>游댮 18:45 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:45:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:21 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135693</link><description>游릭 18:21 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:21:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:21 Draw an alarm to the Zaporizhzhia region. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135692</link><description>游릭 18:21 Draw an alarm to the Zaporizhzhia region. Stop by further messages.#Zaporizhzhia_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:21:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:40 Return the threat of artobrats in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135691</link><description>游릭 17:40 Return the threat of artobrats in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 14:40:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:31 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135690</link><description>游릭 17:31 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 14:31:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:31 Driven the alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135689</link><description>游릭 17:31 Driven the alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 14:31:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 17:30 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district-Lipetsk territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135688</link><description>游리 17:30 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district-Lipetsk territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community#Kharkiv_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 14:30:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:30 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135687</link><description>游릭 17:30 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 14:30:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:22 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135686</link><description>游댮 17:22 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 14:22:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:19 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135685</link><description>游릭 17:19 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 14:19:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:18 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135684</link><description>游댮 17:18 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 14:18:52 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>