<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 13:40 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150232</link><description>游릭 13:40 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 10:40:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:33 Driven anxiety in the Kherson region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150231</link><description>游릭 13:33 Driven anxiety in the Kherson region. Since further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 10:33:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:33 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150230</link><description>游릭 13:33 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 10:33:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:29 WARNING !!! DONE ASKRIGHT OF USEED AVIRTED AVIRT BOMB (Kabiv).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150229</link><description>游릭 13:29 WARNING !!! DONE ASKRIGHT OF USEED AVIRTED AVIRT BOMB (Kabiv). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 10:29:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 13:28 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150228</link><description>游리 13:28 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district#Zaporizhzhya_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 10:28:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:27 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150227</link><description>游댮 13:27 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 10:27:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:23 Drive alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150226</link><description>游릭 13:23 Drive alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 10:23:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 13:13 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin of the old part</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150225</link><description>游 13:13 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin of the old part #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial_ community This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 10:13:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:07 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150224</link><description>游댮 13:07 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 10:07:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 13:04 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150223</link><description>游 13:04 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 10:04:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:04 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150222</link><description>游댮 13:04 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 10:04:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:52 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150221</link><description>游댮 12:52 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 09:52:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:48 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150220</link><description>游댮 12:48 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 09:48:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:38 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150219</link><description>游 12:38 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 09:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:33 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150218</link><description>游릭 12:33 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 09:33:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:31 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150217</link><description>游릭 12:31 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on subsequent messages.#Chernihiv_e This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 09:31:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:30 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150216</link><description>游댮 12:30 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 09:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:03 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150215</link><description>游댮 12:03 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 09:03:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:58 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150214</link><description>游댮 11:58 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 08:58:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:54 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150213</link><description>游댮 11:54 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 08:54:16 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>