<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮33</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135582</link><description>游댮33 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 20:33:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:16 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135581</link><description>游댮 23:16 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 20:16:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:05 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135580</link><description>游댮 23:05 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 20:05:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:43 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135579</link><description>游댮 22:43 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:43:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:43 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135578</link><description>游댮 22:43 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:43:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:31 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135577</link><description>游댮 22:31 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:31:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:31 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135576</link><description>游댮 22:31 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:31:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:15 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135575</link><description>游릭 22:15 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:15:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:59 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135574</link><description>游댮 21:59 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 21:58 Auxiliary in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Mirovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135573</link><description>游리 21:58 Auxiliary in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Mirovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:58:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:39 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135572</link><description>游댮 21:39 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:39:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:39 Air anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135571</link><description>游댮 21:39 Air anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:39:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:36 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135570</link><description>游댮 21:36 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:36:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 21:29 The threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135569</link><description>游 21:29 The threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"#m_harkiv_that_harkivskaya_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:29 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135568</link><description>游댮 21:29 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:29 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135567</link><description>游댮 21:29 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:29:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:21 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135566</link><description>游댮 21:21 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:21:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:12 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135565</link><description>游댮 21:12 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 20:42 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135564</link><description>游리 20:42 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 17:42:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:42 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135563</link><description>游릭 20:42 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 17:42:30 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>