<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 10:36 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131295</link><description>游댮 10:36 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 08:36:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:26 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131294</link><description>游댮 10:26 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 08:26:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:14 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131293</link><description>游댮 10:14 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 08:14:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131292</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 08:00:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:16 Air anxiety in Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131291</link><description>游댮 08:16 Air anxiety in Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 06:16:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:51 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131290</link><description>游릭 06:51 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 04:51:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:37 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131289</link><description>游릭 05:37 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 03:37:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 03:46 Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-mirorskaya territorial community-Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131288</link><description>游리 03:46 Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-mirorskaya territorial community-Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 01:46:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:46 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131287</link><description>游릭 03:46 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 01:46:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:46 Run the threat of shock bpadbius threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131286</link><description>游릭 03:46 Run the threat of shock bpadbius threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 01:46:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 03:46 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lajpetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131285</link><description>游리 03:46 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lajpetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 01:46:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:34 WARNING !!! DONE ALREADY OF USEED AVIRTED AVIRT Bombs (Kabiv).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131284</link><description>游릭 03:34 WARNING !!! DONE ALREADY OF USEED AVIRTED AVIRT Bombs (Kabiv).#Zaporizhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 01:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 03:34 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131283</link><description>游리 03:34 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya district#Zaporizhzhya_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 01:34:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:32 Drive anxiety in the Poltava region.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131282</link><description>游릭 03:32 Drive anxiety in the Poltava region.Creck on further reports.#Poltava_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 01:32:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 3</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131281</link><description>游릭 3 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 01:12:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:39 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131280</link><description>游릭 02:39 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 00:39:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:56 Drive alarm to the Odesa region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131279</link><description>游릭 23:56 Drive alarm to the Odesa region.Creck on further messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 21:56:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:56 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131278</link><description>游릭 23:56 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 21:56:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:55 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131277</link><description>游릭 23:55 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Watch for further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 21:55:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:34 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131276</link><description>游댮 23:34 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 21:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>