<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148909</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 07:00:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:50 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city center</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148908</link><description>游 09:50 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city center #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 06:50:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:40 Attack Dronov-Kamikadze Timerukh on the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148907</link><description>游 09:40 Attack Dronov-Kamikadze Timerukh on the city #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 06:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:38 Close the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148906</link><description>游릭 09:38 Close the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 06:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:20 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148905</link><description>游댮 09:20 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 06:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:17 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148904</link><description>游 09:17 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 06:17:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:17 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148903</link><description>游댮 09:17 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 06:17:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:59 Air anxiety in Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148902</link><description>游댮 08:59 Air anxiety in Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 05:59:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 08:55 Drone-Kamikadze Drone Attack on Novopavlovka</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148901</link><description>游 08:55 Drone-Kamikadze Drone Attack on Novopavlovka #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 05:55:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 08:52 Attack drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148900</link><description>游 08:52 Attack drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 05:52:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 08:49 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148899</link><description>游 08:49 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 05:49:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:49 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148898</link><description>游댮 08:49 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 05:49:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:32 Drive alarm to the Kiev region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148897</link><description>游릭 08:32 Drive alarm to the Kiev region. Since further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 05:32:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:32 Drive alarm to the Chernihiv region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148896</link><description>游릭 08:32 Drive alarm to the Chernihiv region. Watch for further messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 05:32:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:32 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148895</link><description>游릭 08:32 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 05:32:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:31 Driven the anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148894</link><description>游릭 08:31 Driven the anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 05:31:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:31 Drive alarm to Cherkasy region. Follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148893</link><description>游릭 08:31 Drive alarm to Cherkasy region. Follow the following messages.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 05:31:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:31 Draw anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148892</link><description>游릭 08:31 Draw anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region. Since further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 05:31:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:31 Drive anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148891</link><description>游릭 08:31 Drive anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 05:31:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 08:31 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148890</link><description>游리 08:31 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community#Kharkiv_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 05:31:51 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>