<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 10:52 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140827</link><description>游릭 10:52 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 07:52:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:44 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140826</link><description>游 10:44 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 07:44:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:27 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140825</link><description>游댮 10:27 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 07:27:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:26 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzev District Port-Autoshkola</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140824</link><description>游 10:26 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzev District Port-Autoshkola#M_Nikopol_that_nikopol_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 07:26:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:24 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140823</link><description>游 10:24 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 07:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:17 Attack drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140822</link><description>游 10:17 Attack drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 07:17:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:09 threat of use of the copecreal application</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140821</link><description>游 10:09 threat of use of the copecreal application This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 07:09:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:09 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140820</link><description>游댮 10:09 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 07:09:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:09 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140819</link><description>游댮 10:09 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 07:09:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:02 Attack drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140818</link><description>游 10:02 Attack drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 07:02:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:02 Radiation danger in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140817</link><description>游릭 10:02 Radiation danger in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 07:02:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:02 Radiation Danger! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Radiation Danger. Go to the shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140816</link><description>游댮 10:02 Radiation Danger! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Radiation Danger. Go to the shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 07:02:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:02 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140815</link><description>游댮 10:02 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 07:02:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140814</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#KUDYANSKY This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 07:00:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:58 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140813</link><description>游댮 09:58 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 06:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:50 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140812</link><description>游댮 09:50 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 06:50:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:21 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140811</link><description>游릭 09:21 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 06:21:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:21 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140810</link><description>游릭 09:21 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 06:21:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:11 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140809</link><description>游댮 09:11 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 06:11:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 08:59 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city center</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140808</link><description>游 08:59 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city center #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:59:10 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>