<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 10:04 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin Center city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150708</link><description>游 10:04 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin Center city #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 07:04:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:03 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150707</link><description>游댮 10:03 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 07:03:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:03 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150706</link><description>游댮 10:03 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 07:03:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150705</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 07:00:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:57 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150704</link><description>游릭 09:57 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 06:57:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 9</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150703</link><description>游릭 9 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 06:57:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:56 Failure to alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150702</link><description>游릭 09:56 Failure to alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 06:56:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:48 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150701</link><description>游댮 09:48 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 06:48:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:48 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150700</link><description>游댮 09:48 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 06:48:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:31 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150699</link><description>游댮 09:31 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 06:31:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:30 Reduce the threat of Artobrytile to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150698</link><description>游릭 09:30 Reduce the threat of Artobrytile to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 06:30:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:20 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150697</link><description>游댮 09:20 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 06:20:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 09:18 Fragrant anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150696</link><description>游리 09:18 Fragrant anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 06:18:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:18 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150695</link><description>游릭 09:18 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 06:18:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:18 Run the threat of shock bplavidbium threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150694</link><description>游릭 09:18 Run the threat of shock bplavidbium threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 06:18:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:10 Attention! Drones attack, ammunition in the city center</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150693</link><description>游 09:10 Attention! Drones attack, ammunition in the city center #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 06:10:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:07 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150692</link><description>游댮 09:07 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 06:07:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:07 The threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150691</link><description>游 09:07 The threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"#m_harkiv_that_harkivskaya_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 06:07:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:07 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150690</link><description>游댮 09:07 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 06:07:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:52 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150689</link><description>游댮 08:52 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 05:52:18 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>