<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 04:55 Drive alarm to Poltava region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143393</link><description>游릭 04:55 Drive alarm to Poltava region.Creck on further messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 01:55:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:49 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143392</link><description>游릭 04:49 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further reports.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 01:49:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:37 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143391</link><description>游릭 04:37 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 01:37:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:37 Run the threat of shock bplavidbium threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143390</link><description>游릭 04:37 Run the threat of shock bplavidbium threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 01:37:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 04:36 Frouping anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lajpetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143389</link><description>游리 04:36 Frouping anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lajpetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 01:36:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:26 Air anxiety in the Vinnytsia region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143388</link><description>游댮 04:26 Air anxiety in the Vinnytsia region follow the following messages.#Vinnytsia_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 01:26:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:09 Air alarm in Zvenigorod District to care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143387</link><description>游댮 04:09 Air alarm in Zvenigorod District to care for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 01:09:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:09 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143386</link><description>游댮 04:09 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 01:09:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:09 Air anxiety in the Zhytomyr Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143385</link><description>游댮 04:09 Air anxiety in the Zhytomyr Oblast follow the following messages.#Zhytomyr_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 01:09:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:52 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143384</link><description>游댮 03:52 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 00:52:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:31 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143383</link><description>游댮 03:31 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 00:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:28 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District to follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143382</link><description>游댮 03:28 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District to follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 00:28:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:28 Air alarm to Cherkasy district observe further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143381</link><description>游댮 03:28 Air alarm to Cherkasy district observe further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 00:28:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:22 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143380</link><description>游댮 03:22 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 00:22:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:13 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsk District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143379</link><description>游릭 03:13 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsk District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 00:13:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:12 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143378</link><description>游릭 03:12 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 00:12:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:43 Driven anxiety in Nikopol District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143377</link><description>游릭 02:43 Driven anxiety in Nikopol District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 23:43:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:42 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143376</link><description>游댮 02:42 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 23:42:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 02:41 Flashing anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Nikopol district- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143375</link><description>游리 02:41 Flashing anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Nikopol district- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 23:41:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:38 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143374</link><description>游댮 02:38 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 23:38:57 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>