<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 01:27 The threat of shock UAVs The threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147939</link><description>游 01:27 The threat of shock UAVs The threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 22:27:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:12 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147938</link><description>游댮 01:12 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 22:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:09 Provision of the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147937</link><description>游릭 01:09 Provision of the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 22:09:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:09 MAKALABIBIBIUM ALREADY UPPLECTION AVIRIAL Bombs (Kabiv).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147936</link><description>游릭 01:09 MAKALABIBIBIUM ALREADY UPPLECTION AVIRIAL Bombs (Kabiv).#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 22:09:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:08 Supervise threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147935</link><description>游릭 01:08 Supervise threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 22:08:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:06 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147934</link><description>游릭 01:06 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 22:06:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 01:06 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Cont attention, anxiety is still in:- Vasylivsky district- Zaporizhzhya district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147933</link><description>游리 01:06 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Cont attention, anxiety is still in:- Vasylivsky district- Zaporizhzhya district#Zaporizhzhya_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 22:06:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:35 Air anxiety in the Poltava region follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147932</link><description>游댮 00:35 Air anxiety in the Poltava region follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 21:35:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:22 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Follow the subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147931</link><description>游릭 00:22 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Follow the subsequent messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 21:22:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:14 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147930</link><description>游댮 00:14 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.#Sinelnikov. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 21:14:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:11 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147929</link><description>游릭 00:11 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region. Salt for further messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 21:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:59 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147928</link><description>游댮 23:59 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 20:59:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:44 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147927</link><description>游릭 23:44 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 20:44:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:39 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147926</link><description>游릭 23:39 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 20:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:38 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147925</link><description>游릭 23:38 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 20:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 23:38 Drawing of anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Manganese and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147924</link><description>游리 23:38 Drawing of anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Manganese and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 20:38:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:38 Drive alarm to Poltava region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147923</link><description>游릭 23:38 Drive alarm to Poltava region. Watch for further messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 20:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:37 Driven to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147922</link><description>游릭 23:37 Driven to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 20:37:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:36 Drive alarm to Cherkasy region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147921</link><description>游릭 23:36 Drive alarm to Cherkasy region. Watch for further messages.#Cherkasy_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 20:36:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:19 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147920</link><description>游댮 23:19 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 20:19:34 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>