<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游리 11:41 Dumping anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141049</link><description>游리 11:41 Dumping anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 08:41:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:20 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141048</link><description>游 11:20 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).#Pologovsky_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 08:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:16 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141047</link><description>游댮 11:16 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 08:16:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:12 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141046</link><description>游릭 11:12 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 08:12:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:12 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141045</link><description>游릭 11:12 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 08:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:10 ploug to Sinelnikovsky District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141044</link><description>游릭 11:10 ploug to Sinelnikovsky District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 08:10:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:52 Attack Drones-Camikadzethip Prayer</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141043</link><description>游 10:52 Attack Drones-Camikadzethip Prayer This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 07:52:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:43 Driven anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141042</link><description>游릭 10:43 Driven anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 07:43:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:42 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141041</link><description>游 10:42 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 07:42:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:42 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141040</link><description>游댮 10:42 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 07:42:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:36 Driven anxiety in the Odesa region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141039</link><description>游릭 10:36 Driven anxiety in the Odesa region.Creck on further messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 07:36:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:35 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141038</link><description>游릭 10:35 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 07:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:35 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141037</link><description>游릭 10:35 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Watch for further messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 07:35:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:30 alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141036</link><description>游릭 10:30 alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 07:30:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:30 Return the threat of the use of Cabbaths The threat of application</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141035</link><description>游릭 10:30 Return the threat of the use of Cabbaths The threat of application This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 07:30:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:17 Threat of use of the cope proportion of use of managed aviation bombs</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141034</link><description>游 10:17 Threat of use of the cope proportion of use of managed aviation bombs#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 07:17:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:17 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141033</link><description>游댮 10:17 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 07:17:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:17 Air alarm to the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141032</link><description>游댮 10:17 Air alarm to the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 07:17:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:17 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141031</link><description>游댮 10:17 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 07:17:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:16 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141030</link><description>游댮 10:16 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 07:16:49 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>