<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 07:43 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136266</link><description>游릭 07:43 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 04:43:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:30 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136265</link><description>游댮 07:30 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 04:30:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:19 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136264</link><description>游댮 07:19 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 04:19:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:14 Close the threat of artobrats in Pokrovskaya territorial community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136263</link><description>游릭 07:14 Close the threat of artobrats in Pokrovskaya territorial community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 04:14:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:53 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136262</link><description>游릭 06:53 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 03:53:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:53 Driven anxiety in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136261</link><description>游릭 06:53 Driven anxiety in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 03:53:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:49 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136260</link><description>游릭 06:49 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 03:49:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 06:34 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136259</link><description>游리 06:34 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 03:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:34 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136258</link><description>游릭 06:34 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creat by further messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 03:34:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:34 PM anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136257</link><description>游릭 06:34 PM anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 03:34:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:34 Drive alarm to Poltava region. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136256</link><description>游릭 06:34 Drive alarm to Poltava region. Salt for further messages.#Poltava_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 03:34:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:03 Air Alarm to Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136255</link><description>游댮 06:03 Air Alarm to Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Chernihiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 03:03:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:02 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136254</link><description>游댮 06:02 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 03:02:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:02 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136253</link><description>游댮 06:02 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 03:02:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:02 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136252</link><description>游댮 06:02 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 03:02:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:47 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136251</link><description>游댮 05:47 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 02:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 03:19 Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-mirorical territorial community-Nikopol and Nikopol territorial community-Chervono-Grigoriva territorial community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136250</link><description>游리 03:19 Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-mirorical territorial community-Nikopol and Nikopol territorial community-Chervono-Grigoriva territorial community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 00:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:12 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136249</link><description>游댮 03:12 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 00:12:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:12 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136248</link><description>游릭 03:12 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 00:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 3</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136247</link><description>游릭 3 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 00:10:32 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>