<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 07:34 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132639</link><description>游릭 07:34 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 05:34:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:48 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast. Since Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132638</link><description>游릭 06:48 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast. Since Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 04:48:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:48 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132637</link><description>游릭 06:48 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region. Since further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 04:48:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 06:48 pm alarm in Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-mirorskaya territorial community-Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132636</link><description>游리 06:48 pm alarm in Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-mirorskaya territorial community-Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 04:48:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 06:47 Attention !!! Notice, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132635</link><description>游리 06:47 Attention !!! Notice, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya region#Pologovsky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 04:47:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 06:47 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132634</link><description>游리 06:47 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 04:47:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:47 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132633</link><description>游릭 06:47 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 04:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:47 Drive the threat of shock bpadbius threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132632</link><description>游릭 06:47 Drive the threat of shock bpadbius threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 04:47:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:47 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132631</link><description>游릭 06:47 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region.Creck on further reports.#Poltava_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 04:47:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:46 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132630</link><description>游릭 06:46 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region. Since further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 04:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:37 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Follow the subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132629</link><description>游릭 05:37 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Follow the subsequent messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 03:37:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:04 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132628</link><description>游릭 05:04 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 03:04:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:41 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132627</link><description>游릭 04:41 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region. Stop by further messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 02:41:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:26 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132626</link><description>游댮 04:26 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 02:26:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:25 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132625</link><description>游댮 04:25 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 02:25:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:18 Drive alarm to the Khmelnytsky region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132624</link><description>游릭 04:18 Drive alarm to the Khmelnytsky region. Watch for further messages.#Khmelnitskaya This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 02:18:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:16 Drive alarm to Vinnytsia region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132623</link><description>游릭 04:16 Drive alarm to Vinnytsia region. Watch for further messages.#Vinnytsia_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 02:16:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:44 Air alarm to the Khmelnytsky region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132622</link><description>游댮 03:44 Air alarm to the Khmelnytsky region follow the following messages.#Khmelnitskaya This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 01:44:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:22 Drive alarm to the Kiev region. Stop by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132621</link><description>游릭 03:22 Drive alarm to the Kiev region. Stop by subsequent messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 01:22:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:22 Drive alarm to Uman District.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132620</link><description>游릭 03:22 Drive alarm to Uman District.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 01:22:25 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>