<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 12:30 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151327</link><description>游댮 12:30 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 09:30:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:28 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151326</link><description>游댮 12:28 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 09:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:28 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151325</link><description>游댮 12:28 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 09:28:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:28 Air alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151324</link><description>游댮 12:28 Air alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Cherkasy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 09:28:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:28 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151323</link><description>游댮 12:28 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 09:28:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:28 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151322</link><description>游댮 12:28 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 09:28:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:27 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151321</link><description>游댮 12:27 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 09:27:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:27 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151320</link><description>游댮 12:27 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 09:27:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:27 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151319</link><description>游댮 12:27 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 09:27:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:19 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack is ongoing, Novopavlivka area</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151318</link><description>游 12:19 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack is ongoing, Novopavlivka area #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 09:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:08 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast. Since Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151317</link><description>游릭 12:08 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast. Since Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 09:08:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:53 The threat of shock UAVs The threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151316</link><description>游 11:53 The threat of shock UAVs The threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 08:53:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:52 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151315</link><description>游댮 11:52 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 08:52:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:52 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151314</link><description>游댮 11:52 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 08:52:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:48 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin Novopavlivka</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151313</link><description>游 11:48 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin Novopavlivka #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 08:48:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:25 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151312</link><description>游릭 11:25 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 08:25:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:16 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151311</link><description>游댮 11:16 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 08:16:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:55 Failure to alarm to the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151310</link><description>游릭 10:55 Failure to alarm to the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 07:55:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:55 threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151309</link><description>游댮 10:55 threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 07:55:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:55 Threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151308</link><description>游댮 10:55 Threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 07:55:12 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>