<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 11:52 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast. Since Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131615</link><description>游릭 11:52 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast. Since Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 09:52:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:44 PM threats of artebing to Pokrovskaya Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131614</link><description>游릭 11:44 PM threats of artebing to Pokrovskaya Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 09:44:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:42 Plowing the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131613</link><description>游릭 11:42 Plowing the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 09:42:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:42 Driving in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky Territorial Community-March Territorial Community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivska Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131612</link><description>游리 11:42 Driving in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky Territorial Community-March Territorial Community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivska Territorial Community This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 09:42:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:42 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131611</link><description>游릭 11:42 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 09:42:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:41 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131610</link><description>游릭 11:41 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 09:41:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:41 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131609</link><description>游댮 11:41 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 09:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:36 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131608</link><description>游릭 11:36 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creat by further messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 09:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:34 Auxiliary alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131607</link><description>游릭 11:34 Auxiliary alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 09:34:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:34 Auxiliary in Kharkiv region. Please note that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131606</link><description>游리 11:34 Auxiliary in Kharkiv region. Please note that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 09:34:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:33 Driven the alarm to the Poltava region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131605</link><description>游릭 11:33 Driven the alarm to the Poltava region. Watch for further reports.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 09:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:26 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131604</link><description>游댮 11:26 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 09:26:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:15 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Find attention, the alarm is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131603</link><description>游리 11:15 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Find attention, the alarm is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region#m_nikopol_that_nikopol. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 09:15:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:12 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131602</link><description>游댮 11:12 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 09:12:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:12 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131601</link><description>游댮 11:12 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 09:12:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:12 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131600</link><description>游댮 11:12 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 09:12:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:12 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131599</link><description>游댮 11:12 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 09:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:08 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131598</link><description>游댮 11:08 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 09:08:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:08 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131597</link><description>游댮 11:08 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 09:08:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:30 Pleasure the threats of the article to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131596</link><description>游릭 10:30 Pleasure the threats of the article to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 08:30:46 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>