<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 18:46 attack drones, possible discharges to the city center</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152252</link><description>游 18:46 attack drones, possible discharges to the city center #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 15:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:42 Dumping anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152251</link><description>游릭 18:42 Dumping anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 15:42:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:42 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152250</link><description>游릭 18:42 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further reports.#Nikopol_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 15:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:42 Dumping anxiety in Kryvyi Rih District. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152249</link><description>游릭 18:42 Dumping anxiety in Kryvyi Rih District. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 15:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:42 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd district.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152248</link><description>游릭 18:42 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd district.Creck on further reports.#Pavlograd_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 15:42:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:42 Driven in the Dnieper District. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152247</link><description>游릭 18:42 Driven in the Dnieper District. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 15:42:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:42 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsk District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152246</link><description>游릭 18:42 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsk District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 15:42:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:42 Driven the alarm to Kamyansky District.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152245</link><description>游릭 18:42 Driven the alarm to Kamyansky District.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 15:42:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 18:40 Attack drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152244</link><description>游 18:40 Attack drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 15:40:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:40 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152243</link><description>游댮 18:40 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 15:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 18:39 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152242</link><description>游리 18:39 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 15:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:29 AMAGABIBIUM The threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152241</link><description>游릭 18:29 AMAGABIBIUM The threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).#Vasylivsky This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 15:29:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:28 Driven Alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152240</link><description>游릭 18:28 Driven Alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 15:28:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 18:28 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Vasylivsky district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152239</link><description>游리 18:28 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Vasylivsky district#Zaporizhzhya_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 15:28:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:26 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152238</link><description>游릭 18:26 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 15:26:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 18:22 The threat of artobrats to Pokrovskaya territorial community. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Nikopol district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152237</link><description>游리 18:22 The threat of artobrats to Pokrovskaya territorial community. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Nikopol district#Pokrovskay This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 15:22:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:15 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152236</link><description>游댮 18:15 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 15:15:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:00 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152235</link><description>游댮 18:00 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kirovograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 15:00:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:59 Threat of Artbuster! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152234</link><description>游댮 17:59 Threat of Artbuster! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 14:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:57 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152233</link><description>游릭 17:57 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 14:57:10 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>