<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游리 16:51 Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky Territorial Community-Mirorsk Territorial Community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135357</link><description>游리 16:51 Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky Territorial Community-Mirorsk Territorial Community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 13:51:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:45 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135356</link><description>游댮 16:45 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 13:45:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:45 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135355</link><description>游댮 16:45 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 13:45:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:44 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135354</link><description>游댮 16:44 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 13:44:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:42 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135353</link><description>游릭 16:42 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 13:42:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:32 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135352</link><description>游댮 16:32 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 13:32:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:17 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135351</link><description>游릭 16:17 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 13:17:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:17 Drive the threat of shock bplas.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135350</link><description>游릭 16:17 Drive the threat of shock bplas. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 13:17:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 16:04 The threat of shock UAVs The threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135349</link><description>游 16:04 The threat of shock UAVs The threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 13:04:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:03 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135348</link><description>游댮 16:03 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 13:03:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:50 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135347</link><description>游댮 15:50 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 12:50:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:38 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135346</link><description>游댮 15:38 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 12:38:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:32 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135345</link><description>游댮 15:32 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 12:32:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:25 Reduce the threat of Artobhstil to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135344</link><description>游릭 15:25 Reduce the threat of Artobhstil to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 12:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 15:14 Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky Territorial Community- Mirorsk Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervonohrigor Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135343</link><description>游리 15:14 Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky Territorial Community- Mirorsk Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervonohrigor Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 12:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:13 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135342</link><description>游릭 15:13 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 12:13:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:13 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135341</link><description>游댮 15:13 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 12:13:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 15:10 The threat of a shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Find out, the alarm is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135340</link><description>游리 15:10 The threat of a shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Find out, the alarm is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region#m_nikopol_that_nikopol. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 12:10:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:02 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135339</link><description>游댮 15:02 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 12:02:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:02 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135338</link><description>游댮 15:02 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 12:02:31 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>