<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 06:20 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141412</link><description>游댮 06:20 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 03:20:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:15 Failure of the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141411</link><description>游릭 06:15 Failure of the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 03:15:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:15 Attention! Rap off the attack of drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141410</link><description>游릭 06:15 Attention! Rap off the attack of drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 03:15:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:07 Air alarm in Zvenigorod district to care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141409</link><description>游댮 06:07 Air alarm in Zvenigorod district to care for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 03:07:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:15 Dumping anxiety in the Zhytomyr region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141408</link><description>游릭 05:15 Dumping anxiety in the Zhytomyr region.Creck on further messages.#Zhytomyr_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 02:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:14 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141407</link><description>游댮 05:14 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 02:14:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:14 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141406</link><description>游댮 05:14 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 02:14:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:12 Driven the alarm in Kyiv. Include on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141405</link><description>游릭 05:12 Driven the alarm in Kyiv. Include on further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 02:12:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:08 MAKALABIBIBIBIUM ALREADY AVIRTION AVIRTEVERY BOMB (Kabiv).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141404</link><description>游릭 05:08 MAKALABIBIBIBIUM ALREADY AVIRTION AVIRTEVERY BOMB (Kabiv). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 02:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:07 Axiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141403</link><description>游릭 05:07 Axiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 02:07:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:07 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141402</link><description>游리 05:07 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district#Zaporizhzhia_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 02:07:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:06 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141401</link><description>游릭 05:06 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District.Creck on further reports.#Pavlograd_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 02:06:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:06 Failure to alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141400</link><description>游릭 05:06 Failure to alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 02:06:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:06 Show the threat of shock Blividbium threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141399</link><description>游릭 05:06 Show the threat of shock Blividbium threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 02:06:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:06 Fragrant anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Pavlograd district-Sinelnikovsky rayon- Marganets and Marganese territorial community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141398</link><description>游리 05:06 Fragrant anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Pavlograd district-Sinelnikovsky rayon- Marganets and Marganese territorial community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 02:06:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:06 Frogging anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141397</link><description>游리 05:06 Frogging anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community#Kharkiv_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 02:06:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:04 Drive alarm to the Khmelnytsky region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141396</link><description>游릭 05:04 Drive alarm to the Khmelnytsky region. Watch for further messages.#Khmelnitskaya This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 02:04:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:30 Air alarm to the Khmelnytsky region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141395</link><description>游댮 04:30 Air alarm to the Khmelnytsky region follow the following messages.#Khmelnitskaya This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 01:30:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:00 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141394</link><description>游댮 04:00 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.#M_kiiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 01:00:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:10 Failure to alarm to the Nikolaev area. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141393</link><description>游릭 03:10 Failure to alarm to the Nikolaev area. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 00:10:53 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>