<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>🟠 20:40 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133037</link><description>🟠 20:40 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 18:40:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟡 20:32 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133036</link><description>🟡 20:32 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 18:32:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 20:32 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133035</link><description>🔴 20:32 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 18:32:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 20:18 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133034</link><description>🔴 20:18 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 18:18:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 20:18 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133033</link><description>🔴 20:18 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 18:18:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 20:13 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133032</link><description>🔴 20:13 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 18:13:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 20:05 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133031</link><description>🔴 20:05 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 18:05:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 20:05 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133030</link><description>🔴 20:05 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 18:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 19:35 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133029</link><description>🔴 19:35 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 17:35:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 19:33 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133028</link><description>🔴 19:33 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 17:33:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 19:15 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133027</link><description>🔴 19:15 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 17:15:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 19:08 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133026</link><description>🔴 19:08 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 17:08:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 19:08 Air alarm in Zvenigorod District to care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133025</link><description>🔴 19:08 Air alarm in Zvenigorod District to care for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 17:08:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 18:57 Air alarm to Cherkasy district to care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133024</link><description>🔴 18:57 Air alarm to Cherkasy district to care for further messages.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 16:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 18:57 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133023</link><description>🔴 18:57 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 16:57:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 18:17 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133022</link><description>🔴 18:17 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kirovograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 16:17:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 18:06 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133021</link><description>🔴 18:06 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 16:06:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 17:50 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133020</link><description>🔴 17:50 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast follow the following messages.#Kharkiv_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 15:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 17:18 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133019</link><description>🔴 17:18 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporozhye_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 15:18:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 17:18 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133018</link><description>🔴 17:18 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 15:18:24 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>