<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 16:50 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138543</link><description>游댮 16:50 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:50:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 16:44 The threat of use of the copecreal application</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138542</link><description>游 16:44 The threat of use of the copecreal application This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:44:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:43 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138541</link><description>游댮 16:43 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:43:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:43 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138540</link><description>游댮 16:43 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:43:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:40 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138539</link><description>游릭 16:40 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:40:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:27 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138538</link><description>游댮 16:27 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:27:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 16:21 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138537</link><description>游리 16:21 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:21:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:19 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138536</link><description>游댮 16:19 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:19:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:16 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138535</link><description>游댮 16:16 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:16:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:00 Return the threat of a shelling in Marganets and Marhanetsky territorial community. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138534</link><description>游릭 16:00 Return the threat of a shelling in Marganets and Marhanetsky territorial community. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:00:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:58 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138533</link><description>游댮 15:58 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 12:58:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:55 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138532</link><description>游릭 15:55 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 12:55:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:55 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138531</link><description>游릭 15:55 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 12:55:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:55 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138530</link><description>游릭 15:55 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 12:55:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 15:54 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138529</link><description>游리 15:54 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 12:54:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:54 Auxiliary in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138528</link><description>游릭 15:54 Auxiliary in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 12:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:54 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138527</link><description>游릭 15:54 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 12:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:54 Driven the alarm to Poltava region.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138526</link><description>游릭 15:54 Driven the alarm to Poltava region.Creck on further reports.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 12:54:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:54 Draw an alarm to Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138525</link><description>游릭 15:54 Draw an alarm to Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporozhye This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 12:54:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:54 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138524</link><description>游릭 15:54 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 12:54:30 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>