<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 04:15 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148278</link><description>游릭 04:15 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 01:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:15 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148277</link><description>游릭 04:15 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Of Zaporizhzhia_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 01:15:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:13 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148276</link><description>游릭 04:13 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 01:13:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:13 Drive anxiety in the Kryvyi Rih District. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148275</link><description>游릭 04:13 Drive anxiety in the Kryvyi Rih District. Watch for further messages.#Kryvyi Rih. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 01:13:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 04:08 Drawing of anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kryvyi Rih district-Nikopol district- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-Nikopol and Nikopol territorial community-Pokrovskaya territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148274</link><description>游리 04:08 Drawing of anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kryvyi Rih district-Nikopol district- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-Nikopol and Nikopol territorial community-Pokrovskaya territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 01:08:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:07 Return the threat of the use of Cabbaths The threat of application</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148273</link><description>游릭 04:07 Return the threat of the use of Cabbaths The threat of application This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 01:07:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:07 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148272</link><description>游릭 04:07 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 01:07:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:07 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148271</link><description>游릭 04:07 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creat by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 01:07:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 04:07 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lajpetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148270</link><description>游리 04:07 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lajpetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 01:07:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:52 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148269</link><description>游댮 03:52 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 00:52:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 03:37 The threat of use of the adhesive application</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148268</link><description>游 03:37 The threat of use of the adhesive application This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 00:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:36 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148267</link><description>游댮 03:36 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 00:36:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 3</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148266</link><description>游댮 3 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 00:36:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:31 Driven anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148265</link><description>游릭 03:31 Driven anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 00:31:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:20 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148264</link><description>游댮 03:20 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 00:20:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:57 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148263</link><description>游댮 02:57 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 23:57:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 2:57</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148262</link><description>游댮 2:57 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 23:57:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:57 Air alarm to Nikopol District Surveat as Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148261</link><description>游댮 02:57 Air alarm to Nikopol District Surveat as Further Messages.#Nikopol. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 23:57:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:57 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148260</link><description>游댮 02:57 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.#Kryvyi Rih This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 23:57:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:49 Air anxiety in the Kherson Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148259</link><description>游댮 02:49 Air anxiety in the Kherson Oblast follow the following messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 23:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>