<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 04:49 Driven the alarm in Kyiv. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140425</link><description>游릭 04:49 Driven the alarm in Kyiv. Stop by further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 01:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:46 Air anxiety in the Vinnytsia region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140424</link><description>游댮 04:46 Air anxiety in the Vinnytsia region follow the following messages.#Vinnytsia_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 01:46:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:35 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140423</link><description>游댮 04:35 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 01:35:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:17 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140422</link><description>游댮 04:17 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 01:17:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:17 Air Alarm in Zvenigorod District Survene from further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140421</link><description>游댮 04:17 Air Alarm in Zvenigorod District Survene from further messages.#Zvenigorod_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 01:17:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:07 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140420</link><description>游릭 03:07 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 00:07:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:07 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140419</link><description>游릭 03:07 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 00:07:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:07 Dumping anxiety in Pavlograd district.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140418</link><description>游릭 03:07 Dumping anxiety in Pavlograd district.Creck on further reports.#Pavlograd_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 00:07:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:07 Driven the anxiety in the Dnieper district.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140417</link><description>游릭 03:07 Driven the anxiety in the Dnieper district.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 00:07:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:07 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140416</link><description>游릭 03:07 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 00:07:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:07 Run the threat of shock bplavidbium threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140415</link><description>游릭 03:07 Run the threat of shock bplavidbium threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 00:07:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:07 Dumping anxiety in Novomoskovsk District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140414</link><description>游릭 03:07 Dumping anxiety in Novomoskovsk District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 00:07:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:07 Driven the alarm to Kamyansky District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140413</link><description>游릭 03:07 Driven the alarm to Kamyansky District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 00:07:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 03:06 Fragrant anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140412</link><description>游리 03:06 Fragrant anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 00:06:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:06 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140411</link><description>游릭 03:06 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Of Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 00:06:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:31 Air alarm to Cherkasy district observe further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140410</link><description>游댮 02:31 Air alarm to Cherkasy district observe further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 23:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:31 Air anxiety in the Zolotonsky district observe by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140409</link><description>游댮 02:31 Air anxiety in the Zolotonsky district observe by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 23:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:29 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140408</link><description>游댮 02:29 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 23:29:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:01 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140407</link><description>游댮 02:01 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 23:01:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:49 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140406</link><description>游댮 01:49 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 22:49:46 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>