<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 06:50 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129079</link><description>游릭 06:50 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 04:50:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:35 Dumping anxiety in the Kiev region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129078</link><description>游릭 05:35 Dumping anxiety in the Kiev region. Since further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 03:35:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:34 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129077</link><description>游릭 05:34 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 03:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:34 Driven anxiety in Donetsk Region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129076</link><description>游릭 05:34 Driven anxiety in Donetsk Region. Watch for further messages.#Donetsk_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 03:34:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:33 Drive anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129075</link><description>游릭 05:33 Drive anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 03:33:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:33 Drawing anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129074</link><description>游리 05:33 Drawing anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 03:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:09 Air anxiety in the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129073</link><description>游댮 05:09 Air anxiety in the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 03:09:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:53 Driven anxiety in Kyiv. Investigate by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129072</link><description>游릭 04:53 Driven anxiety in Kyiv. Investigate by subsequent messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 02:53:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:52 Driven the alarm to the Kiev region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129071</link><description>游릭 04:52 Driven the alarm to the Kiev region. Since further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 02:52:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:22 Drive alarm to the Zolotonsky district.Creb</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129070</link><description>游릭 04:22 Drive alarm to the Zolotonsky district.Creb This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 02:22:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:22 Driven the alarm to Cherkasy district.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129069</link><description>游릭 04:22 Driven the alarm to Cherkasy district.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 02:22:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:22 Rap on the Zvenigorod District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129068</link><description>游릭 04:22 Rap on the Zvenigorod District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 02:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:15 Dumping anxiety in the Zhytomyr region.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129067</link><description>游릭 04:15 Dumping anxiety in the Zhytomyr region.Creck on further reports.#Zhytomyr_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 02:15:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:09 Draw alarms to Poltava region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129066</link><description>游릭 04:09 Draw alarms to Poltava region. Since further reports.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 02:09:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:33 Driven to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129065</link><description>游릭 03:33 Driven to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 01:33:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:31 Draw anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129064</link><description>游릭 03:31 Draw anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region. Since further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 01:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 03:31 Drawing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganets Territorial Community, Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Mirovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129063</link><description>游리 03:31 Drawing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganets Territorial Community, Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Mirovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 01:31:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:03 Drive alarm to the Khmelnytsky region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129062</link><description>游릭 03:03 Drive alarm to the Khmelnytsky region. Watch for further messages.#Khmelnitskaya This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 01:03:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:42 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129061</link><description>游댮 02:42 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 00:42:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:47 Air alarm to the Khmelnytsky region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129060</link><description>游댮 01:47 Air alarm to the Khmelnytsky region follow the following messages.#Khmelnitskaya This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 23:47:08 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>