<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 22:17 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146619</link><description>游릭 22:17 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 19:17:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:17 Run the threat of shock bplavidbium threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146618</link><description>游릭 22:17 Run the threat of shock bplavidbium threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 19:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:12 Air alarm in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146617</link><description>游댮 22:12 Air alarm in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 19:12:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:57 Air anxiety in the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146616</link><description>游댮 21:57 Air anxiety in the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 18:57:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:46 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146615</link><description>游댮 21:46 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 18:46:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 21:05 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146614</link><description>游 21:05 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 18:05:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:05 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146613</link><description>游댮 21:05 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 18:05:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:54 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146612</link><description>游댮 20:54 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:54:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 20:39 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Cont attention, anxiety is still in:- Nikopol district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146611</link><description>游리 20:39 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Cont attention, anxiety is still in:- Nikopol district#Pokrovskaya_T territorial_ community This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:39:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:35 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146610</link><description>游댮 20:35 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:35:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:35 Air alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146609</link><description>游댮 20:35 Air alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.#Nikopol. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:35:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:35 Air alarm to Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146608</link><description>游댮 20:35 Air alarm to Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.#Pavlograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:35:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:35 Air alarm to Dniprovskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146607</link><description>游댮 20:35 Air alarm to Dniprovskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:35:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:35 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146606</link><description>游댮 20:35 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:35:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:35 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146605</link><description>游댮 20:35 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:35:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:34 The threat of shelling! The Chervonohrigor Territorial Community is now Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146604</link><description>游댮 20:34 The threat of shelling! The Chervonohrigor Territorial Community is now Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:34:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:13 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146603</link><description>游댮 20:13 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:13:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:13 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146602</link><description>游댮 20:13 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:13:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:11 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146601</link><description>游댮 20:11 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:11:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:06 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146600</link><description>游댮 20:06 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:06:21 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>