<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135130</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 07:00:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:28 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135129</link><description>游댮 09:28 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:28:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:19 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135128</link><description>游댮 09:19 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:51 Return the threat of artobrats in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Solid by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135127</link><description>游릭 08:51 Return the threat of artobrats in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Solid by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 05:51:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 07:16 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135126</link><description>游리 07:16 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 04:16:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:16 Failure in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135125</link><description>游릭 07:16 Failure in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 04:16:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:12 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135124</link><description>游릭 07:12 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 04:12:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 07:12 Drawing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community- Chervonohrigor Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135123</link><description>游리 07:12 Drawing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community- Chervonohrigor Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 04:12:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:12 Drive the threat of shock bplas.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135122</link><description>游릭 07:12 Drive the threat of shock bplas. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 04:12:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:12 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135121</link><description>游릭 07:12 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 04:12:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:12 Driven the anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135120</link><description>游릭 07:12 Driven the anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 04:12:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:12 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135119</link><description>游릭 07:12 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 04:12:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 06:26 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135118</link><description>游리 06:26 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 03:26:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:09 Air anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135117</link><description>游댮 06:09 Air anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 03:09:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:09 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135116</link><description>游댮 06:09 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 03:09:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:09 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135115</link><description>游댮 06:09 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 03:09:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:32 Drive alarm to the Kiev region. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135114</link><description>游릭 05:32 Drive alarm to the Kiev region. Stop by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 02:32:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:31 Driven anxiety in the Zhytomyr region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135113</link><description>游릭 05:31 Driven anxiety in the Zhytomyr region. Watch for further reports.#Zhytomyr This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 02:31:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:29 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135112</link><description>游릭 05:29 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 02:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:51 Driven anxiety in Kyiv. Investigate by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135111</link><description>游릭 04:51 Driven anxiety in Kyiv. Investigate by subsequent messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 01:51:48 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>