<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 10:18 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143274</link><description>游댮 10:18 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 07:18:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:00 pimplifting the threat of artebing in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143273</link><description>游릭 10:00 pimplifting the threat of artebing in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 07:00:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:00 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143272</link><description>游릭 10:00 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #M_Nikopol_ta_nikopol_ Territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 07:00:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143271</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 07:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 09:40 Auxiliary alarm to Kharkiv region.Cont attention, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143270</link><description>游리 09:40 Auxiliary alarm to Kharkiv region.Cont attention, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community#Kharkiv_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 06:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:26 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143269</link><description>游댮 09:26 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 06:26:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:15 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143268</link><description>游댮 09:15 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 06:15:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:10 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh in the direction</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143267</link><description>游 09:10 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh in the direction This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 06:10:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:08 Attention! Drone-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143266</link><description>游 09:08 Attention! Drone-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 06:08:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:53 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143265</link><description>游릭 08:53 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 05:53:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 08:46 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143264</link><description>游 08:46 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 05:46:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:45 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143263</link><description>游댮 08:45 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 05:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:44 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143262</link><description>游댮 08:44 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 05:44:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:35 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143261</link><description>游댮 08:35 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 05:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:21 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143260</link><description>游릭 08:21 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region. Since further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 05:21:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:20 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143259</link><description>游릭 08:20 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 05:20:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:15 Return the threat of artobstil in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143258</link><description>游릭 08:15 Return the threat of artobstil in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 05:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:42 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143257</link><description>游릭 06:42 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 03:42:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:14 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143256</link><description>游릭 06:14 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 03:14:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:02 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143255</link><description>游댮 06:02 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 03:02:52 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>