<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 18:22 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142640</link><description>游릭 18:22 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 15:22:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:22 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142639</link><description>游릭 18:22 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 15:22:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:32 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142638</link><description>游댮 17:32 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 14:32:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:40 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142637</link><description>游릭 16:40 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:40:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:39 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142636</link><description>游릭 16:39 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Salt for further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:39:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:39 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142635</link><description>游릭 16:39 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:39 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142634</link><description>游릭 16:39 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:39:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:28 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142633</link><description>游댮 16:28 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:28:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:27 Air anxiety in the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142632</link><description>游댮 16:27 Air anxiety in the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:27:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 16:00 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh in the direction of Novopavlivka</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142631</link><description>游 16:00 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh in the direction of Novopavlivka #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 15:55 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142630</link><description>游 15:55 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack! #m_nikopol_tay_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 12:55:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:55 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142629</link><description>游댮 15:55 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 12:55:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:06 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142628</link><description>游댮 15:06 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 12:06:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:56 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142627</link><description>游댮 14:56 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 11:56:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>?</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142626</link><description>? This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 11:46:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:00 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142625</link><description>游 14:00 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#KUDYANSKY This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 11:00:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:34 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142624</link><description>游댮 13:34 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast follow the following messages.#Kharkiv_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 10:34:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:04 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142623</link><description>游릭 13:04 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 10:04:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:04 Drives the threat of shock bpadbius threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142622</link><description>游릭 13:04 Drives the threat of shock bpadbius threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 10:04:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 13:03 Flashing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lipetsk territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142621</link><description>游리 13:03 Flashing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lipetsk territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community#Kharkiv_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 10:03:45 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>