<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 22:09 Air alarm to the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140383</link><description>游댮 22:09 Air alarm to the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 19:09:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:05 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140382</link><description>游댮 22:05 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 19:05:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:55 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140381</link><description>游댮 21:55 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 18:55:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:37 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140380</link><description>游댮 21:37 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 18:37:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:37 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140379</link><description>游댮 21:37 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 18:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:29 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140378</link><description>游댮 21:29 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 18:29:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:28 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140377</link><description>游댮 21:28 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 18:28:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:17 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140376</link><description>游댮 21:17 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 18:17:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:17 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140375</link><description>游댮 21:17 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 18:17:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:15 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140374</link><description>游댮 21:15 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 18:15:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:15 Reduce the threat of Artobstil to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140373</link><description>游릭 20:15 Reduce the threat of Artobstil to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 17:15:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:45 The threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140372</link><description>游댮 19:45 The threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 16:45:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:04 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140371</link><description>游댮 19:04 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 16:04:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:55 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140370</link><description>游릭 18:55 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 15:55:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:55 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140369</link><description>游릭 18:55 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADze #M_Nikopol_ti_nikopol. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 15:55:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 18:30 Attention! Drone-Kamikadze Dronov Drohnia</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140368</link><description>游 18:30 Attention! Drone-Kamikadze Dronov Drohnia #M_Nikopol_that_nikopol_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 15:30:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:30 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140367</link><description>游댮 18:30 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 15:30:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 18:28 Drawing of anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140366</link><description>游리 18:28 Drawing of anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 15:28:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:05 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140365</link><description>游릭 18:05 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region. Stop by further messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 15:05:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:05 Driven anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140364</link><description>游릭 18:05 Driven anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 15:05:32 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>