<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 10:22 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138633</link><description>游댮 10:22 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 07:22:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:22 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138632</link><description>游댮 10:22 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 07:22:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:08 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138631</link><description>游댮 10:08 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 07:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:00 Air alarm to Zhytomyr Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138630</link><description>游댮 10:00 Air alarm to Zhytomyr Oblast follow the following messages.#Zhytomyr This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 07:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138629</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 07:00:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:32 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138628</link><description>游댮 09:32 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 06:32:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:05 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138627</link><description>游댮 09:05 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 06:05:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:05 Air alarm to Cherkasy district carefully monitored.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138626</link><description>游댮 09:05 Air alarm to Cherkasy district carefully monitored. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 06:05:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:39 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138625</link><description>游댮 08:39 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 05:39:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:33 Air Alarm to Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138624</link><description>游댮 08:33 Air Alarm to Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Chernihiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 05:33:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:25 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138623</link><description>游댮 08:25 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 05:25:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:24 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138622</link><description>游댮 08:24 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 05:24:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:23 Return the threat of artobrats in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138621</link><description>游릭 08:23 Return the threat of artobrats in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 05:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:12 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138620</link><description>游릭 07:12 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 04:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:37 PM threats of artobrats in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138619</link><description>游릭 06:37 PM threats of artobrats in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 03:37:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 04:59 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138618</link><description>游리 04:59 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 01:59:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:59 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138617</link><description>游릭 04:59 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 01:59:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:59 Clease the threat of using Cabbaths The threat of application</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138616</link><description>游릭 04:59 Clease the threat of using Cabbaths The threat of application This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 01:59:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:59 Dumping anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138615</link><description>游릭 04:59 Dumping anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 01:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:41 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138614</link><description>游댮 03:41 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 00:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>