<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 11:40 PM threats of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142610</link><description>游릭 11:40 PM threats of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 08:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:40 WARNING! DRAWE DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142609</link><description>游릭 11:40 WARNING! DRAWE DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_The community This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 08:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:30 AM ATTENTION !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142608</link><description>游 11:30 AM ATTENTION !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 08:30:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:28 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142607</link><description>游 11:28 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 08:28:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:21 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142606</link><description>游댮 11:21 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 08:21:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:17 Close the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142605</link><description>游릭 11:17 Close the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 08:17:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:11 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142604</link><description>游댮 11:11 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 08:11:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:53 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142603</link><description>游댮 10:53 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 07:53:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:51 Attack drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142602</link><description>游 10:51 Attack drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 07:51:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:51 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142601</link><description>游댮 10:51 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 07:51:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:15 threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142600</link><description>游댮 10:15 threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 07:15:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:04 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142599</link><description>游댮 10:04 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 07:04:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142598</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#KUDYANSKY This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 07:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:33 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142597</link><description>游릭 09:33 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 06:33:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:33 WARNING! DROVIA DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142596</link><description>游릭 09:33 WARNING! DROVIA DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 06:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:15 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142595</link><description>游댮 09:15 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 06:15:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 08:58 Attack Dronov-Camikadzethip Prayer</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142594</link><description>游 08:58 Attack Dronov-Camikadzethip Prayer This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 05:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:57 Return the threat of artebrow to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142593</link><description>游릭 08:57 Return the threat of artebrow to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 05:57:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 08:52 Attack Drones-Camikadzethip Pracement</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142592</link><description>游 08:52 Attack Drones-Camikadzethip Pracement This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 05:52:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 08:30 Attention! Drone-Kamikadze Dronov-type attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142591</link><description>游 08:30 Attention! Drone-Kamikadze Dronov-type attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 05:30:35 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>