<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 14:46 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149336</link><description>游릭 14:46 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 11:46:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:46 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADE!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149335</link><description>游릭 14:46 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADE! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 11:46:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:33 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149334</link><description>游댮 14:33 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 11:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:02 Attack drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149333</link><description>游 14:02 Attack drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 11:02:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:00 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149332</link><description>游 14:00 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:52 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149331</link><description>游댮 13:52 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 10:52:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:50 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149330</link><description>游댮 13:50 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 10:50:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 13:48 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149329</link><description>游 13:48 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 10:48:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:47 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149328</link><description>游댮 13:47 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 10:47:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:31 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149327</link><description>游릭 13:31 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 10:31:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:31 Draw an alarm to the Zaporizhzhia region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149326</link><description>游릭 13:31 Draw an alarm to the Zaporizhzhia region. Since further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 10:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 13:31 Drives the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149325</link><description>游리 13:31 Drives the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 10:31:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:30 Fragrant anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149324</link><description>游릭 13:30 Fragrant anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 10:30:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:55 PM threats of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149323</link><description>游릭 12:55 PM threats of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 09:55:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:55 Attention! Sleep Dronov-Kamikadze attack!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149322</link><description>游릭 12:55 Attention! Sleep Dronov-Kamikadze attack! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 09:55:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:37 Attack drones, possible discharges of ammunition to the center</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149321</link><description>游 12:37 Attack drones, possible discharges of ammunition to the center This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 09:37:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:32 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149320</link><description>游리 12:32 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 09:32:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:32 Drive alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149319</link><description>游릭 12:32 Drive alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 09:32:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:21 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149318</link><description>游댮 12:21 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 09:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:17 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149317</link><description>游 12:17 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 09:17:49 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>