<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 11:51 Close the threat of artobrats in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143704</link><description>游릭 11:51 Close the threat of artobrats in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:51:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:40 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143703</link><description>游릭 11:40 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:40:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:40 pm a alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kryvyi Rih rayon- Marganets and Marhanetsky Territorial Community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivska Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143702</link><description>游리 11:40 pm a alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kryvyi Rih rayon- Marganets and Marhanetsky Territorial Community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivska Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:40 Air Alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat as Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143701</link><description>游댮 11:40 Air Alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat as Further Messages.#Kryvyi Rih Ri This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:40:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:39 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143700</link><description>游릭 11:39 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:39:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:39 Return the threat of shock bplavidbium threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143699</link><description>游릭 11:39 Return the threat of shock bplavidbium threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:39 Driven the alarm in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143698</link><description>游릭 11:39 Driven the alarm in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:39:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:38 Auxiliary in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143697</link><description>游리 11:38 Auxiliary in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:38:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:38 Drive alarm to Cherkasy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143696</link><description>游릭 11:38 Drive alarm to Cherkasy region.Creck on further messages.#Cherkasy_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:38 Plow anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143695</link><description>游릭 11:38 Plow anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporozhye This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:38 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143694</link><description>游릭 11:38 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region.Creck on further reports.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:38:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:38 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143693</link><description>游릭 11:38 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:35 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143692</link><description>游댮 11:35 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:35:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:09 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Find out, the alarm is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143691</link><description>游리 11:09 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Find out, the alarm is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region#m_nikopol_that_tikopolskaya_T territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:09:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:09 Attention! Please note that anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143690</link><description>游리 11:09 Attention! Please note that anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:09:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:02 The threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143689</link><description>游 11:02 The threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"#m_harkiv_tha_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:02:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:01 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143688</link><description>游댮 11:01 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:01:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:01 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143687</link><description>游댮 11:01 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:01:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:00 Air Alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143686</link><description>游댮 11:00 Air Alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Cherkasy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:00:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:00 Air Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143685</link><description>游댮 11:00 Air Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:00:58 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>