<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 00:18 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Follow the subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150100</link><description>游릭 00:18 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Follow the subsequent messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 21:18:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:18 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150099</link><description>游릭 00:18 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 21:18:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:15 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150098</link><description>游릭 00:15 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 21:15:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:14 Drive alarm to Poltava region.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150097</link><description>游릭 00:14 Drive alarm to Poltava region.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 21:14:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:13 Air anxiety in the Zhytomyr Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150096</link><description>游댮 00:13 Air anxiety in the Zhytomyr Oblast follow the following messages.#Zhytomyr_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 21:13:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:37 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150095</link><description>游댮 23:37 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.#M_kiiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 20:37:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:20 Air alarm to Cherkasy District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150094</link><description>游댮 23:20 Air alarm to Cherkasy District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 20:20:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:20 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150093</link><description>游댮 23:20 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 20:20:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:18 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150092</link><description>游댮 23:18 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 20:18:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:14 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150091</link><description>游댮 23:14 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 20:14:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:12 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150090</link><description>游댮 23:12 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 20:12:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:57 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150089</link><description>游댮 22:57 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 19:57:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:19 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150088</link><description>游댮 22:19 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 19:19:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:05 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150087</link><description>游댮 22:05 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 19:05:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 21:58 Close the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150086</link><description>游릭 21:58 Close the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 18:58:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:55 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150085</link><description>游댮 21:55 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 18:55:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:45 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150084</link><description>游댮 21:45 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 18:45:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:37 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150083</link><description>游댮 21:37 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 18:37:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:37 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150082</link><description>游댮 21:37 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 18:37:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:57 The threat of shelling! The Chervonohrigor Territorial Community is now Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150081</link><description>游댮 20:57 The threat of shelling! The Chervonohrigor Territorial Community is now Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 17:57:41 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>