<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 07:43 Air Alarm to Poltava Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144157</link><description>游댮 07:43 Air Alarm to Poltava Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 04:43:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:41 Air anxiety in Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144156</link><description>游댮 07:41 Air anxiety in Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 04:41:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:39 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144155</link><description>游댮 07:39 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 04:39:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:38 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144154</link><description>游댮 07:38 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 04:38:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:17 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144153</link><description>游댮 07:17 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 04:17:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:50 PM threats of artobrats in Pokrovskaya territorial community. Solid by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144152</link><description>游릭 06:50 PM threats of artobrats in Pokrovskaya territorial community. Solid by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 03:50:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:45 PM The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144151</link><description>游릭 06:45 PM The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 03:45:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:39 Driven to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144150</link><description>游릭 06:39 Driven to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 03:39:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:17 Dumping anxiety in the Kryvyi Rih District.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144149</link><description>游릭 06:17 Dumping anxiety in the Kryvyi Rih District.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 03:17:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:15 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144148</link><description>游댮 06:15 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 03:15:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:28 Driven Alarm to Kamyansky District.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144147</link><description>游릭 05:28 Driven Alarm to Kamyansky District.Creck on Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 02:28:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:27 Driven anxiety in the Dnieper district.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144146</link><description>游릭 05:27 Driven anxiety in the Dnieper district.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 02:27:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:27 Drive alarm to Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144145</link><description>游릭 05:27 Drive alarm to Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 02:27:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:27 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144144</link><description>游릭 05:27 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 02:27:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:26 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144143</link><description>游릭 05:26 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 02:26:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:22 Air anxiety in the Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144142</link><description>游댮 05:22 Air anxiety in the Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.#Nikopol_ Region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 02:22:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:20 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144141</link><description>游댮 05:20 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.#Kryvyi Rih Ri This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 02:20:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:16 Flashing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kamyansky district- Dniprovskyi district-Sinelnikovsky district- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community- Nikopol and Nikopol territorial community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144140</link><description>游리 05:16 Flashing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kamyansky district- Dniprovskyi district-Sinelnikovsky district- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community- Nikopol and Nikopol territorial community This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 02:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:12 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd district. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144139</link><description>游리 05:12 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd district. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region#Pavlograd_RAV This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 02:12:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:12 Driven anxiety in the Novomoskovsky District. Full attention, anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144138</link><description>游리 05:12 Driven anxiety in the Novomoskovsky District. Full attention, anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region#Novomoskovsk_RAVKOD This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 02:12:47 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>