<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 18:29 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Crete on subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141792</link><description>游릭 18:29 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Crete on subsequent messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 15:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:29 Driven anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141791</link><description>游릭 18:29 Driven anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 15:29:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:29 Driven anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141790</link><description>游릭 18:29 Driven anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 15:29:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:29 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141789</link><description>游릭 18:29 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the following messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 15:29:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 18:29 Dumping anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141788</link><description>游리 18:29 Dumping anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 15:29:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:13 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya region follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141787</link><description>游댮 18:13 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya region follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 15:13:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:06 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141786</link><description>游댮 18:06 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 15:06:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:41 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141785</link><description>游릭 17:41 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 14:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:41 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141784</link><description>游릭 17:41 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADze #M_Nikopol_ti_nikopol_ Territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 14:41:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 17:23 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city center</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141783</link><description>游 17:23 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city center #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 14:23:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:23 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141782</link><description>游댮 17:23 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 14:23:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:15 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141781</link><description>游릭 17:15 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 14:15:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:56 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141780</link><description>游릭 16:56 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 13:56:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:56 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141779</link><description>游릭 16:56 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADze #M_Nikopol_ti_nikopol_ Territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 13:56:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 16:46 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city center</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141778</link><description>游 16:46 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city center #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 13:46:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:46 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141777</link><description>游댮 16:46 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 13:46:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:38 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141776</link><description>游릭 16:38 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 13:38:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:38 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141775</link><description>游릭 16:38 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 13:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:30 Air alarm to the Donetsk region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141774</link><description>游댮 16:30 Air alarm to the Donetsk region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 13:30:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:14 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141773</link><description>游댮 16:14 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 13:14:40 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>