<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 14:13 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143719</link><description>游 14:13 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 11:13:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:09 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143718</link><description>游릭 14:09 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 11:09:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:09 Driven the alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143717</link><description>游릭 14:09 Driven the alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 11:09:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:09 Driven anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143716</link><description>游릭 14:09 Driven anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 11:09:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:03 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143715</link><description>游 14:03 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 11:03:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:31 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143714</link><description>游댮 13:31 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:31:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:31 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143713</link><description>游댮 13:31 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:23 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143712</link><description>游릭 13:23 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:23:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:23 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143711</link><description>游릭 13:23 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:23:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:02 Driven the alarm to Kryvyi Rih District. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143710</link><description>游릭 13:02 Driven the alarm to Kryvyi Rih District. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:02:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:54 Attack Drones-Camikadzethip Pracement</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143709</link><description>游 12:54 Attack Drones-Camikadzethip Pracement This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 09:54:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:54 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143708</link><description>游댮 12:54 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 09:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:22 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143707</link><description>游릭 12:22 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 09:22:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:21 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143706</link><description>游댮 12:21 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 09:21:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:11 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143705</link><description>游댮 12:11 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 09:11:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:51 Close the threat of artobrats in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143704</link><description>游릭 11:51 Close the threat of artobrats in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:51:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:40 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143703</link><description>游릭 11:40 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:40:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:40 A.curely in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kryvyi Rih rayon- Marganets and Marhanetsky Territorial Community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervonohrigorivska Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143702</link><description>游리 11:40 A.curely in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kryvyi Rih rayon- Marganets and Marhanetsky Territorial Community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervonohrigorivska Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:40 Air Alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat as Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143701</link><description>游댮 11:40 Air Alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat as Further Messages.#Kryvyi Rih Ri This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:40:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:39 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143700</link><description>游릭 11:39 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:39:18 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>