<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 12:37 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150026</link><description>游릭 12:37 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 09:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:37 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150025</link><description>游릭 12:37 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 09:37:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:36 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150024</link><description>游댮 12:36 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 09:36:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:11 pm alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150023</link><description>游리 12:11 pm alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 09:11:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:08 Attack drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150022</link><description>游 12:08 Attack drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 09:08:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:56 Auxiliary alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150021</link><description>游릭 11:56 Auxiliary alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 08:56:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:48 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin Lapinka</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150020</link><description>游 11:48 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin Lapinka #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 08:48:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:47 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150019</link><description>游댮 11:47 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 08:47:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:44 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150018</link><description>游댮 11:44 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 08:44:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:10 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150017</link><description>游릭 11:10 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 08:10:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:04 PM anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150016</link><description>游릭 11:04 PM anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 08:04:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:57 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150015</link><description>游릭 10:57 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 07:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:57 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150014</link><description>游릭 10:57 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region. Since further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 07:57:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:53 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150013</link><description>游댮 10:53 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 07:53:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:51 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150012</link><description>游댮 10:51 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 07:51:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:3.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150011</link><description>游댮 10:3. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 07:39:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:16 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150010</link><description>游 10:16 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 07:16:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:13 Drive alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150009</link><description>游릭 10:13 Drive alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 07:13:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:13 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150008</link><description>游릭 10:13 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 07:13:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:13 Run the threat of shock bpadbius threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150007</link><description>游릭 10:13 Run the threat of shock bpadbius threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 07:13:40 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>