<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 20:42 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148075</link><description>游댮 20:42 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 17:42:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 19:41 Driven anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148074</link><description>游릭 19:41 Driven anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on subsequent messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 16:41:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:28 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148073</link><description>游댮 19:28 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 16:28:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 19:09 WARNING !!! DONE ASKRIGHT OF USEED AVIRTED AVIRIAL Bombs (Kabiv).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148072</link><description>游릭 19:09 WARNING !!! DONE ASKRIGHT OF USEED AVIRTED AVIRIAL Bombs (Kabiv). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 16:09:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 19:08 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148071</link><description>游릭 19:08 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 16:08:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 19:08 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148070</link><description>游릭 19:08 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 16:08:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 19:07 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148069</link><description>游리 19:07 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district#Zaporizhzhya_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 16:07:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:36 Driven the alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148068</link><description>游릭 18:36 Driven the alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on subsequent messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 15:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 18:35 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148067</link><description>游 18:35 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).#Pologovsky_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 15:35:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:35 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky district to care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148066</link><description>游댮 18:35 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky district to care for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 15:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:28 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148065</link><description>游댮 18:28 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 15:28:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 17:44 Auxiliary in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148064</link><description>游리 17:44 Auxiliary in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 14:44:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:34 The threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148063</link><description>游릭 17:34 The threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 14:34:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:34 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148062</link><description>游릭 17:34 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADze #M_Nikopol_ti_nikopol_ Territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 14:34:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:29 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148061</link><description>游릭 17:29 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 14:29:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:29 Drive the threat of using Cabbaths The threat of application</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148060</link><description>游릭 17:29 Drive the threat of using Cabbaths The threat of application This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 14:29:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 17:11 Threat of use of the CD Threat of use of managed aviation bombs</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148059</link><description>游 17:11 Threat of use of the CD Threat of use of managed aviation bombs This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 14:11:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:11 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148058</link><description>游댮 17:11 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 14:11:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:07 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148057</link><description>游댮 17:07 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 14:07:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 17:02 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148056</link><description>游 17:02 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 14:02:24 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>