<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 01:32 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144909</link><description>游댮 01:32 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad Oblast follow the following messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 22:32:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:24 Dumping anxiety in the Kiev region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144908</link><description>游릭 01:24 Dumping anxiety in the Kiev region. Since further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 22:24:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:24 Driven Alarm to Chernihiv Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144907</link><description>游릭 01:24 Driven Alarm to Chernihiv Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Chernihiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 22:24:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:23 Driven anxiety in Kyiv. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144906</link><description>游릭 01:23 Driven anxiety in Kyiv. Stop by further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 22:23:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:13 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144905</link><description>游댮 01:13 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 22:13:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:11 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144904</link><description>游댮 01:11 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 22:11:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:05 Air anxiety in the Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144903</link><description>游댮 01:05 Air anxiety in the Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Chernihiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 22:05:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:59 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144902</link><description>游댮 00:59 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 21:59:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:36 Air anxiety in the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144901</link><description>游댮 00:36 Air anxiety in the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 21:36:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:15 Drive anxiety in the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144900</link><description>游릭 00:15 Drive anxiety in the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 21:15:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:15 Drive anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creck on subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144899</link><description>游릭 00:15 Drive anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creck on subsequent messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 21:15:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:15 Drive anxiety in Cherkasy district.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144898</link><description>游릭 00:15 Drive anxiety in Cherkasy district.Creck on further reports.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 21:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:09 Air anxiety in Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Posts.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144897</link><description>游댮 00:09 Air anxiety in Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Posts.#Kryvyi Rih This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 21:09:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:07 Air alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144896</link><description>游댮 00:07 Air alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.#Nikopol. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 21:07:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:46 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144895</link><description>游댮 23:46 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow the following messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:46:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:44 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144894</link><description>游댮 23:44 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:44:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:44 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District to follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144893</link><description>游댮 23:44 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District to follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:44:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:39 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144892</link><description>游댮 23:39 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:39:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:38 Air alarm to the Dniprovsky district to care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144891</link><description>游댮 23:38 Air alarm to the Dniprovsky district to care for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:38:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:34 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144890</link><description>游댮 23:34 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:34:58 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>