<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 11:51 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin Center city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152740</link><description>游 11:51 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin Center city #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 08:51:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:49 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152739</link><description>游 11:49 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 08:49:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:35 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152738</link><description>游댮 11:35 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 08:35:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:34 Air Alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152737</link><description>游댮 11:34 Air Alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.#Nikopol_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 08:34:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:34 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152736</link><description>游댮 11:34 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 08:34:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:34 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152735</link><description>游댮 11:34 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 08:34:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:34 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152734</link><description>游댮 11:34 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 08:34:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:33 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152733</link><description>游댮 11:33 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 08:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:33 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152732</link><description>游댮 11:33 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 08:33:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:33 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152731</link><description>游댮 11:33 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 08:33:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:25 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152730</link><description>游댮 11:25 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 08:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:02 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152729</link><description>游댮 11:02 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 08:02:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:00 pm the threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take the following reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152728</link><description>游릭 11:00 pm the threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take the following reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 08:00:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:00 AM ATTENTION! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152727</link><description>游릭 11:00 AM ATTENTION! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_tay_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 08:00:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:44 Air anxiety in Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152726</link><description>游댮 10:44 Air anxiety in Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.#Pavlograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 07:44:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:44 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Survene from further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152725</link><description>游댮 10:44 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Survene from further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 07:44:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:44 Air alarm in the Dnieper District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152724</link><description>游댮 10:44 Air alarm in the Dnieper District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 07:44:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:37 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152723</link><description>游댮 10:37 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 07:37:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:37 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152722</link><description>游댮 10:37 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 07:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:35 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152721</link><description>游 10:35 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 07:35:43 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>