<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 20:01 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138576</link><description>游릭 20:01 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 17:01:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 19:22 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138575</link><description>游릭 19:22 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 16:22:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 19:12 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138574</link><description>游릭 19:12 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 16:12:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 19:12 WARNING! DROVIA DRONNE-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138573</link><description>游릭 19:12 WARNING! DROVIA DRONNE-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 16:12:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 18:43 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138572</link><description>游 18:43 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 15:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:42 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138571</link><description>游댮 18:42 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 15:42:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:33 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138570</link><description>游릭 18:33 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 15:33:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:33 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138569</link><description>游릭 18:33 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 15:33:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:23 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138568</link><description>游댮 18:23 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 15:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 18:05 Dronov-Kamikadze Dronov-Kamikadze continues</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138567</link><description>游 18:05 Dronov-Kamikadze Dronov-Kamikadze continues This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 15:05:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 17:58 Dronov-Kamikadze Dronov-Kamikadze, NFF Movement</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138566</link><description>游 17:58 Dronov-Kamikadze Dronov-Kamikadze, NFF Movement This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 14:58:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 17:55 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138565</link><description>游 17:55 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 14:55:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:54 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138564</link><description>游댮 17:54 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 14:54:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 17:53 Drawing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138563</link><description>游리 17:53 Drawing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 14:53:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:52 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138562</link><description>游릭 17:52 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 14:52:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:52 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky District. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138561</link><description>游릭 17:52 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky District. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 14:52:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:52 Driven Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138560</link><description>游릭 17:52 Driven Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 14:52:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:52 Drive the threat of use of the Cabinet of Construction by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138559</link><description>游릭 17:52 Drive the threat of use of the Cabinet of Construction by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 14:52:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:52 Driven the alarm to Cherkasy district.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138558</link><description>游릭 17:52 Driven the alarm to Cherkasy district.Creck on further reports.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 14:52:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:52 Driven Alarm to the Chernihiv Oblast. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138557</link><description>游릭 17:52 Driven Alarm to the Chernihiv Oblast. Watch for further reports.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 14:52:49 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>