<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 17:17 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138710</link><description>游릭 17:17 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 14:17:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:17 WARNING! DROVIA DRONNE-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138709</link><description>游릭 17:17 WARNING! DROVIA DRONNE-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 14:17:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 16:49 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack! Movement in the direction of the bus station!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138708</link><description>游 16:49 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack! Movement in the direction of the bus station! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 13:49:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:48 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138707</link><description>游댮 16:48 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 13:48:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:26 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138706</link><description>游릭 16:26 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 13:26:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:26 Reduce threatening Cabbaths The threat of application</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138705</link><description>游릭 16:26 Reduce threatening Cabbaths The threat of application This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 13:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:20 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138704</link><description>游릭 16:20 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 13:20:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:20 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138703</link><description>游릭 16:20 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 13:20:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 16:07 Threat of use of the copecreal use of managed aviation bombs</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138702</link><description>游 16:07 Threat of use of the copecreal use of managed aviation bombs#m_harkiv_tha_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 13:07:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:06 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138701</link><description>游댮 16:06 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 13:06:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 16:01 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, traffic in the direction of the city center!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138700</link><description>游 16:01 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, traffic in the direction of the city center! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 13:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 15:58 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138699</link><description>游 15:58 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 12:58:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:48 Threat of Artbill! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138698</link><description>游댮 15:48 Threat of Artbill! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 12:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 15:39 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138697</link><description>游 15:39 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 12:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:39 Threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138696</link><description>游댮 15:39 Threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 12:39:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 15:27 Drawing of anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Manganese and Marganets Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138695</link><description>游리 15:27 Drawing of anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Manganese and Marganets Territorial Community#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 12:27:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:25 Failure to alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138694</link><description>游릭 15:25 Failure to alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 12:25:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:25 Reduce threatening shock bpadbius threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138693</link><description>游릭 15:25 Reduce threatening shock bpadbius threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 12:25:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 15:09 The threat of artobrytile to the Chervonohrigor territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138692</link><description>游리 15:09 The threat of artobrytile to the Chervonohrigor territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 12:09:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:07 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138691</link><description>游댮 15:07 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 12:07:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>