<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 21:30 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142525</link><description>游댮 21:30 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 18:30:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 20:46 Failure to alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142524</link><description>游리 20:46 Failure to alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:45 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142523</link><description>游릭 20:45 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:45:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:17 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142522</link><description>游댮 20:17 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:17:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:17 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142521</link><description>游댮 20:17 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:17:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 19:29 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142520</link><description>游 19:29 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 16:29:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:29 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142519</link><description>游댮 19:29 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 16:29:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 19:29 Driven anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142518</link><description>游릭 19:29 Driven anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 16:29:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 19:03 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142517</link><description>游릭 19:03 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 16:03:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 19:03 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142516</link><description>游릭 19:03 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the following messages.#Zaporizhzhia. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 16:03:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:53 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142515</link><description>游댮 18:53 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:53:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:53 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142514</link><description>游댮 18:53 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:53:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:52 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142513</link><description>游댮 18:52 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:52:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:21 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142512</link><description>游릭 18:21 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:21:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:20 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142511</link><description>游릭 18:20 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:20:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:16 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District to follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142510</link><description>游댮 17:16 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District to follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:16:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:54 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142509</link><description>游릭 16:54 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:54:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:54 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast. Since Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142508</link><description>游릭 16:54 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast. Since Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:54:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 16:54 Alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142507</link><description>游리 16:54 Alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:26 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142506</link><description>游릭 16:26 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:26:14 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>