<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 13:14 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130473</link><description>游댮 13:14 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 11:14:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:07 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130472</link><description>游릭 13:07 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 11:07:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:59 Dumping anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130471</link><description>游릭 12:59 Dumping anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 10:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:59 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130470</link><description>游릭 12:59 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 10:59:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:59 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130469</link><description>游릭 12:59 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 10:59:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:59 Market threats of percussion bplavidbiy threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130468</link><description>游릭 12:59 Market threats of percussion bplavidbiy threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 10:59:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:58 Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Mirovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130467</link><description>游리 12:58 Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Mirovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 10:58:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:58 Driven Alarm to Poltava Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130466</link><description>游릭 12:58 Driven Alarm to Poltava Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 10:58:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:58 Alarm to Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130465</link><description>游리 12:58 Alarm to Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 10:58:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:58 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130464</link><description>游릭 12:58 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 10:58:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:58 threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130463</link><description>游댮 12:58 threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 10:58:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:58 Dumping anxiety in the Kiev region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130462</link><description>游릭 12:58 Dumping anxiety in the Kiev region. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 10:58:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:30 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130461</link><description>游댮 12:30 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 10:30:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:28 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130460</link><description>游댮 12:28 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 10:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:28 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130459</link><description>游댮 12:28 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 10:28:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:28 Flowing anxiety in Pologovsky District. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130458</link><description>游리 12:28 Flowing anxiety in Pologovsky District. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya region#Pologovsky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 10:28:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:28 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130457</link><description>游댮 12:28 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 10:28:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:28 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130456</link><description>游댮 12:28 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 10:28:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:28 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130455</link><description>游댮 12:28 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 10:28:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:28 Air anxiety in Pologovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130454</link><description>游댮 12:28 Air anxiety in Pologovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 10:28:01 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>