<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游리 17:38 Auxiliary in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky Territorial Community, Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Mirovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133988</link><description>游리 17:38 Auxiliary in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky Territorial Community, Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Mirovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 15:38:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:21 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133987</link><description>游댮 17:21 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 15:21:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:07 The threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133986</link><description>游댮 17:07 The threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 15:07:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:06 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133985</link><description>游댮 17:06 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 15:06:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 17:05 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133984</link><description>游리 17:05 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 15:05:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:58 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133983</link><description>游릭 16:58 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 14:58:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:40 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133982</link><description>游댮 16:40 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 14:40:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:16 Driven anxiety in the Odesa region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133981</link><description>游릭 16:16 Driven anxiety in the Odesa region. Watch for further messages.#Odessa_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 14:16:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:58 Driven Alarm to Cherkasy District.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133980</link><description>游릭 15:58 Driven Alarm to Cherkasy District.Creck on Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 13:58:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:58 Dumping anxiety in Zolotonsky District. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133979</link><description>游릭 15:58 Dumping anxiety in Zolotonsky District. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 13:58:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:58 Driven the alarm to Poltava region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133978</link><description>游릭 15:58 Driven the alarm to Poltava region.Creck on further messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 13:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:52 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District to follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133977</link><description>游댮 15:52 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District to follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 13:52:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:52 Air alarm to Cherkasy District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133976</link><description>游댮 15:52 Air alarm to Cherkasy District Surveat for Further Messages.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 13:52:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:52 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133975</link><description>游댮 15:52 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 13:52:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:49 Air alarm to the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133974</link><description>游댮 15:49 Air alarm to the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 13:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:44 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133973</link><description>游릭 15:44 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 13:44:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:12 Return the threat of Artobstil to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133972</link><description>游릭 15:12 Return the threat of Artobstil to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 13:12:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:10 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133971</link><description>游댮 15:10 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 13:10:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:09 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133970</link><description>游릭 15:09 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 13:09:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:17 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133969</link><description>游댮 14:17 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 12:17:47 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>