<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>🟢 00:50:50 Pleasure in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145203</link><description>🟢 00:50:50 Pleasure in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 21:50:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 00:50 PM Alarm to Zaporizhzhya region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145202</link><description>🟢 00:50 PM Alarm to Zaporizhzhya region. Since further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 21:50:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 00:19 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145201</link><description>🟢 00:19 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 21:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 00:18 Air anxiety in Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145200</link><description>🔴 00:18 Air anxiety in Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 21:18:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 00:18 Driven your alarm to Donetsk region. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145199</link><description>🟢 00:18 Driven your alarm to Donetsk region. Stop by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 21:18:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 00:16 Drive anxiety in the Sinelnikov District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145198</link><description>🟢 00:16 Drive anxiety in the Sinelnikov District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 21:16:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟡 00:16 Flashing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145197</link><description>🟡 00:16 Flashing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 21:16:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 00:13 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145196</link><description>🔴 00:13 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 21:13:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 00:13 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145195</link><description>🔴 00:13 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 21:13:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 00:12 Threat of Arteball! Pokrovskaya Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145194</link><description>🔴 00:12 Threat of Arteball! Pokrovskaya Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 21:12:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 00:11 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145193</link><description>🟢 00:11 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 21:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 23:30 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145192</link><description>🔴 23:30 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 20:30:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 23:27 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145191</link><description>🔴 23:27 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 20:27:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 22:57 Air alarm to the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145190</link><description>🔴 22:57 Air alarm to the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 19:57:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 22:54 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145189</link><description>🔴 22:54 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 19:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 21:40 Attention! Drone attack! Possible discharges! The area of ​​the old part</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145188</link><description>🟠 21:40 Attention! Drone attack! Possible discharges! The area of ​​the old part #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 18:40:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:40 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145187</link><description>🔴 21:40 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 18:40:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 21:33 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145186</link><description>🟢 21:33 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 18:33:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:28 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145185</link><description>🔴 21:28 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 18:28:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:28 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145184</link><description>🔴 21:28 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast follow the following messages.#Kharkiv_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 18:28:38 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>