<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 12:25 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145279</link><description>游릭 12:25 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 09:25:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:25 Attention! Droze Dronov-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145278</link><description>游릭 12:25 Attention! Droze Dronov-Kamikadze #M_Nikopol_ti_nikopol_ Territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 09:25:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:24 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145277</link><description>游댮 12:24 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 09:24:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:04 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack continues</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145276</link><description>游 12:04 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack continues This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 09:04:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:22 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin of the old part</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145275</link><description>游 11:22 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin of the old part #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 08:22:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:17 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145274</link><description>游 11:17 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 08:17:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:14 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145273</link><description>游댮 11:14 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 08:14:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:49 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145272</link><description>游댮 10:49 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 07:49:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:13 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145271</link><description>游릭 10:13 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 07:13:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:00 pimplifting the threat of artebing in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145270</link><description>游릭 10:00 pimplifting the threat of artebing in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 07:00:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:00 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145269</link><description>游릭 10:00 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 07:00:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145268</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 07:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:52 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145267</link><description>游댮 09:52 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 06:52:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:36 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack is ongoing, area 3 sections</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145266</link><description>游 09:36 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack is ongoing, area 3 sections #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 06:36:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:35 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145265</link><description>游댮 09:35 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 06:35:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:28 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145264</link><description>游댮 09:28 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 06:28:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:22 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145263</link><description>游릭 09:22 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 06:22:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 09:22 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145262</link><description>游리 09:22 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community#Kharkiv_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 06:22:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 09:22 Drawing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganets Territorial Community, Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivsk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145261</link><description>游리 09:22 Drawing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganets Territorial Community, Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivsk Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 06:22:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:09 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack continues</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145260</link><description>游 09:09 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack continues This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 06:09:47 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>