<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 06:40 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast. Since Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134418</link><description>游릭 06:40 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast. Since Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 04:40:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:40 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134417</link><description>游릭 06:40 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 04:40:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:40 Down the threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134416</link><description>游릭 06:40 Down the threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 04:40:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 06:40 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134415</link><description>游리 06:40 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 04:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:02 Flow to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134414</link><description>游릭 06:02 Flow to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 04:02:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:02 Driven the alarm to Poltava region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134413</link><description>游릭 06:02 Driven the alarm to Poltava region. Since further reports.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 04:02:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:42 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creck on subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134412</link><description>游릭 05:42 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creck on subsequent messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 03:42:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:42 Driven the alarm to Cherkasy district. Stop the following reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134411</link><description>游릭 05:42 Driven the alarm to Cherkasy district. Stop the following reports.#Cherkasy_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 03:42:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:42 Drive alarm to Uman District.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134410</link><description>游릭 05:42 Drive alarm to Uman District.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 03:42:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:42 Driven the alarm to Zvenigorod district. Stop after further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134409</link><description>游릭 05:42 Driven the alarm to Zvenigorod district. Stop after further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 03:42:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:09 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134408</link><description>游릭 04:09 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 02:09:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:09 Driven anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134407</link><description>游릭 04:09 Driven anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 02:09:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 04:01 Drawing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivka Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134406</link><description>游리 04:01 Drawing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivka Territorial Community#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 02:01:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:32 Frame alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134405</link><description>游릭 03:32 Frame alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 01:32:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:32 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134404</link><description>游릭 03:32 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 01:32:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 03:30 WARNING !!! Notice, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134403</link><description>游리 03:30 WARNING !!! Notice, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya region#Pologovsky_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 01:30:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:15 Driven the alarm to the Kiev region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134402</link><description>游릭 03:15 Driven the alarm to the Kiev region. Since further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 01:15:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:15 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134401</link><description>游릭 03:15 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 01:15:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:13 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134400</link><description>游댮 02:13 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:13:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:13 Air alarm in Zvenigorod District to care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134399</link><description>游댮 02:13 Air alarm in Zvenigorod District to care for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:13:47 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>