<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 14:39 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154191</link><description>游릭 14:39 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region. Since further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 11:39:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:38 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154190</link><description>游릭 14:38 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 11:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:22 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154189</link><description>游댮 14:22 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 11:22:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:10 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154188</link><description>游 14:10 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 11:10:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:08 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154187</link><description>游댮 14:08 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 11:08:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:04 Air alarm to the Donetsk region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154186</link><description>游댮 14:04 Air alarm to the Donetsk region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 11:04:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:00 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154185</link><description>游 14:00 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 11:00:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:56 Return the threat of Artobstil to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154184</link><description>游릭 13:56 Return the threat of Artobstil to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 10:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:44 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154183</link><description>游댮 13:44 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 10:44:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:42 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154182</link><description>游릭 13:42 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 10:42:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:42 WARNING! DRAWE DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154181</link><description>游릭 13:42 WARNING! DRAWE DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 10:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:02 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154180</link><description>游릭 13:02 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 10:02:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:02 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154179</link><description>游릭 13:02 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporozhye This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 10:02:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 13:02 Attention !!! Note, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154178</link><description>游리 13:02 Attention !!! Note, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya region#Zaporizhzhya_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 10:02:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:02 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154177</link><description>游릭 13:02 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 10:02:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:02 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154176</link><description>游릭 13:02 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 10:02:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:41 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154175</link><description>游댮 12:41 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 09:41:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:35 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabins).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154174</link><description>游 12:35 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabins). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 09:35:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:28 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154173</link><description>游댮 12:28 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 09:28:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:09 Attack drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154172</link><description>游 12:09 Attack drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 09:09:50 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>