<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 20:20 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya region follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144074</link><description>游댮 20:20 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya region follow further messages.#Of Zaporizhzhia_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 17:20:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:13 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144073</link><description>游릭 20:13 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 17:13:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:13 Run the threat of shock bpadbium threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144072</link><description>游릭 20:13 Run the threat of shock bpadbium threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 17:13:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:08 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144071</link><description>游댮 20:08 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 17:08:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:06 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144070</link><description>游댮 20:06 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 17:06:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 20:02 The threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144069</link><description>游 20:02 The threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"#m_harkiv_tha_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 17:02:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:02 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144068</link><description>游댮 20:02 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 17:02:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:01 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144067</link><description>游댮 20:01 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 17:01:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>?</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144066</link><description>? This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 16:59:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:28 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144065</link><description>游댮 19:28 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 16:28:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:53 Driven anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144064</link><description>游릭 18:53 Driven anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:53:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:52 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144063</link><description>游릭 18:52 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:52:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:03 WARNING !!! DONE ALREADY OF USED AVIRTED AVIRT BOMB (Kabiv).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144062</link><description>游릭 18:03 WARNING !!! DONE ALREADY OF USED AVIRTED AVIRT BOMB (Kabiv). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:03:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 18:01 Flowing anxiety in the Zaporizhzhia region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144061</link><description>游리 18:01 Flowing anxiety in the Zaporizhzhia region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district#Zaporizhzhia_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:49 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144060</link><description>游릭 17:49 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:49:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:37 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144059</link><description>游댮 17:37 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 17:27 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144058</link><description>游 17:27 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:27:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:17 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144057</link><description>游댮 17:17 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:17:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:11 The threat of a shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144056</link><description>游릭 17:11 The threat of a shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:11:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:01 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144055</link><description>游댮 17:01 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:01:49 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>