<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 17:16 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146780</link><description>游릭 17:16 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 14:16:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 17:09 Attack Dronivative Ammunition Discharges, Old Store area</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146779</link><description>游 17:09 Attack Dronivative Ammunition Discharges, Old Store area #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 14:09:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 17:07 Failure to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Sinelnikovsky rayon- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivska Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146778</link><description>游리 17:07 Failure to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Sinelnikovsky rayon- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivska Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 14:07:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:06 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146777</link><description>游릭 17:06 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 14:06:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:06 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146776</link><description>游릭 17:06 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 14:06:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:06 Flow to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146775</link><description>游릭 17:06 Flow to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 14:06:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:06 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146774</link><description>游릭 17:06 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 14:06:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:05 Draw alarms to Poltava region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146773</link><description>游릭 17:05 Draw alarms to Poltava region. Since further reports.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 14:05:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 17:05 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146772</link><description>游리 17:05 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 14:05:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:03 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146771</link><description>游릭 17:03 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 14:03:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:32 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146770</link><description>游댮 16:32 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:32:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:32 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146769</link><description>游댮 16:32 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:32:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:31 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146768</link><description>游댮 16:31 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:31:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:31 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146767</link><description>游댮 16:31 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:31:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:31 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146766</link><description>游댮 16:31 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:31 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146765</link><description>游댮 16:31 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:31 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146764</link><description>游댮 16:31 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:31:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:31 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146763</link><description>游댮 16:31 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:31:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:05 Driven Alarm to the Chernihiv Oblast. Follow the subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146762</link><description>游릭 16:05 Driven Alarm to the Chernihiv Oblast. Follow the subsequent messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:05:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 15:57 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146761</link><description>游 15:57 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 12:57:16 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>