<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游리 17:18 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135246</link><description>游리 17:18 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 14:18:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 17:11 The threat of a shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Consider, the alarm is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135245</link><description>游리 17:11 The threat of a shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Consider, the alarm is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region#m_nikopol_that_nikopol. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 14:11:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:07 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135244</link><description>游댮 17:07 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 14:07:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:02 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135243</link><description>游댮 17:02 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 14:02:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:00 AMACK IN Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135242</link><description>游릭 17:00 AMACK IN Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 14:00:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:59 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135241</link><description>游댮 16:59 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 13:59:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:59 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135240</link><description>游댮 16:59 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 13:59:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:51 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135239</link><description>游댮 16:51 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 13:51:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:48 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135238</link><description>游릭 16:48 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 13:48:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:16 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135237</link><description>游댮 16:16 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 13:16:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:13 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135236</link><description>游릭 16:13 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 13:13:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:54 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135235</link><description>游댮 15:54 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 12:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:32 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135234</link><description>游댮 15:32 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 12:32:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:22 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135233</link><description>游릭 15:22 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 12:22:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:12 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135232</link><description>游댮 15:12 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 12:12:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:09 Threat of Arteball! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135231</link><description>游댮 15:09 Threat of Arteball! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 12:09:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:52 The threat of shelling! Now in the Mirovskaya Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135230</link><description>游댮 14:52 The threat of shelling! Now in the Mirovskaya Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 11:52:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:42 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135229</link><description>游댮 14:42 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 11:42:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:33 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135228</link><description>游릭 14:33 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 11:33:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:08 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135227</link><description>游댮 14:08 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 11:08:59 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>