<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 13:17 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134446</link><description>游릭 13:17 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 11:17:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:17 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134445</link><description>游릭 13:17 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 11:17:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:16 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134444</link><description>游릭 13:16 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the following messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 11:16:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 13:16 Failure to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky Territorial Community, Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134443</link><description>游리 13:16 Failure to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky Territorial Community, Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 11:16:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:12 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134442</link><description>游댮 13:12 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 11:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:03 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134441</link><description>游댮 13:03 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 11:03:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:03 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134440</link><description>游댮 13:03 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 11:03:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:03 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134439</link><description>游댮 13:03 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 11:03:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:47 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134438</link><description>游댮 12:47 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 10:47:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:34 Close the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134437</link><description>游릭 12:34 Close the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 10:34:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:05 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134436</link><description>游릭 12:05 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region. Stop by further messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 10:05:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:57 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134435</link><description>游댮 11:57 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 09:57:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:54 Threat of Artbill! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134434</link><description>游댮 11:54 Threat of Artbill! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 09:54:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:35 Return of the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134433</link><description>游릭 11:35 Return of the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 09:35:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:23 Driven anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134432</link><description>游릭 11:23 Driven anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 09:23:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:08 PM threats of artobrats in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134431</link><description>游릭 11:08 PM threats of artobrats in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 09:08:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:54 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134430</link><description>游댮 10:54 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 08:54:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:41 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134429</link><description>游릭 10:41 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 08:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 10:38 Fragrance in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134428</link><description>游리 10:38 Fragrance in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 08:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134427</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 08:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>