<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 13:42 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143512</link><description>游댮 13:42 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:42:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:41 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Crete on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143511</link><description>游릭 13:41 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Crete on further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:41:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:40 Driven anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143510</link><description>游릭 13:40 Driven anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:40:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:40 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143509</link><description>游릭 13:40 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Creat by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 13:29 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the old part</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143508</link><description>游 13:29 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the old part This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:29 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143507</link><description>游댮 13:29 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:29:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:07 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143506</link><description>游댮 13:07 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:07:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:56 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143505</link><description>游댮 12:56 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 09:56:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:54 Axiety in Zaporizhzhia region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143504</link><description>游릭 12:54 Axiety in Zaporizhzhia region. Since further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 09:54:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:50 PM The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143503</link><description>游릭 12:50 PM The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 09:50:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:32 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143502</link><description>游댮 12:32 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 09:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:29 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143501</link><description>游릭 12:29 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 09:29:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:29 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143500</link><description>游리 12:29 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 09:29:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:00 pm alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143499</link><description>游릭 12:00 pm alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 09:00:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:00 Return the threat of percussion bplavidbium threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143498</link><description>游릭 12:00 Return the threat of percussion bplavidbium threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 09:00:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:54 The threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143497</link><description>游 11:54 The threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 08:54:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:53 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143496</link><description>游댮 11:53 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 08:53:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:29 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143495</link><description>游댮 11:29 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 08:29:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:02 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143494</link><description>游릭 11:02 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 08:02:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:02 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143493</link><description>游릭 11:02 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 08:02:13 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>