<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 12:47 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131306</link><description>游댮 12:47 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 10:47:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:16 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Make sure</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131305</link><description>游릭 12:16 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Make sure This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 10:16:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:56 Return of the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131304</link><description>游릭 11:56 Return of the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 09:56:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:43 Return the threat of Artobstil to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131303</link><description>游릭 11:43 Return the threat of Artobstil to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 09:43:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:41 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131302</link><description>游댮 11:41 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:35 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131301</link><description>游릭 11:35 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 09:35:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:34 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131300</link><description>游릭 11:34 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creat by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 09:34:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:34 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131299</link><description>游릭 11:34 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region.Creck on further messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 09:34:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:34 A.c.34 Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganese territorial community-mirorskaya territorial community- Chervono-Grigorivka territorial community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131298</link><description>游리 11:34 A.c.34 Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganese territorial community-mirorskaya territorial community- Chervono-Grigorivka territorial community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 09:34:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:07 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131297</link><description>游댮 11:07 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 09:07:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:07 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131296</link><description>游댮 11:07 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 09:07:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:36 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131295</link><description>游댮 10:36 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 08:36:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:26 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131294</link><description>游댮 10:26 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 08:26:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:14 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131293</link><description>游댮 10:14 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 08:14:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131292</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 08:00:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:16 Air anxiety in Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131291</link><description>游댮 08:16 Air anxiety in Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 06:16:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:51 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131290</link><description>游릭 06:51 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 04:51:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:37 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131289</link><description>游릭 05:37 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 03:37:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 03:46 Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-mirorskaya territorial community-Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131288</link><description>游리 03:46 Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-mirorskaya territorial community-Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 01:46:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:46 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131287</link><description>游릭 03:46 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 01:46:31 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>