<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 17:40 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136772</link><description>游 17:40 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 14:40:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:32 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136771</link><description>游댮 17:32 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 14:32:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:31 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136770</link><description>游댮 17:31 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 14:31:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 17:30 The threat of use of the cope proportion of the use</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136769</link><description>游 17:30 The threat of use of the cope proportion of the use This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 14:30:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:29 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136768</link><description>游댮 17:29 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 14:29:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:18 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136767</link><description>游댮 17:18 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 14:18:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:17 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136766</link><description>游릭 17:17 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 14:17:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:17 Drive the threat of shock bplavidbiy threat of percussion UAV</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136765</link><description>游릭 17:17 Drive the threat of shock bplavidbiy threat of percussion UAV#M_Kharkiv_that_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 14:17:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:08 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136764</link><description>游댮 17:08 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 14:08:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:02 Air anxiety in the Zhytomyr region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136763</link><description>游댮 17:02 Air anxiety in the Zhytomyr region follow the following messages.#Zhytomyr_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 14:02:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 17:00 The threat of shock Bplasaggras of UAV type "Prayer"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136762</link><description>游 17:00 The threat of shock Bplasaggras of UAV type "Prayer"#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 14:00:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:59 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136761</link><description>游댮 16:59 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 13:59:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:57 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136760</link><description>游댮 16:57 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 13:57:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:46 Return the threat of artebing to Pokrovskaya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136759</link><description>游릭 16:46 Return the threat of artebing to Pokrovskaya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 13:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:44 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136758</link><description>游릭 16:44 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Since further reports.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 13:44:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:44 alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136757</link><description>游릭 16:44 alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 13:44:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:44 Draw an alarm to Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136756</link><description>游릭 16:44 Draw an alarm to Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporozhye This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 13:44:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:43 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136755</link><description>游댮 16:43 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 13:43:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:43 Driven anxiety in the Odesa region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136754</link><description>游릭 16:43 Driven anxiety in the Odesa region.Creck on further messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 13:43:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:42 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136753</link><description>游릭 16:42 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 13:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>