<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 4</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140992</link><description>游 4 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 01:30:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:30 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140991</link><description>游댮 04:30 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 01:30:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:30 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140990</link><description>游댮 04:30 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 01:30:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:27 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140989</link><description>游릭 04:27 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 01:27:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:27 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140988</link><description>游릭 04:27 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 01:27:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:26 Drive alarm to Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140987</link><description>游릭 04:26 Drive alarm to Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 01:26:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:26 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140986</link><description>游릭 04:26 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District. Watch for further reports.#Pavlograd_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 01:26:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:26 Driven anxiety in the Dnieper district.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140985</link><description>游릭 04:26 Driven anxiety in the Dnieper district.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 01:26:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:26 Failure to alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140984</link><description>游릭 04:26 Failure to alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 01:26:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:26 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsk District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140983</link><description>游릭 04:26 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsk District.Creck on further reports.#Novomoskovsky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 01:26:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:26 Drives the threat of shock Blividbium threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140982</link><description>游릭 04:26 Drives the threat of shock Blividbium threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 01:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:26 Drive alarm to Kamyansky District.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140981</link><description>游릭 04:26 Drive alarm to Kamyansky District.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 01:26:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:26 Driven anxiety in Kryvyi Rih District.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140980</link><description>游릭 04:26 Driven anxiety in Kryvyi Rih District.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 01:26:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 04:26 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140979</link><description>游리 04:26 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 01:26:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:57 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140978</link><description>游댮 03:57 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 00:57:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:57 Air alarm to Cherkasy district care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140977</link><description>游댮 03:57 Air alarm to Cherkasy district care for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 00:57:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:18 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Follow the subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140976</link><description>游릭 03:18 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Follow the subsequent messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 00:18:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:17 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140975</link><description>游릭 03:17 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 00:17:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:05 Air anxiety in Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140974</link><description>游댮 03:05 Air anxiety in Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kirovograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 00:05:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:58 Air anxiety in Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140973</link><description>游댮 02:58 Air anxiety in Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.#Kryvyi Rih Ri This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 23:58:51 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>