<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 10:48 threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138029</link><description>游댮 10:48 threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 07:48:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:36 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138028</link><description>游릭 10:36 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Since further reports.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 07:36:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:36 Flow to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138027</link><description>游릭 10:36 Flow to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 07:36:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:34 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138026</link><description>游릭 10:34 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 07:34:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:31 Draw an alarm to Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138025</link><description>游릭 10:31 Draw an alarm to Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 07:31:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 10:25 Fragrant alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138024</link><description>游리 10:25 Fragrant alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 07:25:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:22 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138023</link><description>游댮 10:22 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 07:22:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:21 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138022</link><description>游댮 10:21 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 07:21:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:05 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138021</link><description>游댮 10:05 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 07:05:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:04 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138020</link><description>游댮 10:04 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 07:04:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:01 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138019</link><description>游댮 10:01 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 07:01:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138018</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 07:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:57 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138017</link><description>游댮 09:57 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 06:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:50 Pleasure threats of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138016</link><description>游릭 09:50 Pleasure threats of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 06:50:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 9:44</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138015</link><description>游댮 9:44 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 06:44:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:35 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138014</link><description>游댮 09:35 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 06:35:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:27 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138013</link><description>游릭 09:27 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 06:27:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:27 Driven the anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138012</link><description>游릭 09:27 Driven the anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 06:27:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:27 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138011</link><description>游릭 09:27 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 06:27:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:27 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138010</link><description>游릭 09:27 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 06:27:05 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>