<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 18:18 Driven the threat of Artobstil to Pokrovskaya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134782</link><description>游릭 18:18 Driven the threat of Artobstil to Pokrovskaya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 16:18:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:47 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134781</link><description>游릭 17:47 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 15:47:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:47 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134780</link><description>游릭 17:47 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the following messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 15:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:47 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134779</link><description>游릭 17:47 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 15:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 17:47 Failure to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community- Pokrovskaya Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivka Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134778</link><description>游리 17:47 Failure to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community- Pokrovskaya Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivka Territorial Community#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 15:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 17:45 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134777</link><description>游리 17:45 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 15:45:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:52 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134776</link><description>游댮 16:52 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 14:52:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 16:49 The threat of artebing in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134775</link><description>游리 16:49 The threat of artebing in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 14:49:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:34 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134774</link><description>游댮 16:34 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 14:34:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:34 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134773</link><description>游댮 16:34 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 14:34:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:17 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134772</link><description>游댮 16:17 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 14:17:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:09 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134771</link><description>游릭 16:09 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 14:09:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:57 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134770</link><description>游댮 15:57 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:57:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 15:38 Drawing of anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134769</link><description>游리 15:38 Drawing of anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:38:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:37 Close the threat of artbilitril in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134768</link><description>游릭 15:37 Close the threat of artbilitril in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:37:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:34 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134767</link><description>游댮 15:34 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:34:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:33 The threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134766</link><description>游댮 15:33 The threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:33:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 15:00 A.Corets in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district-Lipetsk territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134765</link><description>游리 15:00 A.Corets in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district-Lipetsk territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community#Kharkiv_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:00:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:52 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134764</link><description>游댮 14:52 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:52:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:42 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134763</link><description>游릭 14:42 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:42:39 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>