<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>🔴 19:45 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127636</link><description>🔴 19:45 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 17:45:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 19:29 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127635</link><description>🔴 19:29 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 17:29:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 18:58 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127634</link><description>🔴 18:58 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 16:58:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟡 18:16 Flashing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127633</link><description>🟡 18:16 Flashing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 16:16:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟡 18:09 Driven the threat of percussion BLAZPLACE, anxiety is still in:- Kharkiv region- Kharkiv district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127632</link><description>🟡 18:09 Driven the threat of percussion BLAZPLACE, anxiety is still in:- Kharkiv region- Kharkiv district#m_harkiv_tha_tha_harkiv_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 16:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 17:56 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127631</link><description>🟢 17:56 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 15:56:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 17:54 The threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127630</link><description>🟠 17:54 The threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"#m_harkiv_that_harkivskaya_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 15:54:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 17:21 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127629</link><description>🟢 17:21 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 15:21:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 16:53 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127628</link><description>🟢 16:53 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 14:53:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 16:28 Driven Alarm to Kyiv Oblast. Since Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127627</link><description>🟢 16:28 Driven Alarm to Kyiv Oblast. Since Further Messages.#Kyiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 14:28:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 16:25 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127626</link><description>🔴 16:25 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 14:25:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 16:23 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127625</link><description>🔴 16:23 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 14:23:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 16:13 Driven anxiety in Cherkasy district.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127624</link><description>🟢 16:13 Driven anxiety in Cherkasy district.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 14:13:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 16:13 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127623</link><description>🟢 16:13 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 14:13:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 15:53 ​​Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127622</link><description>🔴 15:53 ​​Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 13:53:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 15:53 ​​Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127621</link><description>🟢 15:53 ​​Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 13:53:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 15:25 Driven the alarm to the Poltava region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127620</link><description>🟢 15:25 Driven the alarm to the Poltava region. Watch for further messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 13:25:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 15:20 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127619</link><description>🔴 15:20 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 13:20:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 15:01 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127618</link><description>🔴 15:01 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 13:01:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 14:59 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127617</link><description>🔴 14:59 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 12:59:23 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>