<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 01:55 Dumping anxiety in the Odesa region. Follow the subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146262</link><description>游릭 01:55 Dumping anxiety in the Odesa region. Follow the subsequent messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 22:55:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 1:49</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146261</link><description>游댮 1:49 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 22:49:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:41 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146260</link><description>游릭 01:41 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 22:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:33 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146259</link><description>游릭 01:33 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District. Solve for further reports.#Pavlograd_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 22:33:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:32 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsk District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146258</link><description>游릭 01:32 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsk District. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 22:32:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:57 Driven your alarm to Sumy region.Creat for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146257</link><description>游릭 00:57 Driven your alarm to Sumy region.Creat for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 21:57:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:57 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146256</link><description>游릭 00:57 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 21:57:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:46 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146255</link><description>游댮 00:46 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 21:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:45 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146254</link><description>游댮 00:45 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 21:45:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:43 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146253</link><description>游릭 00:43 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 21:43:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:43 Drive the threat of shock bpadbias threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146252</link><description>游릭 00:43 Drive the threat of shock bpadbias threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 21:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:40 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146251</link><description>游릭 00:40 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 21:40:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:39 Driven anxiety in the Dnieper district.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146250</link><description>游릭 00:39 Driven anxiety in the Dnieper district.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 21:39:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:38 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146249</link><description>游릭 00:38 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 21:38:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:28 Drive anxiety in the Poltava region.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146248</link><description>游릭 00:28 Drive anxiety in the Poltava region.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 21:28:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:09 Air anxiety in the Dnieper District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146247</link><description>游댮 00:09 Air anxiety in the Dnieper District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 21:09:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:09 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146246</link><description>游댮 00:09 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 21:09:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:09 Air anxiety in Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146245</link><description>游댮 00:09 Air anxiety in Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.#Pavlograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 21:09:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:09 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146244</link><description>游댮 00:09 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 21:09:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:04 Air anxiety in Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146243</link><description>游댮 00:04 Air anxiety in Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.#Nikopol. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 21:04:02 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>