<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 11:46 Attack drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148703</link><description>游 11:46 Attack drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 08:46:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:45 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city center</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148702</link><description>游 11:45 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city center #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 08:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:44 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin Lapinka</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148701</link><description>游 11:44 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin Lapinka #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 08:44:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:43 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148700</link><description>游댮 11:43 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 08:43:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:42 Dronov-Kamikadze Attack! Movement on the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148699</link><description>游 11:42 Dronov-Kamikadze Attack! Movement on the city#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 08:42:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:41 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148698</link><description>游댮 11:41 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 08:41:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:34 Dumping anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148697</link><description>游릭 11:34 Dumping anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 08:34:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:20 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148696</link><description>游릭 11:20 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 08:20:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:20 pads of anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district-Lipetsk territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148695</link><description>游리 11:20 pads of anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district-Lipetsk territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community#Kharkiv_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 08:20:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:13 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148694</link><description>游댮 11:13 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 08:13:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:20 alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148693</link><description>游릭 10:20 alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 07:20:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:20 Return the threat of using Cabbaths The threat of application</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148692</link><description>游릭 10:20 Return the threat of using Cabbaths The threat of application This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 07:20:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:18 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148691</link><description>游릭 10:18 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 07:18:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:18 Attention! Sleep Dronov-Kamikadze's attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148690</link><description>游릭 10:18 Attention! Sleep Dronov-Kamikadze's attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 07:18:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148689</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 07:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 9</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148688</link><description>游 9 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 06:56:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:54 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148687</link><description>游댮 09:54 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 06:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:54 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148686</link><description>游댮 09:54 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 06:54:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:30 Threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148685</link><description>游댮 09:30 Threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 06:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:22 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148684</link><description>游댮 09:22 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 06:22:51 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>