<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 15:30 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130484</link><description>游댮 15:30 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 13:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:29 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130483</link><description>游댮 15:29 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 13:29:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 15:29 The threat of use of the copecreal use of managed aviation bombs</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130482</link><description>游 15:29 The threat of use of the copecreal use of managed aviation bombs#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 13:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:25 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130481</link><description>游릭 15:25 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 13:25:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:55 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130480</link><description>游댮 14:55 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 12:55:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:45 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130479</link><description>游릭 14:45 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 12:45:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:40 Driven Alarm to the Chernihiv Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130478</link><description>游릭 14:40 Driven Alarm to the Chernihiv Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 12:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:30 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. Walk to the shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130477</link><description>游댮 14:30 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. Walk to the shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 12:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:29 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130476</link><description>游 14:29 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 12:29:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:27 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130475</link><description>游릭 14:27 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 12:27:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:53 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130474</link><description>游댮 13:53 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 11:53:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:14 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130473</link><description>游댮 13:14 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 11:14:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:07 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130472</link><description>游릭 13:07 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 11:07:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:59 Dumping anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130471</link><description>游릭 12:59 Dumping anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 10:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:59 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130470</link><description>游릭 12:59 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 10:59:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:59 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130469</link><description>游릭 12:59 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 10:59:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:59 Market threats of percussion bplavidbiy threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130468</link><description>游릭 12:59 Market threats of percussion bplavidbiy threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 10:59:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:58 Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Mirovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130467</link><description>游리 12:58 Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Mirovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 10:58:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:58 Driven Alarm to Poltava Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130466</link><description>游릭 12:58 Driven Alarm to Poltava Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 10:58:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:58 Alarm to Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130465</link><description>游리 12:58 Alarm to Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 10:58:40 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>