<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 23:04 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134800</link><description>游댮 23:04 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 21:04:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:07 Air alarm to Zhytomyr Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134799</link><description>游댮 22:07 Air alarm to Zhytomyr Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zhytomyr_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 20:07:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:59 Threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134798</link><description>游댮 21:59 Threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 19:59:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:33 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134797</link><description>游댮 21:33 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 19:33:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:32 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District to care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134796</link><description>游댮 21:32 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District to care for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 19:32:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:30 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134795</link><description>游댮 21:30 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast follow the following messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 19:30:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:16 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134794</link><description>游댮 21:16 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 19:16:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:53 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134793</link><description>游댮 20:53 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 18:53:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:51 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134792</link><description>游댮 20:51 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 18:51:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:51 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134791</link><description>游댮 20:51 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 18:51:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:45 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134790</link><description>游댮 20:45 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 18:45:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:44 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134789</link><description>游댮 20:44 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 18:44:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:16 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134788</link><description>游댮 20:16 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 18:16:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:15 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134787</link><description>游댮 20:15 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 18:15:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 20:15 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134786</link><description>游 20:15 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 18:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:14 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134785</link><description>游댮 20:14 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 18:14:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:07 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134784</link><description>游댮 20:07 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 18:07:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:58 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134783</link><description>游댮 19:58 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 17:58:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:18 Driven the threat of Artobstil to Pokrovskaya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134782</link><description>游릭 18:18 Driven the threat of Artobstil to Pokrovskaya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 16:18:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:47 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134781</link><description>游릭 17:47 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 15:47:41 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>