<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 05:02 Drive alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134068</link><description>游릭 05:02 Drive alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 03:02:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:02 Failure to alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134067</link><description>游릭 05:02 Failure to alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 03:02:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:02 Drive the threat of shock bplas.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134066</link><description>游릭 05:02 Drive the threat of shock bplas. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 03:02:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:02 Fragrant anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134065</link><description>游리 05:02 Fragrant anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community#Kharkiv_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 03:02:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:10 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134064</link><description>游댮 04:10 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 02:10:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:01 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Follow the subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134063</link><description>游릭 03:01 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Follow the subsequent messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 01:01:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:47 Dumping anxiety in the Zhytomyr region.Crete on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134062</link><description>游릭 02:47 Dumping anxiety in the Zhytomyr region.Crete on further reports.#Zhytomyr This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 00:47:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:43 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134061</link><description>游댮 02:43 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 00:43:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:29 Drive alarm to the Khmelnytsky region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134060</link><description>游릭 02:29 Drive alarm to the Khmelnytsky region. Watch for further messages.#Khmelnitskaya This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 00:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:24 Draw an alarm to Zaporizhzhia region.Crete on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134059</link><description>游릭 02:24 Draw an alarm to Zaporizhzhia region.Crete on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 00:24:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:24 Pleasure in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134058</link><description>游릭 02:24 Pleasure in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 00:24:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 02:23 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134057</link><description>游 02:23 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_that_harkivskaya_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 00:23:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 02:23 Drawing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Mirovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134056</link><description>游리 02:23 Drawing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Mirovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 00:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:22 Air Air Anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134055</link><description>游댮 02:22 Air Air Anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 00:22:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:22 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134054</link><description>游댮 02:22 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 00:22:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:18 Air anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134053</link><description>游댮 02:18 Air anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 00:18:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:18 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134052</link><description>游댮 02:18 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 00:18:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:18 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134051</link><description>游댮 02:18 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 00:18:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:17 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134050</link><description>游릭 02:17 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 00:17:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 02:16 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134049</link><description>游리 02:16 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 00:16:56 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>