<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 13:24 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136304</link><description>游댮 13:24 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:24:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 13:21 The threat of shock UAVs The threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136303</link><description>游 13:21 The threat of shock UAVs The threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:21:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:20 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136302</link><description>游댮 13:20 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:20:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:18 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136301</link><description>游댮 13:18 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow the following messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:18:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:16 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136300</link><description>游댮 13:16 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:16:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:15 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136299</link><description>游댮 13:15 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:15:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:15 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136298</link><description>游댮 13:15 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:15:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:15 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136297</link><description>游댮 13:15 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:15:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:14 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136296</link><description>游댮 13:14 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:14:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:14 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136295</link><description>游댮 13:14 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:14:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:14 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136294</link><description>游댮 13:14 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:14:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:09 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136293</link><description>游댮 13:09 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:09:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:57 Fragrance in Zaporizhzhia region. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136292</link><description>游릭 12:57 Fragrance in Zaporizhzhia region. Stop by further messages.#Zaporizhzhia_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 09:57:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:57 Auxiliary in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136291</link><description>游릭 12:57 Auxiliary in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 09:57:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:56 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136290</link><description>游릭 12:56 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 09:56:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:56 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136289</link><description>游릭 12:56 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 09:56:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:56 Drive the threat of shock bplas.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136288</link><description>游릭 12:56 Drive the threat of shock bplas. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 09:56:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:56 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136287</link><description>游리 12:56 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 09:56:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:55 Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-mirorskaya territorial community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136286</link><description>游리 12:55 Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-mirorskaya territorial community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 09:55:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:19 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136285</link><description>游 12:19 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"#m_harkiv_that_harkivskaya_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 09:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>