<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 00:04 Air anxiety in Vinnytsia region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148412</link><description>游댮 00:04 Air anxiety in Vinnytsia region follow the following messages.#Vinnytsia_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 21:04:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:58 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148411</link><description>游댮 23:58 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 20:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:58 Air alarm in Zvenigorod district to care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148410</link><description>游댮 23:58 Air alarm in Zvenigorod district to care for further reports.#Zvenigorod_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 20:58:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:20 Air alarm to Zhytomyr Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148409</link><description>游댮 23:20 Air alarm to Zhytomyr Oblast follow the following messages.#Zhytomyr_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 20:20:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:04 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148408</link><description>游댮 23:04 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 20:04:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:49 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148407</link><description>游댮 22:49 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 19:49:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:43 Air alarm to Cherkasy District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148406</link><description>游댮 22:43 Air alarm to Cherkasy District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 19:43:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:43 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148405</link><description>游댮 22:43 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 19:43:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:33 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148404</link><description>游댮 22:33 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 19:33:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 22:25 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148403</link><description>游 22:25 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 19:25:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:24 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148402</link><description>游댮 22:24 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 19:24:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:19 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148401</link><description>游릭 22:19 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 19:19:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:17 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148400</link><description>游댮 22:17 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 19:17:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:23 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148399</link><description>游댮 21:23 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 18:23:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:03 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148398</link><description>游댮 21:03 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 18:03:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:58 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148397</link><description>游댮 20:58 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 17:58:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:50 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148396</link><description>游댮 20:50 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.#Kryvyi Rih district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 17:50:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:50 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148395</link><description>游댮 20:50 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 17:50:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:50 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148394</link><description>游댮 20:50 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 17:50:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:43 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148393</link><description>游릭 20:43 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 17:43:19 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>