<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>🟢 12:42 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146320</link><description>🟢 12:42 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 09:42:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 12:42 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146319</link><description>🟢 12:42 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 09:42:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 12:41 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146318</link><description>🟢 12:41 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 09:41:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 12:31 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146317</link><description>🟢 12:31 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 09:31:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 12:31 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146316</link><description>🟢 12:31 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 09:31:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 12:19 Drone -free attack, the area</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146315</link><description>🟠 12:19 Drone -free attack, the area This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 09:19:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 11:53 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marhanetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146314</link><description>🔴 11:53 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marhanetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 08:53:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 11:52 Return the threat of artebing to Pokrovskaya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146313</link><description>🟢 11:52 Return the threat of artebing to Pokrovskaya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 08:52:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 11:47 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146312</link><description>🟠 11:47 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 08:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 11:34 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146311</link><description>🔴 11:34 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 08:34:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 11:02 Return the threat of Artobstil in Marganets and Marhanetsky Territorial Community. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146310</link><description>🟢 11:02 Return the threat of Artobstil in Marganets and Marhanetsky Territorial Community. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 08:02:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 10:59 Close the threat of Artobstil to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146309</link><description>🟢 10:59 Close the threat of Artobstil to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 07:59:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 10:48 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146308</link><description>🔴 10:48 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 07:48:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 10:45 A. Return in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146307</link><description>🟢 10:45 A. Return in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 07:45:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 10:45 Return the threat of shock bpadbius threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146306</link><description>🟢 10:45 Return the threat of shock bpadbius threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 07:45:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 10:45 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Survene from further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146305</link><description>🔴 10:45 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Survene from further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 07:45:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 10:38 Attention! Drone attack, the area of ​​the old part</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146304</link><description>🟠 10:38 Attention! Drone attack, the area of ​​the old part #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 07:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 10:28 The threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146303</link><description>🟠 10:28 The threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"#m_harkiv_that_harkivskaya_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 07:28:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 10:28 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146302</link><description>🔴 10:28 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 07:28:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 10:24 The threat of artobrats to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146301</link><description>🟢 10:24 The threat of artobrats to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 07:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>