<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 13:22 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV indefinite type</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143290</link><description>游 13:22 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV indefinite type#m_harkiv_that_tha_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 10:22:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:22 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143289</link><description>游댮 13:22 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 10:22:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:56 Driven the alarm to the Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143288</link><description>游릭 12:56 Driven the alarm to the Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 09:56:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:53 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143287</link><description>游 12:53 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 09:53:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:35 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh in the direction of Novopavlivka</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143286</link><description>游 12:35 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh in the direction of Novopavlivka #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 09:35:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:17 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143285</link><description>游릭 12:17 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region. Since further reports.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 09:17:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:16 Driven the alarm to the Chernihiv region. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143284</link><description>游릭 12:16 Driven the alarm to the Chernihiv region. Salt for further messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 09:16:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:08 Attention! Drone attack! Discharged explosive items!  Be in shelters!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143283</link><description>游 12:08 Attention! Drone attack! Discharged explosive items!  Be in shelters! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 09:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:07 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143282</link><description>游댮 12:07 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 09:07:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:05 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143281</link><description>游릭 12:05 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 09:05:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:05 Attention! Rap off the attack of drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143280</link><description>游릭 12:05 Attention! Rap off the attack of drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 09:05:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:53 Air Alarm to Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143279</link><description>游댮 11:53 Air Alarm to Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Chernihiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 08:53:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:52 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143278</link><description>游댮 11:52 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 08:52:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:52 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143277</link><description>游댮 11:52 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 08:52:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:24 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, traffic on the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143276</link><description>游 11:24 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, traffic on the city#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 08:24:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:19 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143275</link><description>游댮 11:19 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 08:19:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:18 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143274</link><description>游댮 10:18 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 07:18:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:00 pimplifting the threat of artebing in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143273</link><description>游릭 10:00 pimplifting the threat of artebing in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 07:00:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:00 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143272</link><description>游릭 10:00 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #M_Nikopol_ta_nikopol_ Territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 07:00:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143271</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 07:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>