<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游리 07:43 Drawing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142740</link><description>游리 07:43 Drawing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community#Kharkiv_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:41 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Follow the subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142739</link><description>游릭 07:41 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Follow the subsequent messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:41:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:40 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Observe by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142738</link><description>游릭 07:40 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Observe by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:40:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:40 Driven to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142737</link><description>游릭 07:40 Driven to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:40:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:40 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creb</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142736</link><description>游릭 07:40 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creb This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:40:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:40 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142735</link><description>游릭 07:40 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region.Creck on further reports.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:40:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:40 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142734</link><description>游릭 07:40 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Watch for further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:40 Driven anxiety in Cherkasy district.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142733</link><description>游릭 07:40 Driven anxiety in Cherkasy district.Creck on further messages.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 07:39 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the old part</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142732</link><description>游 07:39 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the old part This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 07:38 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142731</link><description>游 07:38 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:38:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:37 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142730</link><description>游댮 07:37 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:37:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:27 Plowing of anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142729</link><description>游릭 07:27 Plowing of anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:27:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:27 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142728</link><description>游릭 07:27 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:27:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 07:27 Plowing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Manganese and Marganetsky territorial community- Chervonohrigor Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142727</link><description>游리 07:27 Plowing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Manganese and Marganetsky territorial community- Chervonohrigor Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:27:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:10 Failure in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142726</link><description>游릭 07:10 Failure in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:10:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:07 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142725</link><description>游댮 07:07 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:07:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:06 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142724</link><description>游댮 07:06 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:06:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:05 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142723</link><description>游댮 07:05 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:05:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:04 Air anxiety in the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142722</link><description>游댮 07:04 Air anxiety in the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:04:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:04 Air anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142721</link><description>游댮 07:04 Air anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:04:38 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>