<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 02:52 Dumping anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135591</link><description>游릭 02:52 Dumping anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 23:52:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:51 Driven the alarm to Poltava region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135590</link><description>游릭 02:51 Driven the alarm to Poltava region. Watch for further messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 23:51:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:47 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135589</link><description>游릭 02:47 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 23:47:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:47 Axiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135588</link><description>游릭 02:47 Axiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 23:47:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:02 Driven the alarm to the Chernihiv region. Follow the subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135587</link><description>游릭 02:02 Driven the alarm to the Chernihiv region. Follow the subsequent messages.#Chernihiv. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 23:02:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:02 Drive alarm to the Kiev region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135586</link><description>游릭 01:02 Drive alarm to the Kiev region. Since further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 22:02:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:01 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creck on subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135585</link><description>游릭 01:01 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creck on subsequent messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 22:01:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:01 Driven the alarm to Cherkasy district.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135584</link><description>游릭 01:01 Driven the alarm to Cherkasy district.Creck on further messages.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 22:01:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:50 pm alarm in Kyiv. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135583</link><description>游릭 00:50 pm alarm in Kyiv. Salt for further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 21:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮33</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135582</link><description>游댮33 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 20:33:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:16 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135581</link><description>游댮 23:16 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 20:16:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:05 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135580</link><description>游댮 23:05 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 20:05:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:43 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135579</link><description>游댮 22:43 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:43:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:43 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135578</link><description>游댮 22:43 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:43:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:31 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135577</link><description>游댮 22:31 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:31:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:31 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135576</link><description>游댮 22:31 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:31:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:15 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135575</link><description>游릭 22:15 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:15:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:59 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135574</link><description>游댮 21:59 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 21:58 Auxiliary in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Mirovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135573</link><description>游리 21:58 Auxiliary in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Mirovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:58:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:39 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135572</link><description>游댮 21:39 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:39:56 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>