<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 13:38 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145298</link><description>游릭 13:38 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 10:38:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:38 WARNING! DRAWING DRONIV-KAMKADze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145297</link><description>游릭 13:38 WARNING! DRAWING DRONIV-KAMKADze #M_Nikopol_ti_nikopol_ Territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 10:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:35 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145296</link><description>游릭 13:35 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 10:35:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:34 Supervise threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145295</link><description>游릭 13:34 Supervise threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 10:34:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:33 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145294</link><description>游릭 13:33 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 10:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 13:33 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145293</link><description>游리 13:33 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district#Zaporizhzhya_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 10:33:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:32 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145292</link><description>游릭 13:32 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 10:32:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 13:16 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145291</link><description>游 13:16 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 10:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 13:08 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145290</link><description>游 13:08 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 10:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 13:08 Attention! Drone attack! Perhaps discharges of explosive items!  Be in shelters!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145289</link><description>游 13:08 Attention! Drone attack! Perhaps discharges of explosive items!  Be in shelters! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 10:08:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:58 Attack drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145288</link><description>游 12:58 Attack drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 09:58:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:58 threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145287</link><description>游댮 12:58 threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 09:58:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:54 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145286</link><description>游릭 12:54 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 09:54:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:54 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145285</link><description>游리 12:54 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 09:54:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:51 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145284</link><description>游댮 12:51 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 09:51:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:42 Return the threat of artobrats in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145283</link><description>游릭 12:42 Return the threat of artobrats in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 09:42:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:42 WARNING! DRAWE DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145282</link><description>游릭 12:42 WARNING! DRAWE DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_The community This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 09:42:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:30 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzenad City</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145281</link><description>游 12:30 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzenad City #M_Nikopol_ta_nikopol_ Territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 09:30:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:30 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145280</link><description>游댮 12:30 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 09:30:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:25 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145279</link><description>游릭 12:25 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 09:25:10 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>