<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 07:12 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140449</link><description>游릭 07:12 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 04:12:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:06 Pleasure for alarm in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140448</link><description>游릭 07:06 Pleasure for alarm in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 04:06:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:06 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140447</link><description>游릭 07:06 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 04:06:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 07:06 Return the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140446</link><description>游리 07:06 Return the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 04:06:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:06 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140445</link><description>游릭 07:06 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 04:06:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:59 Dumping anxiety in the Kiev region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140444</link><description>游릭 06:59 Dumping anxiety in the Kiev region. Since further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 03:59:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:58 Driven Alarm in Kyiv. Investigate by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140443</link><description>游릭 06:58 Driven Alarm in Kyiv. Investigate by subsequent messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 03:58:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:58 Dumping anxiety in the Zhytomyr region.Creck on subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140442</link><description>游릭 06:58 Dumping anxiety in the Zhytomyr region.Creck on subsequent messages.#Zhytomyr_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 03:58:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:50 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140441</link><description>游릭 06:50 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 03:50:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:50 Attention! Droze Dronov-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140440</link><description>游릭 06:50 Attention! Droze Dronov-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 03:50:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:44 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140439</link><description>游릭 06:44 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region. Watch for further messages.#Poltava_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 03:44:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:41 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140438</link><description>游댮 06:41 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 03:41:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:39 Driven the anxiety in Zvenigorod district. Stop after further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140437</link><description>游릭 06:39 Driven the anxiety in Zvenigorod district. Stop after further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 03:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:39 Driven anxiety in the Uman District.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140436</link><description>游릭 06:39 Driven anxiety in the Uman District.Creck on Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 03:39:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:39 Drive alarms in Cherkasy district.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140435</link><description>游릭 06:39 Drive alarms in Cherkasy district.Creck on further reports.#Cherkasy_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 03:39:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:38 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140434</link><description>游릭 06:38 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creat by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 03:38:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:38 Dumping anxiety in the Vinnytsia region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140433</link><description>游릭 06:38 Dumping anxiety in the Vinnytsia region. Since further messages.#Vinnytsia_e This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 03:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:38 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140432</link><description>游릭 06:38 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 03:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:50 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140431</link><description>游댮 05:50 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.#Sinelnikov. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 02:50:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 05:50 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140430</link><description>游 05:50 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 02:50:05 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>