<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 18:18 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack continues</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144264</link><description>游 18:18 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack continues This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 15:18:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 18:13 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin Furset</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144263</link><description>游 18:13 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin Furset#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 15:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 18:13 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh in the direction of the city center</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144262</link><description>游 18:13 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh in the direction of the city center #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 15:13:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:05 The threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144261</link><description>游댮 18:05 The threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 15:05:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:54 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144260</link><description>游댮 17:54 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 14:54:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 17:46 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city center</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144259</link><description>游 17:46 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city center #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 14:46:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:46 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144258</link><description>游댮 17:46 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 14:46:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:38 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144257</link><description>游릭 17:38 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 14:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:37 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144256</link><description>游릭 17:37 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 14:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:37 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144255</link><description>游릭 17:37 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 14:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 17:36 Flashing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetsky territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144254</link><description>游리 17:36 Flashing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetsky territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 14:36:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:36 Driven the alarm to Poltava region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144253</link><description>游릭 17:36 Driven the alarm to Poltava region.Creck on further messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 14:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:36 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144252</link><description>游릭 17:36 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 14:36:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:27 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144251</link><description>游댮 17:27 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 14:27:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:27 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144250</link><description>游댮 17:27 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 14:27:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:26 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144249</link><description>游댮 17:26 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 14:26:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:25 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144248</link><description>游댮 17:25 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 14:25:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:18 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144247</link><description>游댮 17:18 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 14:18:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:58 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144246</link><description>游댮 16:58 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 13:58:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:56 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144245</link><description>游릭 16:56 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 13:56:39 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>