<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 13:31 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139578</link><description>游댮 13:31 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 10:31:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:57 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139577</link><description>游릭 11:57 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporozhye This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 08:57:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:57 Auxiliary alarm in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139576</link><description>游릭 11:57 Auxiliary alarm in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 08:57:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:57 The threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139575</link><description>游리 11:57 The threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 08:57:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:57 Reduce threatening the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139574</link><description>游릭 11:57 Reduce threatening the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 08:57:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:56 Driven the alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139573</link><description>游릭 11:56 Driven the alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 08:56:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:28 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139572</link><description>游 11:28 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 08:28:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:28 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139571</link><description>游 11:28 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 08:28:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:27 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139570</link><description>游댮 11:27 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 08:27:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:26 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139569</link><description>游릭 11:26 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 08:26:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:26 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139568</link><description>游릭 11:26 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 08:26:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:50 pm alarm to the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139567</link><description>游릭 10:50 pm alarm to the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 07:50:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:49 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139566</link><description>游릭 10:49 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Watch for further reports.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 07:49:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:30 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack continues</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139565</link><description>游 10:30 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack continues This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 07:30:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:30 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139564</link><description>游댮 10:30 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:29 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139563</link><description>游댮 10:29 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 07:29:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:23 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, traffic in the direction of the old part</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139562</link><description>游 10:23 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, traffic in the direction of the old part This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 07:23:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:22 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139561</link><description>游댮 10:22 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 07:22:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:16 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139560</link><description>游댮 10:16 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 07:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:14 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139559</link><description>游릭 10:14 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 07:14:58 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>