<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 01:39 Air anxiety in Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139485</link><description>游댮 01:39 Air anxiety in Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 22:39:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:39 Air anxiety in Cherkasy District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139484</link><description>游댮 01:39 Air anxiety in Cherkasy District Surveat for Further Messages.#Cherkasy_ Region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 22:39:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:28 Driven the alarm to the Kiev region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139483</link><description>游릭 01:28 Driven the alarm to the Kiev region. Since further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 22:28:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:44 Driven anxiety in the Zhytomyr region.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139482</link><description>游릭 00:44 Driven anxiety in the Zhytomyr region.Creck on further reports.#Zhytomyr_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 21:44:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:47 Air alarm to Zhytomyr Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139481</link><description>游댮 23:47 Air alarm to Zhytomyr Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zhytomyr_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 20:47:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:20 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139480</link><description>游댮 23:20 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 20:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:20 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139479</link><description>游댮 23:20 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 20:20:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:09 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139478</link><description>游댮 23:09 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 20:09:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:08 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139477</link><description>游댮 23:08 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 20:08:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:33 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139476</link><description>游댮 22:33 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 19:33:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:22 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139475</link><description>游댮 22:22 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 19:22:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:55 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139474</link><description>游댮 21:55 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 18:55:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 21:41 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139473</link><description>游 21:41 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_tha_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 18:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:40 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139472</link><description>游댮 21:40 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 18:40:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:23 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139471</link><description>游댮 21:23 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 18:23:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:17 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139470</link><description>游댮 21:17 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 18:17:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:11 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139469</link><description>游댮 21:11 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 18:11:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:09 Threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139468</link><description>游댮 21:09 Threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 18:09:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 20:04 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139467</link><description>游리 20:04 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 17:04:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:33 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139466</link><description>游댮 19:33 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 16:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>