<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 16:32 Driven the alarm to the Poltava region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145510</link><description>游릭 16:32 Driven the alarm to the Poltava region. Watch for further messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 13:32:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:32 Driven the anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145509</link><description>游릭 16:32 Driven the anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 13:32:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 16:32 Drawing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Sinelnikovsky rayon- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community- Chervonohrigor Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145508</link><description>游리 16:32 Drawing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Sinelnikovsky rayon- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community- Chervonohrigor Territorial Community#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 13:32:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:32 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145507</link><description>游릭 16:32 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the following messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 13:32:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:32 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145506</link><description>游릭 16:32 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 13:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:31 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145505</link><description>游릭 16:31 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 13:31:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 16:31 Drawing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145504</link><description>游리 16:31 Drawing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 13:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 15:54 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Consider, the alarm is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145503</link><description>游리 15:54 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Consider, the alarm is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region#m_nikopol_that_nikopol. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 12:54:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 15:54 Attention! Please note that anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145502</link><description>游리 15:54 Attention! Please note that anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 12:54:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:52 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145501</link><description>游댮 15:52 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 12:52:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:51 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145500</link><description>游댮 15:51 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 12:51:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:51 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145499</link><description>游댮 15:51 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 12:51:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:50 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145498</link><description>游댮 15:50 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 12:50:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:50 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145497</link><description>游댮 15:50 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 12:50:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 15:41 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on Novopavlovka</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145496</link><description>游 15:41 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on Novopavlovka #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 12:41:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:41 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145495</link><description>游댮 15:41 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 12:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:12 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145494</link><description>游댮 15:12 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast follow the following messages.#Kharkiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 12:12:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:51 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Survene from further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145493</link><description>游댮 14:51 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Survene from further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 11:51:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:50 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145492</link><description>游댮 14:50 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 11:50:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:46 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145491</link><description>游릭 14:46 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 11:46:56 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>