<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 08:34 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137546</link><description>游댮 08:34 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 05:34:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:34 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137545</link><description>游댮 08:34 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 05:34:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:23 Return the threat of artobrats in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137544</link><description>游릭 08:23 Return the threat of artobrats in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 05:23:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:58 PM Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137543</link><description>游릭 07:58 PM Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 04:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:58 Show the threat of percussion Blividbium threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137542</link><description>游릭 07:58 Show the threat of percussion Blividbium threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 04:58:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 07:58 PM Anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137541</link><description>游리 07:58 PM Anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 04:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 07:38 The threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137540</link><description>游 07:38 The threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"#m_harkiv_that_harkivskaya_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 04:38:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:38 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137539</link><description>游댮 07:38 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 04:38:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:38 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137538</link><description>游댮 07:38 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 04:38:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:00 pm alarm to the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137537</link><description>游릭 07:00 pm alarm to the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 04:00:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:52 WARNING !!! DONE ALREADY APPLICATION Aviation Bombs (Kabiv).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137536</link><description>游릭 06:52 WARNING !!! DONE ALREADY APPLICATION Aviation Bombs (Kabiv).#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 03:52:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:51 WARNING !!! DONE ALREADY APPLICATION Aviation Bombs (Kabiv).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137535</link><description>游릭 06:51 WARNING !!! DONE ALREADY APPLICATION Aviation Bombs (Kabiv). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 03:51:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:50 Attention !!! Drive the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137534</link><description>游릭 06:50 Attention !!! Drive the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 03:50:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 06:49 Flow to the Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya district-Stepnogorskaya territorial community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137533</link><description>游리 06:49 Flow to the Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya district-Stepnogorskaya territorial community#Zaporizhzhia_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 03:49:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:43 Pleasure in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137532</link><description>游릭 06:43 Pleasure in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 03:43:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:28 Air anxiety in the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137531</link><description>游댮 06:28 Air anxiety in the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 03:28:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:26 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137530</link><description>游릭 06:26 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 03:26:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 05:59 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137529</link><description>游 05:59 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 02:59:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 05:54 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137528</link><description>游 05:54 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 02:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 05:53 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137527</link><description>游 05:53 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 02:53:17 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>