<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 20:39 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137170</link><description>游댮 20:39 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 17:39:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:38 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137169</link><description>游댮 20:38 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 17:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:08 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137168</link><description>游댮 20:08 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 17:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:00 plowing the threat of arteblow to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137167</link><description>游릭 20:00 plowing the threat of arteblow to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 17:00:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 19:15 Reduce the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137166</link><description>游릭 19:15 Reduce the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 16:15:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:59 Threat of Artbill! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137165</link><description>游댮 18:59 Threat of Artbill! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 15:59:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:23 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137164</link><description>游릭 18:23 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 15:23:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 18:15 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137163</link><description>游리 18:15 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 15:15:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:02 Driven the alarm to the Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137162</link><description>游릭 18:02 Driven the alarm to the Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 15:02:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:50 pm alarm to Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137161</link><description>游릭 17:50 pm alarm to Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 14:50:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:50 pm a alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137160</link><description>游릭 17:50 pm a alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 14:50:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:56 Dumping anxiety in the Odesa region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137159</link><description>游릭 16:56 Dumping anxiety in the Odesa region. Watch for further messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 13:56:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:48 Threat of Artbill! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137158</link><description>游댮 16:48 Threat of Artbill! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 13:48:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:41 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137157</link><description>游댮 16:41 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 13:41:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:33 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137156</link><description>游댮 16:33 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 13:33:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:57 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137155</link><description>游릭 15:57 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 12:57:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:16 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137154</link><description>游댮 15:16 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 12:16:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:13 Reduce the threat of Artobstil to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137153</link><description>游릭 15:13 Reduce the threat of Artobstil to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 12:13:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:57 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137152</link><description>游릭 14:57 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 11:57:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:56 Drive the threat of shock bplas.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137151</link><description>游릭 14:56 Drive the threat of shock bplas. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 11:56:59 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>