<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 07:41 Driven an alarm to Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141853</link><description>游릭 07:41 Driven an alarm to Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 04:41:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:41 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141852</link><description>游릭 07:41 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District. Solve for further reports.#Pavlograd_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 04:41:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:40 Dumping anxiety in Novomoskovsk District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141851</link><description>游릭 07:40 Dumping anxiety in Novomoskovsk District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 04:40:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 07:39 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141850</link><description>游 07:39 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 04:39:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:39 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141849</link><description>游댮 07:39 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 04:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:39 Return the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141848</link><description>游릭 07:39 Return the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). Salt for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 04:39:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:38 Drive the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141847</link><description>游릭 07:38 Drive the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 04:38:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:38 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141846</link><description>游릭 07:38 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 04:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:38 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141845</link><description>游릭 07:38 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creat by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 04:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:38 Drive alarms in Cherkasy district. Stop after further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141844</link><description>游릭 07:38 Drive alarms in Cherkasy district. Stop after further messages.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 04:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:38 Pleasure in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141843</link><description>游릭 07:38 Pleasure in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 04:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 07:38 PM Anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141842</link><description>游리 07:38 PM Anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 04:38:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:38 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141841</link><description>游릭 07:38 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporozhye This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 04:38:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:38 Drive alarm to Poltava region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141840</link><description>游릭 07:38 Drive alarm to Poltava region. Watch for further reports.#Poltava_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 04:38:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:38 Driven Alarm to Chernihiv Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141839</link><description>游릭 07:38 Driven Alarm to Chernihiv Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 04:38:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:21 Driven anxiety in Kyiv. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141838</link><description>游릭 07:21 Driven anxiety in Kyiv. Stop by further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 04:21:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:40 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141837</link><description>游릭 06:40 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 03:40:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:40 WARNING! DRONIA DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141836</link><description>游릭 06:40 WARNING! DRONIA DRONNES-Kamikadze #M_Nikopol_ti_nikopol_ Territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 03:40:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:57 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141835</link><description>游댮 05:57 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 02:57:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 05:53 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141834</link><description>游 05:53 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 02:53:12 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>