<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 17:31 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack continues</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138326</link><description>游 17:31 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack continues This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 14:31:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 17:29 Attention! Drone-Kamikadze attack, a traffic in the direction of a paw/Ovary</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138325</link><description>游 17:29 Attention! Drone-Kamikadze attack, a traffic in the direction of a paw/Ovary #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 14:29:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:29 Threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138324</link><description>游댮 17:29 Threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 14:29:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:28 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138323</link><description>游댮 17:28 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 14:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:23 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138322</link><description>游릭 17:23 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 14:23:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:23 WARNING! DROVIA DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138321</link><description>游릭 17:23 WARNING! DROVIA DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 14:23:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:10 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138320</link><description>游댮 17:10 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 14:10:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:59 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138319</link><description>游댮 16:59 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 13:59:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 16:58 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, movement in the port of</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138318</link><description>游 16:58 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, movement in the port of #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 13:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:51 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138317</link><description>游릭 16:51 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 13:51:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:51 Logging the threat of using Cabbaths The threat of application</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138316</link><description>游릭 16:51 Logging the threat of using Cabbaths The threat of application This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 13:51:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:51 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138315</link><description>游릭 16:51 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on subsequent messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 13:51:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 16:51 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138314</link><description>游리 16:51 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 13:51:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 16:44 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138313</link><description>游 16:44 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 13:44:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 16:08 The threat of use of the copecreal application</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138312</link><description>游 16:08 The threat of use of the copecreal application This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 13:08:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:08 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138311</link><description>游댮 16:08 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 13:08:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:04 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138310</link><description>游댮 16:04 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 13:04:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 15:52 Attention, Attack-Drones of Kamikadzerukh in the direction of the lamp</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138309</link><description>游 15:52 Attention, Attack-Drones of Kamikadzerukh in the direction of the lamp This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 12:52:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 15:50 Attention, Attack-Drones of Kamikadzerukh in the direction of the old part</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138308</link><description>游 15:50 Attention, Attack-Drones of Kamikadzerukh in the direction of the old part #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 12:50:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:43 The threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138307</link><description>游댮 15:43 The threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 12:43:04 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>