<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 10:15 threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144954</link><description>游댮 10:15 threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 07:15:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144953</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 07:00:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:20 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144952</link><description>游댮 09:20 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 06:20:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:54 Air Alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144951</link><description>游댮 08:54 Air Alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 05:54:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:54 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144950</link><description>游댮 08:54 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 05:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:22 Run the threat of artebing in Marganets and Marhanetsky territorial community. Solve by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144949</link><description>游릭 08:22 Run the threat of artebing in Marganets and Marhanetsky territorial community. Solve by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 05:22:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:51 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144948</link><description>游릭 06:51 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 03:51:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:43 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144947</link><description>游릭 06:43 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 03:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:43 Driven anxiety in Sinelnikov District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144946</link><description>游릭 06:43 Driven anxiety in Sinelnikov District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 03:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:07 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144945</link><description>游댮 05:07 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.#Sinelnikov. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 02:07:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:58 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast. Since Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144944</link><description>游릭 04:58 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast. Since Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 01:58:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 3</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144943</link><description>游릭 3 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 00:53:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:32 Drive alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144942</link><description>游릭 03:32 Drive alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 00:32:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:32 Drive alarm to the Zolotonsky district.Creck on subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144941</link><description>游릭 03:32 Drive alarm to the Zolotonsky district.Creck on subsequent messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 00:32:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:32 Driven the alarm to Cherkasy district.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144940</link><description>游릭 03:32 Driven the alarm to Cherkasy district.Creck on further reports.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 00:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:31 Drive anxiety in the Poltava region. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144939</link><description>游릭 03:31 Drive anxiety in the Poltava region. Salt for further messages.#Poltava_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:19 Draw alarms in Kamyansky District.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144938</link><description>游릭 03:19 Draw alarms in Kamyansky District.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 00:19:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:19 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsk District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144937</link><description>游릭 03:19 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsk District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 00:19:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:19 Driven the anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144936</link><description>游릭 03:19 Driven the anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 00:19:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:19 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144935</link><description>游릭 03:19 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Of Zaporizhzhia_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 00:19:05 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>