<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游리 06:17 The threat of a shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139516</link><description>游리 06:17 The threat of a shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 03:17:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:15 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creck on subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139515</link><description>游릭 06:15 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creck on subsequent messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 03:15:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:15 Failure to alarm to Cherkasy district.This.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139514</link><description>游릭 06:15 Failure to alarm to Cherkasy district.This. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 03:15:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:15 Dumping anxiety in the Uman district.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139513</link><description>游릭 06:15 Dumping anxiety in the Uman district.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 03:15:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:15 Alarm to Zvenigorod district. Stop after further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139512</link><description>游릭 06:15 Alarm to Zvenigorod district. Stop after further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 03:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:08 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139511</link><description>游댮 06:08 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 03:08:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:06 Dumping anxiety in the Kiev region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139510</link><description>游릭 06:06 Dumping anxiety in the Kiev region. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 03:06:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:06 Flow to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139509</link><description>游릭 06:06 Flow to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 03:06:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:00 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139508</link><description>游댮 06:00 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 03:00:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:44 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139507</link><description>游댮 05:44 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 02:44:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:02 Drawing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Highorivska Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139506</link><description>游리 05:02 Drawing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Highorivska Territorial Community#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 02:02:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:01 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139505</link><description>游릭 05:01 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 02:01:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:01 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139504</link><description>游리 05:01 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 02:01:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:01 Driven the alarm to Poltava region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139503</link><description>游릭 05:01 Driven the alarm to Poltava region. Watch for further messages.#Poltava_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 02:01:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:47 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139502</link><description>游댮 04:47 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 01:47:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:45 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139501</link><description>游릭 04:45 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 01:45:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:38 Drive alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139500</link><description>游릭 04:38 Drive alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 01:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:12 Driven the anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139499</link><description>游릭 04:12 Driven the anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 01:12:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:12 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139498</link><description>游릭 04:12 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 01:12:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:58 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139497</link><description>游릭 03:58 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 00:58:13 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>