<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 00:27 Drive anxiety in the Poltava region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137208</link><description>游릭 00:27 Drive anxiety in the Poltava region. Watch for further messages.#Poltava_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 21:27:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:21 Air anxiety in Uman District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137207</link><description>游댮 00:21 Air anxiety in Uman District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 21:21:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:21 Air anxiety in Zvenigorod district care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137206</link><description>游댮 00:21 Air anxiety in Zvenigorod district care for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 21:21:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:17 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137205</link><description>游댮 00:17 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 21:17:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 00:04 Dumping anxiety in the Cherkasy region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Cherkasy district- Zolotonsky district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137204</link><description>游리 00:04 Dumping anxiety in the Cherkasy region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Cherkasy district- Zolotonsky district#Cherkasy_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 21:04:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:04 Air anxiety in Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137203</link><description>游댮 00:04 Air anxiety in Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 21:04:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:04 Air alarm to Cherkasy district care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137202</link><description>游댮 00:04 Air alarm to Cherkasy district care for further messages.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 21:04:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:03 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137201</link><description>游릭 00:03 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 21:03:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:01 Driven the alarm in Kyiv. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137200</link><description>游릭 00:01 Driven the alarm in Kyiv. Stop by further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 21:01:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:01 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137199</link><description>游릭 00:01 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 21:01:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:01 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137198</link><description>游릭 00:01 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 21:01:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:01 Drive anxiety in the Sumy region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137197</link><description>游릭 00:01 Drive anxiety in the Sumy region.Creat by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 21:01:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:01 Drive anxiety in the Poltava region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137196</link><description>游릭 00:01 Drive anxiety in the Poltava region.Creck on further messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 21:01:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 00:01 Flashing anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137195</link><description>游리 00:01 Flashing anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community#Kharkiv_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 21:01:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:01 Driven the anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137194</link><description>游릭 00:01 Driven the anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 21:01:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:01 Driven anxiety in the Kiev region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137193</link><description>游릭 00:01 Driven anxiety in the Kiev region. Since further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 21:01:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:00 pm alarm to the Chernihiv region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137192</link><description>游릭 00:00 pm alarm to the Chernihiv region. Watch for further reports.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 21:00:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00.00</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137191</link><description>游릭 00.00 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 21:00:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:37 Air alarm to Vinnytsia region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137190</link><description>游댮 23:37 Air alarm to Vinnytsia region follow the following messages.#Vinnytsia_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 20:37:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:35 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137189</link><description>游댮 23:35 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 20:35:22 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>