<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭33</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151213</link><description>游릭33 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 20:33:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 23:32 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151212</link><description>游리 23:32 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district#Zaporizhzhia_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 20:32:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:21 Air Alarm to Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151211</link><description>游댮 23:21 Air Alarm to Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.#Pavlograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 20:21:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:21 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151210</link><description>游댮 23:21 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 20:21:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 22:59 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151209</link><description>游 22:59 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 19:59:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:56 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151208</link><description>游릭 22:56 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 19:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:54 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151207</link><description>游댮 22:54 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 19:54:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:54 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151206</link><description>游댮 22:54 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 19:54:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:48 The threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151205</link><description>游댮 22:48 The threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 19:48:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 22:44 The threat of shock UAVs The threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151204</link><description>游 22:44 The threat of shock UAVs The threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 19:44:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:44 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151203</link><description>游댮 22:44 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 19:44:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:35 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151202</link><description>游댮 22:35 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 19:35:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:49 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151201</link><description>游댮 21:49 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 18:49:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:23 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151200</link><description>游댮 21:23 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 18:23:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:19 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151199</link><description>游댮 21:19 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 18:19:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:54 Return of the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151198</link><description>游릭 20:54 Return of the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 17:54:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 20:37 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151197</link><description>游 20:37 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 17:37:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:37 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151196</link><description>游댮 20:37 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 17:37:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:35 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151195</link><description>游댮 20:35 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast follow the following messages.#Kharkiv_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 17:35:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:42 Threat of Artbill! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151194</link><description>游댮 19:42 Threat of Artbill! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 16:42:50 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>