<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 07:31 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145076</link><description>游릭 07:31 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 04:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:28 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145075</link><description>游릭 07:28 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 04:28:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:27 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145074</link><description>游릭 07:27 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 04:27:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:10 Failure of the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145073</link><description>游릭 07:10 Failure of the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 04:10:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:10 Attention! Droze Dronov-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145072</link><description>游릭 07:10 Attention! Droze Dronov-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 04:10:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:57 Dumping anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145071</link><description>游릭 06:57 Dumping anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 03:57:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:56 Auxiliary alarm in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145070</link><description>游릭 06:56 Auxiliary alarm in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 03:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:56 Frame anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145069</link><description>游릭 06:56 Frame anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region. Since further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 03:56:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 06:56 Failure of the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145068</link><description>游리 06:56 Failure of the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 03:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:42 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145067</link><description>游댮 06:42 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 03:42:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:22 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145066</link><description>游댮 06:22 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 03:22:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 05:54 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145065</link><description>游 05:54 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 02:54:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:50 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145064</link><description>游댮 05:50 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 02:50:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:48 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145063</link><description>游댮 05:48 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 02:48:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:14 Air anxiety in Sinelnikov District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145062</link><description>游댮 05:14 Air anxiety in Sinelnikov District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 02:14:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:40 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145061</link><description>游릭 04:40 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 01:40:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:40 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145060</link><description>游릭 04:40 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District.Creck on further reports.#Pavlograd_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 01:40:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:21 Driven anxiety in the Dnieper district.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145059</link><description>游릭 04:21 Driven anxiety in the Dnieper district.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 01:21:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:21 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsk District. Stop after further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145058</link><description>游릭 04:21 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsk District. Stop after further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 01:21:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:20 Auxiliary in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145057</link><description>游릭 04:20 Auxiliary in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 01:20:09 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>