<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 18:35 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141138</link><description>游댮 18:35 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 15:35:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 18:24 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141137</link><description>游리 18:24 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 15:24:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:16 Reduce the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141136</link><description>游릭 18:16 Reduce the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 15:16:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:16 WARNING! DRAWE DRONNIA-KAMKADze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141135</link><description>游릭 18:16 WARNING! DRAWE DRONNIA-KAMKADze #M_Nikopol_ti_nikopol_ Territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 15:16:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:04 Drive the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141134</link><description>游릭 18:04 Drive the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 15:04:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:03 Driven anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141133</link><description>游릭 18:03 Driven anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 15:03:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 18:03 Flowing anxiety in the Zaporizhzhia region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141132</link><description>游리 18:03 Flowing anxiety in the Zaporizhzhia region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district#Zaporizhzhia_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 15:03:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:03 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141131</link><description>游릭 18:03 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 15:03:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:01 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141130</link><description>游릭 18:01 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 15:01:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:48 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast. Since Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141129</link><description>游릭 17:48 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast. Since Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 14:48:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:48 Driven Alarm to the Chernihiv Oblast. Follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141128</link><description>游릭 17:48 Driven Alarm to the Chernihiv Oblast. Follow the following messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 14:48:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 17:45 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141127</link><description>游 17:45 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 14:45:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:45 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141126</link><description>游댮 17:45 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 14:45:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 17:42 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141125</link><description>游 17:42 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 14:42:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:34 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141124</link><description>游댮 17:34 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 14:34:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:33 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141123</link><description>游릭 17:33 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 14:33:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:16 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141122</link><description>游댮 17:16 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 14:16:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:14 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141121</link><description>游댮 17:14 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 14:14:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:14 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141120</link><description>游댮 17:14 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 14:14:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:14 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141119</link><description>游댮 17:14 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 14:14:10 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>