<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 21:27 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135186</link><description>游댮 21:27 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 18:27:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:24 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135185</link><description>游댮 21:24 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 18:24:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:11 Air alarm to the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135184</link><description>游댮 21:11 Air alarm to the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 18:11:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:10 Air Air In Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135183</link><description>游댮 21:10 Air Air In Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 18:10:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:10 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135182</link><description>游댮 21:10 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 18:10:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:07 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135181</link><description>游댮 21:07 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 18:07:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:07 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135180</link><description>游댮 21:07 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 18:07:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:07 Air alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135179</link><description>游댮 21:07 Air alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Cherkasy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 18:07:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:05 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135178</link><description>游댮 21:05 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 18:05:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:05 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135177</link><description>游댮 21:05 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 18:05:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:56 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135176</link><description>游댮 20:56 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 17:56:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:56 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135175</link><description>游댮 20:56 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 17:56:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:56 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135174</link><description>游댮 20:56 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 17:56:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:40 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135173</link><description>游릭 20:40 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 17:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:44 The threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135172</link><description>游댮 19:44 The threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 16:44:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:43 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marhanetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135171</link><description>游댮 19:43 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marhanetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 16:43:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:33 Attention !!! Drive the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135170</link><description>游릭 18:33 Attention !!! Drive the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 15:33:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:32 WARNING !!! DONE ASKRIGHT OF USEED AVIRTER BOMB (Kabiv).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135169</link><description>游릭 18:32 WARNING !!! DONE ASKRIGHT OF USEED AVIRTER BOMB (Kabiv). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 15:32:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:31 Driven the anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135168</link><description>游릭 18:31 Driven the anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 15:31:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 18:31 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135167</link><description>游리 18:31 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya district#Zaporizhzhia_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 15:31:25 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>