<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 16:52 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/128880</link><description>游댮 16:52 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 14:52:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:31 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/128879</link><description>游댮 16:31 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 14:31:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:47 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Manganese territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/128878</link><description>游댮 15:47 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Manganese territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 13:47:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:50 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/128877</link><description>游댮 14:50 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast follow the following messages.#Kharkiv_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 12:50:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:18 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/128876</link><description>游릭 14:18 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 12:18:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:00 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. The 24 -hour free hotline on issues will be urgently evacuated from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 08003392911 Vacacing of civilian population - 08003339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/128875</link><description>游 14:00 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. The 24 -hour free hotline on issues will be urgently evacuated from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 08003392911 Vacacing of civilian population - 08003339291 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 12:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:51 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/128874</link><description>游댮 13:51 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 11:51:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:44 Driven the alarm to the Poltava region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/128873</link><description>游릭 13:44 Driven the alarm to the Poltava region. Since further reports.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 11:44:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:44 Draw an alarm to the Zaporizhzhia region. Make sure</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/128872</link><description>游릭 13:44 Draw an alarm to the Zaporizhzhia region. Make sure This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 11:44:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 1:44</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/128871</link><description>游댮 1:44 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 11:44:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:44 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/128870</link><description>游댮 13:44 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 11:44:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:39 Threat of Arteball! Now in the Mirovsky territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/128869</link><description>游댮 13:39 Threat of Arteball! Now in the Mirovsky territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 11:39:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:05 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/128868</link><description>游댮 13:05 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 11:05:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:56 Driven the alarm to the Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/128867</link><description>游릭 12:56 Driven the alarm to the Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 10:56:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:23 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/128866</link><description>游릭 12:23 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 10:23:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:02 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetsky territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/128865</link><description>游리 12:02 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetsky territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 10:02:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:02 Driven Alarm to the Chernihiv Oblast. Follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/128864</link><description>游릭 12:02 Driven Alarm to the Chernihiv Oblast. Follow the following messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 10:02:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:01 Return the threat of Artobrytil to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/128863</link><description>游릭 12:01 Return the threat of Artobrytil to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 10:01:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:01 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Make sure</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/128862</link><description>游릭 12:01 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Make sure This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 10:01:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:01 Attention !!! Notice, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/128861</link><description>游리 12:01 Attention !!! Notice, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya region#Pologovsky_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 10:01:05 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>