<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 10:12 Reduce the threat of Artobstil in Chervonohrigorivska Territorial Community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143056</link><description>游릭 10:12 Reduce the threat of Artobstil in Chervonohrigorivska Territorial Community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 07:12:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143055</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 07:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:54 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143054</link><description>游릭 09:54 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 06:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:48 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143053</link><description>游댮 09:48 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 06:48:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:23 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143052</link><description>游릭 09:23 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 06:23:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:11 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143051</link><description>游댮 09:11 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 06:11:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:59 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143050</link><description>游댮 08:59 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 05:59:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:58 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143049</link><description>游댮 08:58 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 05:58:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:55 Dumping anxiety in the Kiev region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143048</link><description>游릭 08:55 Dumping anxiety in the Kiev region. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 05:55:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:54 Dumping anxiety in Kyiv. Investigate by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143047</link><description>游릭 08:54 Dumping anxiety in Kyiv. Investigate by subsequent messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 05:54:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:04 Dumping anxiety in the Zhytomyr region.Creat on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143046</link><description>游릭 08:04 Dumping anxiety in the Zhytomyr region.Creat on further messages.#Zhytomyr This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 05:04:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:58 Air anxiety in the Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143045</link><description>游댮 07:58 Air anxiety in the Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Chernihiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 04:58:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:54 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143044</link><description>游릭 07:54 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 04:54:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:18 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143043</link><description>游릭 07:18 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creat by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 04:18:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:18 Drive alarm to Cherkasy district.This followed by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143042</link><description>游릭 07:18 Drive alarm to Cherkasy district.This followed by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 04:18:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:08 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143041</link><description>游릭 07:08 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 04:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:08 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast. Since Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143040</link><description>游릭 07:08 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast. Since Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 04:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:44 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143039</link><description>游릭 06:44 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region. Watch for further messages.#Poltava_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 03:44:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:40 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143038</link><description>游릭 05:40 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 02:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:38 Driven your alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143037</link><description>游릭 05:38 Driven your alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Stop by further messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 02:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>