<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 10:09 Threat of Artebroch! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142789</link><description>游댮 10:09 Threat of Artebroch! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:09:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:05 Plowing of the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142788</link><description>游릭 10:05 Plowing of the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:05:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:05 Attention! Rap off the attack of drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142787</link><description>游릭 10:05 Attention! Rap off the attack of drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:05:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142786</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#KUDYANSKY This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:50 Attack drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142785</link><description>游 09:50 Attack drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:50:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:49 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack continues</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142784</link><description>游 09:49 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack continues This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:49:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:44 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142783</link><description>游댮 09:44 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:44:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:13 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142782</link><description>游댮 09:13 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:13:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:11 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142781</link><description>游댮 09:11 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:11:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:02 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142780</link><description>游 09:02 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:02:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:02 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142779</link><description>游댮 09:02 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:02:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:55 Dumping anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142778</link><description>游릭 08:55 Dumping anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:55:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:53 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142777</link><description>游릭 08:53 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:53:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:52 Driven the anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142776</link><description>游릭 08:52 Driven the anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:52:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:52 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142775</link><description>游릭 08:52 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:52:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:52 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142774</link><description>游릭 08:52 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:52:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:52 Drive alarm to Cherkasy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142773</link><description>游릭 08:52 Drive alarm to Cherkasy region.Creck on further messages.#Cherkasy_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:52:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:52 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142772</link><description>游릭 08:52 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:52:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:52 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142771</link><description>游릭 08:52 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:52:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:52 Driven to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142770</link><description>游릭 08:52 Driven to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:52:08 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>