<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 07:52 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129822</link><description>游릭 07:52 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 05:52:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:40 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129821</link><description>游댮 07:40 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 05:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:55 WARNING !!! DONE ALREADY OF USEED AVIRTED AVIRIAL Bombs (Kabiv).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129820</link><description>游릭 05:55 WARNING !!! DONE ALREADY OF USEED AVIRTED AVIRIAL Bombs (Kabiv). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 03:55:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:54 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129819</link><description>游릭 05:54 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 03:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:54 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129818</link><description>游리 05:54 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district#Zaporizhzhia_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 03:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:48 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129817</link><description>游릭 05:48 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 03:48:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 05:28 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129816</link><description>游 05:28 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 03:28:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:26 Failure in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129815</link><description>游릭 05:26 Failure in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 03:26:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:26 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129814</link><description>游릭 05:26 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creat by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 03:26:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:26 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129813</link><description>游리 05:26 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 03:26:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:24 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129812</link><description>游댮 05:24 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 03:24:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:08 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129811</link><description>游댮 04:08 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 02:08:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:07 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129810</link><description>游댮 04:07 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 02:07:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:50 Auxiliary in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129809</link><description>游릭 03:50 Auxiliary in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 01:50:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 03:50 pm alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129808</link><description>游리 03:50 pm alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 01:50:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:06 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129807</link><description>游릭 02:06 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creat by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 00:06:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:05 Drive alarm to Cherkasy district.This followed by further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129806</link><description>游릭 02:05 Drive alarm to Cherkasy district.This followed by further reports.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 00:05:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:00 plowing anxiety in the Kiev region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129805</link><description>游릭 02:00 plowing anxiety in the Kiev region. Since further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 00:00:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:51 Driven anxiety in the Poltava region. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129804</link><description>游릭 01:51 Driven anxiety in the Poltava region. Salt for further messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 23:51:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:50 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129803</link><description>游댮 01:50 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 23:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>