<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 21:16 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149531</link><description>游댮 21:16 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 18:16:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:15 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149530</link><description>游댮 21:15 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 18:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 21:01 The threat of artobrats to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Cont attention, anxiety is still in:- Nikopol district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149529</link><description>游리 21:01 The threat of artobrats to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Cont attention, anxiety is still in:- Nikopol district#Pokrovskaya_T territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 18:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:00 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149528</link><description>游댮 21:00 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 18:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:40 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149527</link><description>游댮 20:40 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 17:40:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:40 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149526</link><description>游댮 20:40 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 17:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:40 Air alarm to Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149525</link><description>游댮 20:40 Air alarm to Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.#Pavlograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 17:40:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:39 Air anxiety in Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149524</link><description>游댮 20:39 Air anxiety in Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.#Kryvyi Rih Ri This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 17:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:38 Air alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149523</link><description>游댮 20:38 Air alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.#Nikopol. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 17:38:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:36 Air alarm to Dniprovskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149522</link><description>游댮 20:36 Air alarm to Dniprovskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 17:36:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:24 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149521</link><description>游댮 20:24 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 17:24:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:11 Return the threat of artobrats in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solid by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149520</link><description>游릭 20:11 Return the threat of artobrats in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solid by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 17:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:11 Attention! Droze Dronov-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149519</link><description>游릭 20:11 Attention! Droze Dronov-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 17:11:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:05 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149518</link><description>游댮 20:05 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 17:05:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:04 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149517</link><description>游댮 20:04 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 17:04:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:02 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149516</link><description>游댮 20:02 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 17:02:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:02 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149515</link><description>游댮 20:02 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 17:02:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:55 Air Air In Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149514</link><description>游댮 19:55 Air Air In Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 16:55:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 19:47 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149513</link><description>游릭 19:47 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 16:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 19:43 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149512</link><description>游릭 19:43 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 16:43:48 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>