<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 13:24 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138677</link><description>游릭 13:24 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on subsequent messages.#Chernihiv_e This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:24:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:22 Driven the alarm to the Sumy region.Creat for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138676</link><description>游릭 13:22 Driven the alarm to the Sumy region.Creat for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:22:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 13:22 Drawing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138675</link><description>游리 13:22 Drawing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:22:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:22 Driven the alarm to the Poltava region.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138674</link><description>游릭 13:22 Driven the alarm to the Poltava region.Creck on further reports.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:22:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 13:21 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138673</link><description>游 13:21 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:21:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:21 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138672</link><description>游릭 13:21 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:21:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 13:14 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, movement in the horizon</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138671</link><description>游 13:14 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, movement in the horizon#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 13:10 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138670</link><description>游 13:10 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:10:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 13:00 WARNING! Drone-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138669</link><description>游 13:00 WARNING! Drone-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:00:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:36 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138668</link><description>游댮 12:36 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 09:36:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:31 The threat of a shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138667</link><description>游리 12:31 The threat of a shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 09:31:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:31 Attention! Please note that anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138666</link><description>游리 12:31 Attention! Please note that anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 09:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:31 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138665</link><description>游 12:31 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_that_harkivskaya_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 09:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:31 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138664</link><description>游댮 12:31 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 09:31:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:11 PM! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138663</link><description>游 12:11 PM! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 09:11:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:11 Threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138662</link><description>游댮 12:11 Threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 09:11:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:04 The threat of artebing in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138661</link><description>游리 12:04 The threat of artebing in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 09:04:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:04 Attention! Please note that the alarm is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138660</link><description>游리 12:04 Attention! Please note that the alarm is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 09:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:01 Dumping anxiety in the Kiev region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138659</link><description>游릭 12:01 Dumping anxiety in the Kiev region. Since further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 09:01:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:46 plout anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138658</link><description>游릭 11:46 plout anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 08:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>