<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 11:37 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137428</link><description>游릭 11:37 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:37:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:35 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137427</link><description>游리 11:35 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:35:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:30 Plowing the threat of artebing in Marganets and Marhanetsky Territorial Community. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137426</link><description>游릭 11:30 Plowing the threat of artebing in Marganets and Marhanetsky Territorial Community. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:30:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:27 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137425</link><description>游댮 11:27 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:27:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:17 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137424</link><description>游릭 11:17 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:17:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:15 Pleasure anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137423</link><description>游릭 11:15 Pleasure anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:15:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:15 Pleasure in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137422</link><description>游릭 11:15 Pleasure in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:15:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:12 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137421</link><description>游릭 11:12 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:12:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:07 Auxiliary alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137420</link><description>游릭 11:07 Auxiliary alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:07:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:07 The threat of percussion bplavidbium threat of percussion UAV</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137419</link><description>游릭 11:07 The threat of percussion bplavidbium threat of percussion UAV#M_Kharkiv_tha_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:07:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:54 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137418</link><description>游댮 10:54 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 07:54:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:43 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137417</link><description>游댮 10:43 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 07:43:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:37 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137416</link><description>游릭 10:37 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 07:37:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:36 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137415</link><description>游댮 10:36 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 07:36:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:32 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137414</link><description>游댮 10:32 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 07:32:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:22 Reduce the threat of Artobstil to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137413</link><description>游릭 10:22 Reduce the threat of Artobstil to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 07:22:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:21 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137412</link><description>游댮 10:21 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 07:21:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:06 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137411</link><description>游릭 10:06 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 07:06:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:00</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137410</link><description>游릭 10:00 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 07:06:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:02 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137409</link><description>游 10:02 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#KUDYANSKY This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 07:02:16 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>