<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>🟢 17:13 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141289</link><description>🟢 17:13 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 14:13:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 17:13 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141288</link><description>🟢 17:13 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 14:13:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 17:11 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141287</link><description>🟠 17:11 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 14:11:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 17:11 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141286</link><description>🔴 17:11 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 14:11:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 16:54 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marhanetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141285</link><description>🔴 16:54 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marhanetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 13:54:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 16:27 Close the threat of artobrats in the Chervonohrigor territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141284</link><description>🟢 16:27 Close the threat of artobrats in the Chervonohrigor territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 13:27:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 16:18 Return the threat of artebors in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141283</link><description>🟢 16:18 Return the threat of artebors in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 13:18:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 16:07 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141282</link><description>🟢 16:07 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 13:07:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 15:53 ​​Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141281</link><description>🟢 15:53 ​​Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 12:53:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟡 15:52 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141280</link><description>🟡 15:52 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 12:52:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 15:37 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141279</link><description>🔴 15:37 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 12:37:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 15:36 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141278</link><description>🟢 15:36 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 12:36:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 15:35 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141277</link><description>🔴 15:35 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 12:35:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 15:35 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141276</link><description>🔴 15:35 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 12:35:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 15:35 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141275</link><description>🔴 15:35 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 12:35:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 15:31 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141274</link><description>🔴 15:31 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 12:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 15:26 Reduce the threat of artebors in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141273</link><description>🟢 15:26 Reduce the threat of artebors in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 12:26:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 15:12 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141272</link><description>🔴 15:12 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 12:12:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 15:00 alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141271</link><description>🟢 15:00 alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 12:00:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟡 15:00 A.Corets in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district-Lipetsk territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141270</link><description>🟡 15:00 A.Corets in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district-Lipetsk territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community#Kharkiv_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 12:00:16 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>