<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 10:08 Driven anxiety to the Odesa region. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153746</link><description>游릭 10:08 Driven anxiety to the Odesa region. Stop by further messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 07:08:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:08 Plowing of the threat of Artobstil to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153745</link><description>游릭 10:08 Plowing of the threat of Artobstil to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 07:08:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:06 Attack Dronov- Kamikadzestar Part Attention!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153744</link><description>游 10:06 Attack Dronov- Kamikadzestar Part Attention! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 07:06:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:05 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153743</link><description>游댮 10:05 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 07:05:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:02 Drive alarm to Poltava region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153742</link><description>游릭 10:02 Drive alarm to Poltava region. Watch for further reports.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 07:02:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:00 pimplifting the threat of artebing in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153741</link><description>游릭 10:00 pimplifting the threat of artebing in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 07:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:00 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153740</link><description>游릭 10:00 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 07:00:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153739</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 07:00:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:49 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153738</link><description>游릭 09:49 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 06:49:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:40 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creck on subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153737</link><description>游릭 09:40 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creck on subsequent messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 06:40:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:28 Driven the alarm to Cherkasy district. Stop after further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153736</link><description>游릭 09:28 Driven the alarm to Cherkasy district. Stop after further messages.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 06:28:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:28 Driven the anxiety in Zvenigorod district. Stop after further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153735</link><description>游릭 09:28 Driven the anxiety in Zvenigorod district. Stop after further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 06:28:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:22 Attack Dronov-Kamikadze! The area</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153734</link><description>游 09:22 Attack Dronov-Kamikadze! The area This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 06:22:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:19 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153733</link><description>游댮 09:19 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 06:19:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:19 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153732</link><description>游댮 09:19 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 06:19:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:17 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153731</link><description>游댮 09:17 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 06:17:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:17 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153730</link><description>游댮 09:17 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 06:17:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:16 Air Alarm to Zhytomyr Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153729</link><description>游댮 09:16 Air Alarm to Zhytomyr Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zhytomyr_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 06:16:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:13 Air alarm in Zvenigorod District to care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153728</link><description>游댮 09:13 Air alarm in Zvenigorod District to care for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 06:13:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:01 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153727</link><description>游릭 09:01 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 06:01:59 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>