<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 07:39 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154143</link><description>游릭 07:39 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 04:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:30 Failure of the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154142</link><description>游릭 07:30 Failure of the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 04:30:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:17 Clear the threat of artebing to Pokrovskaya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154141</link><description>游릭 07:17 Clear the threat of artebing to Pokrovskaya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 04:17:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:12 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154140</link><description>游댮 07:12 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 04:12:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:12 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154139</link><description>游댮 07:12 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 04:12:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:58 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154138</link><description>游릭 06:58 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 03:58:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:58 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154137</link><description>游릭 06:58 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 03:58:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 06:31 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154136</link><description>游 06:31 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 03:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:19 Close the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154135</link><description>游릭 06:19 Close the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 03:19:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:53 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154134</link><description>游댮 05:53 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 02:53:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:47 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154133</link><description>游댮 05:47 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 02:47:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:28 Close the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154132</link><description>游릭 05:28 Close the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 02:28:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:48 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154131</link><description>游댮 04:48 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 01:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:56 Air alarm to Sinelnikov District Solve for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154130</link><description>游댮 03:56 Air alarm to Sinelnikov District Solve for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 00:56:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:05 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154129</link><description>游댮 03:05 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 00:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:04 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154128</link><description>游댮 03:04 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 00:04:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 01:59 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154127</link><description>游리 01:59 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 22:59:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:00 plowing anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154126</link><description>游릭 01:00 plowing anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 22:00:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 1 0</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154125</link><description>游릭 1 0 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 22:00:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:47 Drive alarm to Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154124</link><description>游릭 00:47 Drive alarm to Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 21:47:01 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>