<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 12:45 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149665</link><description>游릭 12:45 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporozhye This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:45:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:45 pm a alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149664</link><description>游릭 12:45 pm a alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:45:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:43 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149663</link><description>游 12:43 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:43:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:42 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149662</link><description>游댮 12:42 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:42:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:29 Threat of Artebating! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149661</link><description>游댮 12:29 Threat of Artebating! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:29:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:29 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149660</link><description>游댮 12:29 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:29:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:29 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149659</link><description>游댮 12:29 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:29:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:26 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149658</link><description>游댮 12:26 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:26:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:26 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149657</link><description>游 12:26 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:26:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:25 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149656</link><description>游댮 12:25 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:25:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:18 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149655</link><description>游릭 12:18 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:18:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:17 Dumping anxiety in the Sinelnikov District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149654</link><description>游릭 12:17 Dumping anxiety in the Sinelnikov District. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:17:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:00</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149653</link><description>游릭 12:00 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:06:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:06 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149652</link><description>游릭 12:06 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:06:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:03 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149651</link><description>游릭 12:03 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:03:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:03 Attention! Droze Dronov-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149650</link><description>游릭 12:03 Attention! Droze Dronov-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:03:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:02 Flashing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Sinelnikovsky rayon- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivka Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149649</link><description>游리 12:02 Flashing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Sinelnikovsky rayon- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivka Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:02:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:02 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149648</link><description>游릭 12:02 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:02:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:02 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetsky territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149647</link><description>游리 12:02 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetsky territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:02:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:02 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast. Since Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149646</link><description>游릭 12:02 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast. Since Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:02:09 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>