<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 01:44 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Stop after further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147036</link><description>游릭 01:44 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Stop after further messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 22:44:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:35 Air anxiety in Zvenigorod district to care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147035</link><description>游댮 01:35 Air anxiety in Zvenigorod district to care for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 22:35:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:35 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147034</link><description>游댮 01:35 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 22:35:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:33 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147033</link><description>游릭 01:33 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Stop by further messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 22:33:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:27 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147032</link><description>游릭 01:27 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 22:27:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:27 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147031</link><description>游릭 01:27 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 22:27:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:10 Air alarm to the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147030</link><description>游댮 01:10 Air alarm to the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 22:10:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:51 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147029</link><description>游댮 00:51 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District care for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 21:51:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:50 Air alarm to Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147028</link><description>游댮 00:50 Air alarm to Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.#Pavlograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 21:50:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:32 Driven the alarm to Kryvyi Rih District. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147027</link><description>游릭 00:32 Driven the alarm to Kryvyi Rih District. Solve for further messages.#Kryvyi Rih. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 21:32:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:17 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147026</link><description>游릭 00:17 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 21:17:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:17 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147025</link><description>游릭 00:17 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 21:17:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 00:</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147024</link><description>游리 00: This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 21:17:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:15 Air anxiety in the Vinnytsia region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147023</link><description>游댮 00:15 Air anxiety in the Vinnytsia region follow the following messages.#Vinnytsia_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 21:15:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 23:20 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147022</link><description>游 23:20 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 20:20:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:16 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147021</link><description>游댮 23:16 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 20:16:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:16 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147020</link><description>游댮 23:16 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 20:16:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 23:09 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV indefinite type</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147019</link><description>游 23:09 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV indefinite type#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 20:09:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:08 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147018</link><description>游댮 23:08 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 20:08:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:51 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147017</link><description>游댮 22:51 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 19:51:23 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>