<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 17:41 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140905</link><description>游댮 17:41 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 14:41:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:41 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140904</link><description>游댮 17:41 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 14:41:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:41 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140903</link><description>游댮 17:41 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 14:41:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:41 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140902</link><description>游댮 17:41 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 14:41:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:41 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140901</link><description>游댮 17:41 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 14:41:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:41 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140900</link><description>游댮 17:41 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 14:41:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:40 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140899</link><description>游댮 17:40 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 14:40:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:20 Return the threat of Artobrytile to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140898</link><description>游릭 17:20 Return the threat of Artobrytile to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 14:20:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:56 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140897</link><description>游릭 16:56 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 13:56:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:56 Logging the threat of using Cabbaths The threat of application</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140896</link><description>游릭 16:56 Logging the threat of using Cabbaths The threat of application This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 13:56:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:55 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140895</link><description>游릭 16:55 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 13:55:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 16:55 Auxiliary in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140894</link><description>游리 16:55 Auxiliary in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 13:55:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:51 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140893</link><description>游릭 16:51 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 13:51:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:51 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140892</link><description>游릭 16:51 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #M_Nikopol_ti_nikopol_ Territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 13:51:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 16:10 The threat of use of the copecreal application</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140891</link><description>游 16:10 The threat of use of the copecreal application This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 13:10:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:10 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140890</link><description>游댮 16:10 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 13:10:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 16:09 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140889</link><description>游 16:09 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 13:09:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:09 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140888</link><description>游댮 16:09 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 13:09:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:30 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140887</link><description>游릭 15:30 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 12:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:21 Driven the alarm to the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140886</link><description>游릭 15:21 Driven the alarm to the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 12:21:08 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>