<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>🔴 11:21 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150196</link><description>🔴 11:21 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 08:21:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 11:20 Air alarm in Kyiv Investigate by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150195</link><description>🔴 11:20 Air alarm in Kyiv Investigate by further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 08:20:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 11:12 Attack Dronov-Kamikadze type laS-2</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150194</link><description>🟠 11:12 Attack Dronov-Kamikadze type laS-2#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 08:12:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 11:12 Attack Dronov-Kamikadze type lardable to 3 polling station</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150193</link><description>🟠 11:12 Attack Dronov-Kamikadze type lardable to 3 polling station #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 08:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 11:10 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery firing.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150192</link><description>🔴 11:10 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery firing. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 08:10:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 11:07 Attack Dronov-Kamikadze Type of port.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150191</link><description>🟠 11:07 Attack Dronov-Kamikadze Type of port. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 08:07:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 11:04 Attack Dronov-Kamikadze type laS</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150190</link><description>🟠 11:04 Attack Dronov-Kamikadze type laS This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 08:04:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 10:57 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150189</link><description>🔴 10:57 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 07:57:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 10:56 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150188</link><description>🔴 10:56 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 07:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 10:56 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150187</link><description>🔴 10:56 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 07:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 10:56 Air alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150186</link><description>🔴 10:56 Air alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Cherkasy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 07:56:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 10:56 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150185</link><description>🔴 10:56 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 07:56:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 10:56 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150184</link><description>🔴 10:56 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 07:56:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 10:48 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the old part</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150183</link><description>🟠 10:48 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the old part This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 07:48:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 10:43 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150182</link><description>🔴 10:43 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 07:43:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 10:42 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh from Novopavlivka Unapryamka OKKO</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150181</link><description>🟠 10:42 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh from Novopavlivka Unapryamka OKKO#M_NIKOPOL_TA_NIKOPOLSKA This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 07:42:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 10:39 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150180</link><description>🔴 10:39 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 07:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 10:39 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150179</link><description>🔴 10:39 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 07:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 10:37 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150178</link><description>🔴 10:37 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 07:37:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 10:36 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150177</link><description>🟠 10:36 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 07:36:41 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>