<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 08:43 attack drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145083</link><description>游 08:43 attack drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 05:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 08:39 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145082</link><description>游 08:39 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 05:39:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:36 Threat of Artbill! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145081</link><description>游댮 08:36 Threat of Artbill! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 05:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 08:31 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin of the old part</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145080</link><description>游 08:31 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin of the old part #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 05:31:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 08:27 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzenad City</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145079</link><description>游 08:27 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzenad City #M_Nikopol_that_nikopol_ Territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 05:27:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:27 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145078</link><description>游댮 08:27 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 05:27:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:27 Return the threat of artobrats in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145077</link><description>游릭 08:27 Return the threat of artobrats in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 05:27:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:31 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145076</link><description>游릭 07:31 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 04:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:28 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145075</link><description>游릭 07:28 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 04:28:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:27 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145074</link><description>游릭 07:27 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 04:27:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:10 Failure of the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145073</link><description>游릭 07:10 Failure of the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 04:10:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:10 Attention! Droze Dronov-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145072</link><description>游릭 07:10 Attention! Droze Dronov-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 04:10:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:57 Drive alarm to Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145071</link><description>游릭 06:57 Drive alarm to Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 03:57:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:56 Auxiliary alarm in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145070</link><description>游릭 06:56 Auxiliary alarm in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 03:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:56 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145069</link><description>游릭 06:56 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 03:56:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 06:56 Return the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145068</link><description>游리 06:56 Return the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 03:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:42 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145067</link><description>游댮 06:42 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 03:42:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:22 Air Air In Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145066</link><description>游댮 06:22 Air Air In Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 03:22:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 05:54 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145065</link><description>游 05:54 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 02:54:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:50 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145064</link><description>游댮 05:50 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 02:50:49 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>