<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 11:29 Attack Dronov-Kamikadze type lace on the city center</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147576</link><description>游 11:29 Attack Dronov-Kamikadze type lace on the city center #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial_ community This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 08:29:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:20 alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147575</link><description>游릭 11:20 alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 08:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:20 Return of the threat of shock bpadbius threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147574</link><description>游릭 11:20 Return of the threat of shock bpadbius threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 08:20:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:08 The threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147573</link><description>游 11:08 The threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"#m_harkiv_that_harkivskaya_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 08:08:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:07 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147572</link><description>游댮 11:07 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 08:07:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:03 a alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147571</link><description>游릭 11:03 a alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 08:03:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:03 Driven the alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147570</link><description>游릭 11:03 Driven the alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 08:03:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:49 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the railway station</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147569</link><description>游 10:49 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the railway station This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 07:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:47 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city center</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147568</link><description>游 10:47 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city center #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 07:47:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:34 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147567</link><description>游댮 10:34 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 07:34:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:16 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147566</link><description>游댮 10:16 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 07:16:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:11 Dronov-Kamikadze attack last</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147565</link><description>游 10:11 Dronov-Kamikadze attack last This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 07:11:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147564</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 07:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:46 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147563</link><description>游댮 09:46 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 06:46:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:46 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147562</link><description>游댮 09:46 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 06:46:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:31 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Crete on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147561</link><description>游릭 09:31 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Crete on further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 06:31:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:31 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147560</link><description>游릭 09:31 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 06:31:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:20 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city center</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147559</link><description>游 09:20 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city center #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 06:20:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:14 Attack drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147558</link><description>游 09:14 Attack drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 06:14:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:14 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147557</link><description>游댮 09:14 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 06:14:36 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>