<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 13:24 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139944</link><description>游릭 13:24 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 10:24:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:24 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139943</link><description>游릭 13:24 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADze#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 10:24:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:19 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139942</link><description>游댮 13:19 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 10:19:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:19 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139941</link><description>游댮 13:19 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 10:19:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:54 Attack drones-Kamikadzerukh in the direction</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139940</link><description>游 12:54 Attack drones-Kamikadzerukh in the direction This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 09:54:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:54 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139939</link><description>游댮 12:54 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 09:54:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:59 Close the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139938</link><description>游릭 11:59 Close the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:59:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:52 The threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139937</link><description>游릭 11:52 The threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:52:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:52 WARNING! DRAWE DRONNES-Kamikadze!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139936</link><description>游릭 11:52 WARNING! DRAWE DRONNES-Kamikadze! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:52:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:30 APPLICATION OF DRONNES-CAMIKADIETIP PRANCE, traffic in the direction of 3 sections</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139935</link><description>游 11:30 APPLICATION OF DRONNES-CAMIKADIETIP PRANCE, traffic in the direction of 3 sections#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:30:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:29 Threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139934</link><description>游댮 11:29 Threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:29:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:27 Close the threat of Artobstil to the Bilenkovskaya Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139933</link><description>游릭 11:27 Close the threat of Artobstil to the Bilenkovskaya Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:27:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:26 Attack Drones-Camikadzethip Prayer</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139932</link><description>游 11:26 Attack Drones-Camikadzethip Prayer This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:26:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:20 Threat of Artebil Still! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139931</link><description>游댮 11:20 Threat of Artebil Still! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:20:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:17 pumping anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139930</link><description>游리 11:17 pumping anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:17:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:13 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139929</link><description>游댮 11:13 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:13:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:10 pm alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139928</link><description>游릭 11:10 pm alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:10:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:06 Plowing the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139927</link><description>游릭 11:06 Plowing the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:06:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:06 Attention! Droze Dronov-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139926</link><description>游릭 11:06 Attention! Droze Dronov-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:06:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:47 threat of shelling! Now in the Belenkovsky territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139925</link><description>游댮 10:47 threat of shelling! Now in the Belenkovsky territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 07:47:19 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>