<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 11:52 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152119</link><description>游 11:52 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 08:52:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:52 The threat of artobrats to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Cont attention, anxiety is still in:- Nikopol district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152118</link><description>游리 11:52 The threat of artobrats to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Cont attention, anxiety is still in:- Nikopol district#Pokrovskaya_T territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 08:52:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:44 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152117</link><description>游댮 11:44 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 08:44:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:42 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152116</link><description>游릭 11:42 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Watch for further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 08:42:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:24 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Consider, the alarm is still in:- Nikopol district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152115</link><description>游리 11:24 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Consider, the alarm is still in:- Nikopol district#m_nikopol_that_nikopol. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 08:24:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:24 Attention! Please note that the alarm is still in:- Nikopol district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152114</link><description>游리 11:24 Attention! Please note that the alarm is still in:- Nikopol district#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 08:24:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:23 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152113</link><description>游댮 11:23 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 08:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:16 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152112</link><description>游댮 11:16 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 08:16:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:10 PM Anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152111</link><description>游릭 11:10 PM Anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 08:10:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:47 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city center</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152110</link><description>游 10:47 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city center #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 07:47:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:34 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152109</link><description>游릭 10:34 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region. Watch for further messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 07:34:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 10:34 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152108</link><description>游리 10:34 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 07:34:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:28 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152107</link><description>游댮 10:28 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 07:28:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:23 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152106</link><description>游댮 10:23 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 07:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:18 Drone attack, ammunition is possible city center</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152105</link><description>游 10:18 Drone attack, ammunition is possible city center #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 07:18:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:18 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152104</link><description>游댮 10:18 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 07:18:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:12 Air Alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152103</link><description>游댮 10:12 Air Alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 07:12:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:12 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152102</link><description>游댮 10:12 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 07:12:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:10 PM threats of artobrats in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152101</link><description>游릭 10:10 PM threats of artobrats in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 07:10:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:10 Attention! Droze Dronov-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152100</link><description>游릭 10:10 Attention! Droze Dronov-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 07:10:57 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>