<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 05:11 Fragrant anxiety in the Uman District.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129939</link><description>游릭 05:11 Fragrant anxiety in the Uman District.Creck on Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 03:11:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 05:09 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129938</link><description>游 05:09 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 03:09:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:04 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129937</link><description>游댮 05:04 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 03:04:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:01 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129936</link><description>游릭 05:01 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 03:01:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:01 Air anxiety in the Volyn Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129935</link><description>游댮 05:01 Air anxiety in the Volyn Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Volyn_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 03:01:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:57 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129934</link><description>游댮 04:57 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.#M_kiiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 02:57:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:46 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129933</link><description>游댮 04:46 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 02:46:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:44 Auxiliary alarm in Zvenigorod district.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129932</link><description>游릭 04:44 Auxiliary alarm in Zvenigorod district.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 02:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:37 Dumping anxiety in the Vinnytsia region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129931</link><description>游릭 04:37 Dumping anxiety in the Vinnytsia region. Watch for further messages.#Vinnytsia_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 02:37:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:31 Drive anxiety in Cherkasy district.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129930</link><description>游릭 04:31 Drive anxiety in Cherkasy district.Creck on further messages.#Cherkasy_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 02:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:30 Fragrant anxiety in Zolotonsky District.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129929</link><description>游릭 04:30 Fragrant anxiety in Zolotonsky District.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 02:30:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:17 Dumping anxiety in Kyiv. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129928</link><description>游릭 04:17 Dumping anxiety in Kyiv. Stop by further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 02:17:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:14 Drive alarm to Poltava region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129927</link><description>游릭 04:14 Drive alarm to Poltava region. Watch for further reports.#Poltava_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 02:14:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:40 Air alarm to the Khmelnytsky region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129926</link><description>游댮 03:40 Air alarm to the Khmelnytsky region follow the following messages.#Khmelnitskaya This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 01:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:23 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129925</link><description>游댮 03:23 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 01:23:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:04 Air anxiety in the Rivne region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129924</link><description>游댮 03:04 Air anxiety in the Rivne region follow the following messages.#Rivne_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 01:04:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:01 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129923</link><description>游댮 03:01 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 01:01:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:52 Attention !!! Drive the threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129922</link><description>游릭 02:52 Attention !!! Drive the threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 00:52:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 02:50 PM Anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-mirorskaya territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivska Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129921</link><description>游리 02:50 PM Anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-mirorskaya territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivska Territorial Community This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 00:50:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 02:49 Flow to the Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129920</link><description>游리 02:49 Flow to the Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya district#Zaporizhzhya_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 00:49:49 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>