<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 22:15 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Include on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135896</link><description>游릭 22:15 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Include on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 19:15:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:59 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135895</link><description>游댮 21:59 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 18:59:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:47 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135894</link><description>游댮 21:47 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 18:47:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:34 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135893</link><description>游댮 21:34 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 18:34:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:06 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135892</link><description>游댮 21:06 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 18:06:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 20:52 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135891</link><description>游 20:52 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 17:52:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:51 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135890</link><description>游댮 20:51 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 17:51:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:51 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135889</link><description>游댮 20:51 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 17:51:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:11 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135888</link><description>游댮 20:11 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 17:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:11 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135887</link><description>游댮 20:11 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 17:11:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:11 Air anxiety in the Zaporizhzhia region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135886</link><description>游댮 20:11 Air anxiety in the Zaporizhzhia region follow the following messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 17:11:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:11 Air anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135885</link><description>游댮 20:11 Air anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 17:11:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:07 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135884</link><description>游댮 20:07 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 17:07:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>?</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135883</link><description>? This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 16:42:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:53 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135882</link><description>游댮 18:53 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 15:53:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:25 WARNING !!! DONE ASKRIGHT OF USEED AVIRTED AVIRT BOMB (Kabiv).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135881</link><description>游릭 18:25 WARNING !!! DONE ASKRIGHT OF USEED AVIRTED AVIRT BOMB (Kabiv).#Zaporizhzhia. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 15:25:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:25 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135880</link><description>游릭 18:25 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 15:25:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:23 Attention !!! Drive the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135879</link><description>游릭 18:23 Attention !!! Drive the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 15:23:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:22 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135878</link><description>游릭 18:22 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 15:22:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 18:22 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135877</link><description>游리 18:22 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya district#Zaporizhzhya_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 15:22:21 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>