<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 13:16 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city center</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148355</link><description>游 13:16 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city center #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 10:16:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:14 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148354</link><description>游릭 13:14 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on subsequent messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 10:14:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:10 Return the threats of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148353</link><description>游릭 13:10 Return the threats of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 10:10:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 13:09 attack drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148352</link><description>游 13:09 attack drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 10:09:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:09 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148351</link><description>游댮 13:09 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:03 Air Alarm to Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148350</link><description>游댮 13:03 Air Alarm to Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Chernihiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 10:03:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:43 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148349</link><description>游릭 12:43 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the following messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 09:43:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:43 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148348</link><description>游릭 12:43 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 09:43:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:43 Return the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). In order to further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148347</link><description>游릭 12:43 Return the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). In order to further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 09:43:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:43 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148346</link><description>游릭 12:43 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 09:43:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:43 The threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148345</link><description>游리 12:43 The threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 09:43:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:43 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetsky territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148344</link><description>游리 12:43 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetsky territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 09:43:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:43 Return the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148343</link><description>游리 12:43 Return the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 09:43:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:35 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148342</link><description>游릭 12:35 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 09:35:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:35 Attention! Rap off the attack of drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148341</link><description>游릭 12:35 Attention! Rap off the attack of drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 09:35:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:32 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148340</link><description>游릭 12:32 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further reports.#Nikopol_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 09:32:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:32 Dumping anxiety in Kryvyi Rih District.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148339</link><description>游릭 12:32 Dumping anxiety in Kryvyi Rih District.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 09:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:32 Dumping anxiety in Pavlograd district. Stop after further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148338</link><description>游릭 12:32 Dumping anxiety in Pavlograd district. Stop after further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 09:32:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:32 Driven anxiety in the Dnieper district.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148337</link><description>游릭 12:32 Driven anxiety in the Dnieper district.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 09:32:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:32 Driven Alarm to Novomoskovsk District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148336</link><description>游릭 12:32 Driven Alarm to Novomoskovsk District. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 09:32:11 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>