<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 18:16 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aircraft bombs (cabin). Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149143</link><description>游 18:16 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aircraft bombs (cabin). Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 15:16:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:11 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149142</link><description>游댮 18:11 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 15:11:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:11 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149141</link><description>游댮 18:11 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 15:11:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 17:45 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149140</link><description>游리 17:45 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 14:45:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:31 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149139</link><description>游릭 17:31 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on subsequent messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 14:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:25 Reduce the threat of Artobstil to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149138</link><description>游릭 17:25 Reduce the threat of Artobstil to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 14:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:07 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149137</link><description>游댮 17:07 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 14:07:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:11 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149136</link><description>游릭 16:11 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 13:11:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:59 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149135</link><description>游댮 14:59 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 11:59:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:45 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149134</link><description>游댮 14:45 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 11:45:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:41 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149133</link><description>游댮 14:41 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 11:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:29 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149132</link><description>游댮 14:29 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 11:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149131</link><description>游 14:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:49 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149130</link><description>游릭 13:49 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:49:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:35 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149129</link><description>游릭 13:35 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:35:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:35 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149128</link><description>游릭 13:35 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:35:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:16 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149127</link><description>游댮 13:16 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:16:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:01 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149126</link><description>游릭 13:01 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:01:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:01 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149125</link><description>游릭 13:01 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:01:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:58 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149124</link><description>游릭 12:58 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 09:58:46 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>