<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 09:27 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146517</link><description>游릭 09:27 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creat by further messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 06:27:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:24 Air anxiety in the Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146516</link><description>游댮 09:24 Air anxiety in the Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Chernihiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 06:24:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:05 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146515</link><description>游댮 09:05 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 06:05:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:05 Air anxiety in the Donetsk region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146514</link><description>游댮 09:05 Air anxiety in the Donetsk region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 06:05:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:03 Attack Dronivative Discharges of Ammunition, Old Part District</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146513</link><description>游 09:03 Attack Dronivative Discharges of Ammunition, Old Part District #M_Nikopol_that_nikopol_ Territorial_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 06:03:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 08:57 Attack drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146512</link><description>游 08:57 Attack drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 05:57:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 08:56 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin Lapinka</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146511</link><description>游 08:56 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin Lapinka #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 05:56:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 08:50 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146510</link><description>游 08:50 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 05:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:47 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146509</link><description>游댮 08:47 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 05:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:42 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk to shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146508</link><description>游댮 08:42 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk to shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 05:42:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:41 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146507</link><description>游댮 08:41 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 05:41:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:33 Drive anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146506</link><description>游릭 08:33 Drive anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 05:33:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:33 Drive alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creb</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146505</link><description>游릭 08:33 Drive alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creb This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 05:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:33 Return the threat of Artobstil to the Bilenkovskaya Territorial Community. Take the following reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146504</link><description>游릭 08:33 Return the threat of Artobstil to the Bilenkovskaya Territorial Community. Take the following reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 05:33:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 08:33 Drawing anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146503</link><description>游리 08:33 Drawing anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community#Kharkiv_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 05:33:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:32 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146502</link><description>游릭 08:32 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 05:32:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:24 The threat of shelling in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Solid by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146501</link><description>游릭 08:24 The threat of shelling in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Solid by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 05:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 08:08 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146500</link><description>游 08:08 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 05:08:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:08 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146499</link><description>游댮 08:08 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 05:08:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:00 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146498</link><description>游릭 08:00 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 05:00:41 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>