<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 07:53 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151499</link><description>游릭 07:53 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 04:53:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:21 Air anxiety in Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151498</link><description>游댮 07:21 Air anxiety in Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.#Pavlograd_ Region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 04:21:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:20 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151497</link><description>游댮 07:20 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 04:20:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:36 AMAGABIBIBIUM ALREADY AVIRTION AVIRIABLE BOMB (Kabiv).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151496</link><description>游릭 06:36 AMAGABIBIBIUM ALREADY AVIRTION AVIRIABLE BOMB (Kabiv). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 03:36:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:35 PM Anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151495</link><description>游릭 06:35 PM Anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 03:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 06:35 Pleasure anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Cont attention, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151494</link><description>游리 06:35 Pleasure anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Cont attention, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district#Zaporizhzhia_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 03:35:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:35 Plowing the threat of shock Blividbium threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151493</link><description>游릭 06:35 Plowing the threat of shock Blividbium threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 03:35:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:07 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151492</link><description>游릭 06:07 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creat by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 03:07:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 06:01 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of Down Uars</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151491</link><description>游 06:01 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of Down Uars This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 03:01:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:00 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151490</link><description>游댮 06:00 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 03:00:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 05:58 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151489</link><description>游 05:58 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 02:58:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:50 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151488</link><description>游댮 05:50 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 02:50:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:26 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151487</link><description>游댮 03:26 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:26:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:22 Air Air In Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151486</link><description>游댮 03:22 Air Air In Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:22:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:21 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151485</link><description>游댮 03:21 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:21:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:57 Axiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151484</link><description>游릭 02:57 Axiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 23:57:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:57 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151483</link><description>游릭 02:57 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 23:57:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:26 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151482</link><description>游릭 02:26 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 23:26:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:26 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151481</link><description>游릭 02:26 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 23:26:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:19 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151480</link><description>游댮 01:19 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 22:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>