<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>🔴 10:11 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141450</link><description>🔴 10:11 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 07:11:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141449</link><description>🟠 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 07:00:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟡 09:56 Flashing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganets Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141448</link><description>🟡 09:56 Flashing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganets Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 06:56:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 09:56 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141447</link><description>🟢 09:56 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 06:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 09:56 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141446</link><description>🟢 09:56 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 06:56:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟡 09:40 The threat of a shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141445</link><description>🟡 09:40 The threat of a shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 06:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟡 09:40 Attention! Please note that anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141444</link><description>🟡 09:40 Attention! Please note that anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 06:40:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 09:36 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141443</link><description>🔴 09:36 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 06:36:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 09:32 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141442</link><description>🔴 09:32 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 06:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 09:30 Threat of shelling! The Chervonohrigor Territorial Community is now Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141441</link><description>🔴 09:30 Threat of shelling! The Chervonohrigor Territorial Community is now Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 06:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 09:29 Air anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141440</link><description>🔴 09:29 Air anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 06:29:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 09:28 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141439</link><description>🔴 09:28 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 06:28:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 09:28 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141438</link><description>🔴 09:28 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 06:28:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 09:27 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141437</link><description>🔴 09:27 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 06:27:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 09:21 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141436</link><description>🔴 09:21 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 06:21:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 09:17 Close the threat of Artobzhtlil to the Chervonohrigor territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141435</link><description>🟢 09:17 Close the threat of Artobzhtlil to the Chervonohrigor territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 06:17:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 09:16 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh in the direction of the city center</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141434</link><description>🟠 09:16 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh in the direction of the city center #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 06:16:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 09:15 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzev area of ​​the old part, traffic in the direction</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141433</link><description>🟠 09:15 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzev area of ​​the old part, traffic in the direction This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 06:15:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 09:14 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, traffic in the direction of the lamp</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141432</link><description>🟠 09:14 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, traffic in the direction of the lamp This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 06:14:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 09:13 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141431</link><description>🔴 09:13 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 06:13:49 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>