<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 12:39 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137437</link><description>游댮 12:39 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 09:39:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:38 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137436</link><description>游댮 12:38 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 09:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:36 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137435</link><description>游댮 12:36 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kirovograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 09:36:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:36 Air Alarm to Poltava Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137434</link><description>游댮 12:36 Air Alarm to Poltava Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Poltava_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 09:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:30 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137433</link><description>游댮 12:30 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 09:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:30 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137432</link><description>游댮 12:30 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 09:30:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:28 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137431</link><description>游댮 12:28 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 09:28:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:26 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137430</link><description>游릭 12:26 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 09:26:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:13 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137429</link><description>游댮 12:13 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 09:13:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:37 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137428</link><description>游릭 11:37 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:37:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:35 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137427</link><description>游리 11:35 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:35:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:30 Plowing the threat of artebing in Marganets and Marhanetsky Territorial Community. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137426</link><description>游릭 11:30 Plowing the threat of artebing in Marganets and Marhanetsky Territorial Community. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:30:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:27 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137425</link><description>游댮 11:27 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:27:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:17 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137424</link><description>游릭 11:17 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:17:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:15 Pleasure anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137423</link><description>游릭 11:15 Pleasure anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:15:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:15 Pleasure in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137422</link><description>游릭 11:15 Pleasure in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:15:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:12 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137421</link><description>游릭 11:12 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:12:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:07 Auxiliary alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137420</link><description>游릭 11:07 Auxiliary alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:07:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:07 The threat of percussion bplavidbium threat of percussion UAV</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137419</link><description>游릭 11:07 The threat of percussion bplavidbium threat of percussion UAV#M_Kharkiv_tha_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:07:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:54 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137418</link><description>游댮 10:54 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 07:54:23 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>