<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 10:51 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city center</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152943</link><description>游 10:51 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city center #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 07:51:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:50 AM Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin NKDC</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152942</link><description>游 10:50 AM Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin NKDC #M_Nikopol_that_nikopol_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 07:50:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:47 plout anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152941</link><description>游릭 10:47 plout anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 07:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:47 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152940</link><description>游릭 10:47 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 07:47:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:47 Auxiliary alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152939</link><description>游릭 10:47 Auxiliary alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 07:47:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 10:47 pumping anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152938</link><description>游리 10:47 pumping anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 07:47:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:36 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152937</link><description>游 10:36 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 07:36:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:35 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152936</link><description>游댮 10:35 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 07:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:30 Plowing of the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152935</link><description>游릭 10:30 Plowing of the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 07:30:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:30 AM ATTENTION! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152934</link><description>游릭 10:30 AM ATTENTION! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 07:30:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:29 Driven anxiety in the Odesa region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152933</link><description>游릭 10:29 Driven anxiety in the Odesa region.Creck on further messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 07:29:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:29 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152932</link><description>游릭 10:29 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Watch for further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 07:29:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:29 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152931</link><description>游릭 10:29 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further reports.#Nikopol_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 07:29:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:29 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152930</link><description>游릭 10:29 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 07:29:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 10:29 a alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Nikopol district- Marganets and Marhanetsky territorial community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152929</link><description>游리 10:29 a alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Nikopol district- Marganets and Marhanetsky territorial community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 07:29:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:29 Driven to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152928</link><description>游릭 10:29 Driven to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 07:29:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:29 Driven the alarm to Cherkasy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152927</link><description>游릭 10:29 Driven the alarm to Cherkasy region.Creck on further messages.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 07:29:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:28 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152926</link><description>游릭 10:28 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region. Since further reports.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 07:28:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:13 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152925</link><description>游댮 10:13 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 07:13:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:13 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152924</link><description>游댮 10:13 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 07:13:27 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>