<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 11:47 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138456</link><description>游댮 11:47 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 08:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:47 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138455</link><description>游댮 11:47 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow the following messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 08:47:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:43 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138454</link><description>游댮 11:43 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 08:43:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:15 pumping anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Marganets and Marganets Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138453</link><description>游리 11:15 pumping anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Marganets and Marganets Territorial Community#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 08:15:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:15 Pleasure anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138452</link><description>游릭 11:15 Pleasure anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 08:15:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:15 A. Run in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138451</link><description>游릭 11:15 A. Run in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 08:15:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:09 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138450</link><description>游릭 11:09 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 08:09:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:09 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138449</link><description>游릭 11:09 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 08:09:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 10:58 pm a alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138448</link><description>游리 10:58 pm a alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 07:58:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:55 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138447</link><description>游댮 10:55 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 07:55:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:48 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138446</link><description>游댮 10:48 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 07:48:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:48 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138445</link><description>游댮 10:48 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 07:48:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:44 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138444</link><description>游댮 10:44 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 07:44:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:39 Air anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138443</link><description>游댮 10:39 Air anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 07:39:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:38 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138442</link><description>游댮 10:38 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 07:38:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:38 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138441</link><description>游댮 10:38 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 07:38:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:35 Plowing the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138440</link><description>游릭 10:35 Plowing the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 07:35:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:35 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138439</link><description>游릭 10:35 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADze#m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 07:35:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:31 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138438</link><description>游댮 10:31 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 07:31:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:26 Return the threat of Artobstil to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138437</link><description>游릭 10:26 Return the threat of Artobstil to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 07:26:21 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>