<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 08:23 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129963</link><description>游댮 08:23 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 06:23:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:19 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129962</link><description>游댮 08:19 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 06:19:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:51 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129961</link><description>游댮 07:51 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 05:51:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:35 Plowing the threat of arteblow to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129960</link><description>游릭 07:35 Plowing the threat of arteblow to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 05:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:28 Drive alarm to the Kiev region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129959</link><description>游릭 07:28 Drive alarm to the Kiev region.Creck on further messages.#Kyiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 05:28:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:28 Driven Alarm to Zhytomyr Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129958</link><description>游릭 07:28 Driven Alarm to Zhytomyr Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Zhytomyr This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 05:28:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:04 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129957</link><description>游릭 07:04 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 05:04:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:01 Drive alarm to the Khmelnytsky region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129956</link><description>游릭 07:01 Drive alarm to the Khmelnytsky region. Watch for further messages.#Khmelnitskaya This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 05:01:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:43 Dumping anxiety in the Rivne region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129955</link><description>游릭 06:43 Dumping anxiety in the Rivne region.Creck on further messages.#Rivne_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 04:43:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:36 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129954</link><description>游릭 06:36 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creat by further messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 04:36:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:35 Dumping anxiety in Kyiv. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129953</link><description>游릭 06:35 Dumping anxiety in Kyiv. Salt for further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 04:35:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:24 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129952</link><description>游릭 06:24 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 04:24:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:09 Driven anxiety in the Volyn Oblast. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129951</link><description>游릭 06:09 Driven anxiety in the Volyn Oblast. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 04:09:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:03 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129950</link><description>游댮 06:03 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.#M_kiiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 04:03:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:57 Air anxiety in the Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129949</link><description>游댮 05:57 Air anxiety in the Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Chernihiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 03:57:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:54 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129948</link><description>游릭 05:54 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 03:54:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:49 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129947</link><description>游릭 05:49 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 03:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:43 Drawing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Mirovskaya Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivska Territorial Community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129946</link><description>游리 05:43 Drawing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Mirovskaya Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivska Territorial Community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 03:43:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:43 Attention !!! Drive the threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129945</link><description>游릭 05:43 Attention !!! Drive the threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 03:43:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:41 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129944</link><description>游리 05:41 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district#Zaporizhzhia_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 03:41:41 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>