<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 14:41 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136873</link><description>游댮 14:41 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 11:41:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:33 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136872</link><description>游릭 14:33 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 11:33:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:30 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136871</link><description>游댮 14:30 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 11:30:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:28 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136870</link><description>游댮 14:28 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 11:28:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:25 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136869</link><description>游댮 14:25 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 11:25:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:00 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136868</link><description>游 14:00 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 11:00:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:58 threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136867</link><description>游댮 12:58 threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 09:58:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:44 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136866</link><description>游릭 12:44 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 09:44:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:39 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136865</link><description>游리 12:39 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 09:39:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:08 punch alarm to Zaporizhzhia region.Crete on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136864</link><description>游릭 12:08 punch alarm to Zaporizhzhia region.Crete on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 09:08:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:08 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136863</link><description>游릭 12:08 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 09:08:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:08 pm a alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Marganets and Marganets Territorial Community- March Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136862</link><description>游리 12:08 pm a alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Marganets and Marganets Territorial Community- March Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 09:08:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:55 Plowing of the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136861</link><description>游리 11:55 Plowing of the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 08:55:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:19 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136860</link><description>游댮 11:19 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 08:19:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:07 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136859</link><description>游댮 11:07 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 08:07:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:45 A. Return in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136858</link><description>游릭 10:45 A. Return in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 07:45:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:45 Return the threat of shock bpadbius threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136857</link><description>游릭 10:45 Return the threat of shock bpadbius threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 07:45:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:42 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136856</link><description>游댮 10:42 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 07:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:27 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136855</link><description>游릭 10:27 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 07:27:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:27 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marhanetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136854</link><description>游댮 10:27 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marhanetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 07:27:42 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>