<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 18:09 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149349</link><description>游릭 18:09 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 15:09:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:09 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149348</link><description>游릭 18:09 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 15:09:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 18:08 Redeem the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149347</link><description>游리 18:08 Redeem the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 15:08:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:06 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149346</link><description>游릭 18:06 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region. Since further messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 15:06:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 17:00 WARNING !!! DOCERNS OF UNITED AVIRTED AVIRT BOMB (Kabiv).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149345</link><description>游 17:00 WARNING !!! DOCERNS OF UNITED AVIRTED AVIRT BOMB (Kabiv). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 14:00:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:55 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149344</link><description>游댮 16:55 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 13:55:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:55 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149343</link><description>游댮 16:55 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 13:55:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:52 Return the threat of Artobstil to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149342</link><description>游릭 16:52 Return the threat of Artobstil to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 13:52:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:45 Driven the alarm to the Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149341</link><description>游릭 16:45 Driven the alarm to the Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 13:45:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:24 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149340</link><description>游댮 16:24 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 13:24:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:54 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149339</link><description>游댮 15:54 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 12:54:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:05 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149338</link><description>游릭 15:05 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 12:05:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:05 Driven your alarm to the Sumy region.Creat for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149337</link><description>游릭 15:05 Driven your alarm to the Sumy region.Creat for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 12:05:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:46 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149336</link><description>游릭 14:46 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 11:46:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:46 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADE!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149335</link><description>游릭 14:46 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADE! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 11:46:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:33 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149334</link><description>游댮 14:33 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 11:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:02 Attack drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149333</link><description>游 14:02 Attack drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 11:02:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:00 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149332</link><description>游 14:00 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:52 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149331</link><description>游댮 13:52 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 10:52:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:50 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149330</link><description>游댮 13:50 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 10:50:37 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>