<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 16:06 Threat of Artbill! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140349</link><description>游댮 16:06 Threat of Artbill! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 13:06:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 16:05 The threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140348</link><description>游 16:05 The threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 13:05:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:05 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140347</link><description>游댮 16:05 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 13:05:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:03 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140346</link><description>游댮 16:03 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 13:03:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:56 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140345</link><description>游댮 15:56 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 12:56:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:52 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140344</link><description>游릭 15:52 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 12:52:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:34 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140343</link><description>游릭 15:34 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 12:34:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:34 WARNING! DROVIA DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140342</link><description>游릭 15:34 WARNING! DROVIA DRONNES-Kamikadze #M_Nikopol_ti_nikopol_ Territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 12:34:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:58 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140341</link><description>游 14:58 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 11:58:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:49 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140340</link><description>游댮 14:49 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 11:49:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:44 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140339</link><description>游릭 14:44 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 11:44:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:44 Driven the threat of shock bplavidbiy threat of percussion UAV</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140338</link><description>游릭 14:44 Driven the threat of shock bplavidbiy threat of percussion UAV#M_Kharkiv_tha_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 11:44:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>?</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140337</link><description>? This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 11:44:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:43 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140336</link><description>游댮 14:43 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 11:43:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:32 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140335</link><description>游릭 14:32 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 11:32:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:32 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140334</link><description>游릭 14:32 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 11:32:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:00 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140333</link><description>游 14:00 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 11:00:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 13:59 Attack drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140332</link><description>游 13:59 Attack drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 10:59:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 13:56 attack drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140331</link><description>游 13:56 attack drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 10:56:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:39 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140330</link><description>游릭 13:39 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 10:39:47 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>