<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 22:36 Driven anxiety in the Kherson region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133174</link><description>游릭 22:36 Driven anxiety in the Kherson region. Since further reports.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 20:36:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:26 Driven the alarm to the Kiev region. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133173</link><description>游릭 22:26 Driven the alarm to the Kiev region. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 20:26:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:23 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133172</link><description>游댮 22:23 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 20:23:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:12 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133171</link><description>游릭 22:12 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 20:12:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:01 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133170</link><description>游댮 22:01 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 20:01:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:58 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133169</link><description>游댮 21:58 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 19:58:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:46 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133168</link><description>游댮 21:46 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 19:46:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:45 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133167</link><description>游댮 21:45 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 19:45:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:44 Air Air In Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133166</link><description>游댮 21:44 Air Air In Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 19:44:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 21:28 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133165</link><description>游 21:28 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 19:28:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 21:17 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133164</link><description>游리 21:17 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 19:17:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮11</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133163</link><description>游댮11 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 19:15:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:59 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133162</link><description>游릭 20:59 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 18:59:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:42 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133161</link><description>游릭 20:42 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 18:42:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 20:42 Drawing of anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Community Community Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133160</link><description>游리 20:42 Drawing of anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Community Community Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 18:42:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:38 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133159</link><description>游댮 20:38 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 18:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:38 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133158</link><description>游댮 20:38 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 18:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:30 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133157</link><description>游댮 20:30 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:25 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133156</link><description>游댮 20:25 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 18:25:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:14 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133155</link><description>游댮 20:14 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 18:14:53 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>