<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 14:39 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137874</link><description>游릭 14:39 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 11:39:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 14:39 Drawing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky Territorial Community-March Territorial Community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivska Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137873</link><description>游리 14:39 Drawing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky Territorial Community-March Territorial Community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivska Territorial Community This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 11:39:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:38 Dreaming of anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137872</link><description>游릭 14:38 Dreaming of anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 11:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:38 Draw an alarm to the Zaporizhzhia region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137871</link><description>游릭 14:38 Draw an alarm to the Zaporizhzhia region. Since further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 11:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:35 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137870</link><description>游댮 14:35 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 11:35:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>?</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137869</link><description>? This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 11:11:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:11 a alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137868</link><description>游릭 14:11 a alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 11:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:04 Driven anxiety in the Odesa region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137867</link><description>游릭 14:04 Driven anxiety in the Odesa region.Creck on further messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 11:04:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:04 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137866</link><description>游릭 14:04 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 11:04:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:03 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creb</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137865</link><description>游릭 14:03 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creb This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 11:03:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:03 Dumping anxiety in the Volyn region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137864</link><description>游릭 14:03 Dumping anxiety in the Volyn region.Creat by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 11:03:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:03 Drive alarm to the Khmelnytsky region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137863</link><description>游릭 14:03 Drive alarm to the Khmelnytsky region. Watch for further messages.#Khmelnitskaya This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 11:03:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:03 Driven the alarm to the Zhytomyr region.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137862</link><description>游릭 14:03 Driven the alarm to the Zhytomyr region.Creck on further reports.#Zhytomyr_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 11:03:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:03 Driven the alarm to Ternopil region. Salt by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137861</link><description>游릭 14:03 Driven the alarm to Ternopil region. Salt by further messages.#Ternopil_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 11:03:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:03 Driven anxiety in the Ivano-Frankivsk region.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137860</link><description>游릭 14:03 Driven anxiety in the Ivano-Frankivsk region.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 11:03:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:03 Driven the alarm to Lviv region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137859</link><description>游릭 14:03 Driven the alarm to Lviv region.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 11:03:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:03 Driven anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137858</link><description>游릭 14:03 Driven anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 11:03:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:03 Driven anxiety in the Kiev region. Follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137857</link><description>游릭 14:03 Driven anxiety in the Kiev region. Follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 11:03:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:03 Driven to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137856</link><description>游릭 14:03 Driven to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 11:03:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:03 Drive alarm to Cherkasy region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137855</link><description>游릭 14:03 Drive alarm to Cherkasy region. Watch for further messages.#Cherkasy_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 11:03:28 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>