<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 17:07 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137888</link><description>游댮 17:07 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 14:07:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:06 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137887</link><description>游릭 17:06 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 14:06:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:32 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137886</link><description>游댮 16:32 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 13:32:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:20 Failure to alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137885</link><description>游릭 16:20 Failure to alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 13:20:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:20 Logging the threat of Cabbaths The threat of use</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137884</link><description>游릭 16:20 Logging the threat of Cabbaths The threat of use This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 13:20:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 16:20 Failure to alarm to Kharkiv region.Cont attention, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district-Lipetsk territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137883</link><description>游리 16:20 Failure to alarm to Kharkiv region.Cont attention, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district-Lipetsk territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community#Kharkiv_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 13:20:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:20 Driven the alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137882</link><description>游릭 16:20 Driven the alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 13:20:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:11 Air alarm to the Donetsk region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137881</link><description>游댮 16:11 Air alarm to the Donetsk region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 13:11:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 15:49 Threat of use of the copecreal use of managed aviation bombs</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137880</link><description>游 15:49 Threat of use of the copecreal use of managed aviation bombs#m_harkiv_tha_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 12:49:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:49 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137879</link><description>游댮 15:49 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 12:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:43 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137878</link><description>游릭 15:43 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 12:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:16 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137877</link><description>游댮 15:16 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 12:16:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:16 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137876</link><description>游릭 15:16 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 12:16:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:12 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137875</link><description>游댮 15:12 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 12:12:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:39 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137874</link><description>游릭 14:39 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 11:39:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 14:39 Drawing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky Territorial Community-March Territorial Community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivska Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137873</link><description>游리 14:39 Drawing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky Territorial Community-March Territorial Community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivska Territorial Community This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 11:39:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:38 Dreaming of anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137872</link><description>游릭 14:38 Dreaming of anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 11:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:38 Draw an alarm to the Zaporizhzhia region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137871</link><description>游릭 14:38 Draw an alarm to the Zaporizhzhia region. Since further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 11:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:35 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137870</link><description>游댮 14:35 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 11:35:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>?</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137869</link><description>? This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 11:11:54 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>