<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游리 13:24 Alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142229</link><description>游리 13:24 Alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:24:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:23 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142228</link><description>游릭 13:23 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region. Since further reports.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:23:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:23 Drive alarms in Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142227</link><description>游릭 13:23 Drive alarms in Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:23:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:21 Driven anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142226</link><description>游릭 13:21 Driven anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:21:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:21 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142225</link><description>游릭 13:21 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:21:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:18 Reduce threatening the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142224</link><description>游릭 13:18 Reduce threatening the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:18:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 13:18 Flowing anxiety in the Zaporizhzhia region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142223</link><description>游리 13:18 Flowing anxiety in the Zaporizhzhia region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district#Zaporizhzhya_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:18:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:08 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142222</link><description>游릭 13:08 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:08:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:08 Shock the threat of shock bplavidbium threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142221</link><description>游릭 13:08 Shock the threat of shock bplavidbium threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:08:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:57 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142220</link><description>游 12:57 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"#m_harkiv_that_harkivskaya_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:57 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142219</link><description>游댮 12:57 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:57:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:52 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142218</link><description>游댮 12:52 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:52:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:52 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142217</link><description>游댮 12:52 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:52:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:32 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142216</link><description>游 12:32 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:32:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:25 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142215</link><description>游댮 12:25 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:25:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:24 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142214</link><description>游 12:24 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:24:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:24 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142213</link><description>游댮 12:24 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:24:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:23 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142212</link><description>游댮 12:23 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:23:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:21 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142211</link><description>游릭 12:21 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:21:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:20 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142210</link><description>游댮 12:20 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:20:44 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>