<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 12:25 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137819</link><description>游릭 12:25 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 09:25:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:16 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137818</link><description>游릭 12:16 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 09:16:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:14 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137817</link><description>游댮 12:14 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 09:14:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:05 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137816</link><description>游댮 12:05 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 09:05:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:05 Auxiliary alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137815</link><description>游릭 12:05 Auxiliary alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 09:05:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:05 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137814</link><description>游릭 12:05 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporozhye This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 09:05:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:05 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137813</link><description>游릭 12:05 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region. Stop by further messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 09:05:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:05 Failure to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marhanetsky Territorial Community- Mirorsk Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivsk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137812</link><description>游리 12:05 Failure to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marhanetsky Territorial Community- Mirorsk Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivsk Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 09:05:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:05 Attention !!! Note, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137811</link><description>游리 12:05 Attention !!! Note, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya region#Zaporizhzhya_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 09:05:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:04 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137810</link><description>游댮 12:04 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 09:04:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:04 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137809</link><description>游댮 12:04 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 09:04:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:34 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137808</link><description>游댮 11:34 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 08:34:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:31 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137807</link><description>游릭 11:31 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creat by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 08:31:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:31 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137806</link><description>游댮 11:31 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 08:31:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:30 A. Run in the Kherson region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137805</link><description>游릭 11:30 A. Run in the Kherson region. Watch for further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 08:30:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:27 Close the threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137804</link><description>游릭 11:27 Close the threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 08:27:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:11 pm alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapets Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137803</link><description>游리 11:11 pm alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapets Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 08:11:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:11 pm alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137802</link><description>游릭 11:11 pm alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 08:11:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:11 pm alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137801</link><description>游릭 11:11 pm alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 08:11:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:11 pm alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Mirovskaya Territorial Community, Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137800</link><description>游리 11:11 pm alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Mirovskaya Territorial Community, Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 08:11:03 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>