<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 22:40 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143000</link><description>游댮 22:40 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 19:40:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 22:25 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142999</link><description>游 22:25 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 19:25:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 22:22 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142998</link><description>游 22:22 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 19:22:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:21 Dumping anxiety in the Kiev region. Follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142997</link><description>游릭 22:21 Dumping anxiety in the Kiev region. Follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 19:21:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:14 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142996</link><description>游댮 22:14 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 19:14:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:02 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142995</link><description>游댮 22:02 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 19:02:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:55 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142994</link><description>游댮 21:55 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 18:55:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 21:44 Driven Alarm to Poltava Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142993</link><description>游릭 21:44 Driven Alarm to Poltava Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 18:44:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:04 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142992</link><description>游댮 21:04 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 18:04:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:33 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142991</link><description>游댮 19:33 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 16:33:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:27 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142990</link><description>游댮 19:27 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 16:27:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:27 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142989</link><description>游댮 19:27 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 16:27:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:57 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142988</link><description>游댮 18:57 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 15:57:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:37 Air anxiety in the Dnieper District Surveat as Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142987</link><description>游댮 18:37 Air anxiety in the Dnieper District Surveat as Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 15:37:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:36 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142986</link><description>游댮 18:36 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 15:36:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:35 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142985</link><description>游릭 18:35 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 15:35:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:26 Driven the alarm to the Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142984</link><description>游릭 18:26 Driven the alarm to the Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 15:26:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:49 Driven the anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142983</link><description>游릭 17:49 Driven the anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 14:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:49 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142982</link><description>游릭 17:49 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the following messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 14:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:46 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142981</link><description>游릭 17:46 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 14:46:27 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>