<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 07:28 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147543</link><description>游릭 07:28 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 04:28:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:10 Done alarm to Donetsk region. Follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147542</link><description>游릭 07:10 Done alarm to Donetsk region. Follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 04:10:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:10 Flowing alarm to Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147541</link><description>游릭 07:10 Flowing alarm to Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 04:10:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:24 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147540</link><description>游댮 06:24 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 03:24:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:21 Driven anxiety in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147539</link><description>游릭 06:21 Driven anxiety in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 03:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:21 Drive the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147538</link><description>游릭 06:21 Drive the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 03:21:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:21 WARNING! DROVIA DRONNE-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147537</link><description>游릭 06:21 WARNING! DROVIA DRONNE-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_The community This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 03:21:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 06:20 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147536</link><description>游리 06:20 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 03:20:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:20 Auxiliary alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147535</link><description>游릭 06:20 Auxiliary alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 03:20:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:20 Return the threat of the use of cards the threat of use</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147534</link><description>游릭 06:20 Return the threat of the use of cards the threat of use This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 03:20:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:36 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147533</link><description>游댮 05:36 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 02:36:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 05:36 Threat of use of the copecreal use of managed aviation bombs</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147532</link><description>游 05:36 Threat of use of the copecreal use of managed aviation bombs#m_harkiv_tha_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 02:36:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:35 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147531</link><description>游댮 05:35 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 02:35:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:11 Frame alarms to the Kiev region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147530</link><description>游릭 05:11 Frame alarms to the Kiev region. Since further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 02:11:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:11 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147529</link><description>游릭 05:11 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creat by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 02:11:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:11 Dumping anxiety in Cherkasy district.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147528</link><description>游릭 05:11 Dumping anxiety in Cherkasy district.Creck on further messages.#Cherkasy_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 02:11:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:11 Fragrant anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147527</link><description>游릭 05:11 Fragrant anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 02:11:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:09 Driven the alarm in Kyiv. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147526</link><description>游릭 05:09 Driven the alarm in Kyiv. Salt for further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 02:09:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:54 Alarm in Zvenigorod district. Stop after further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147525</link><description>游릭 04:54 Alarm in Zvenigorod district. Stop after further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 01:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:54 Dumping anxiety in the Uman district.Creck on subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147524</link><description>游릭 04:54 Dumping anxiety in the Uman district.Creck on subsequent messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 01:54:14 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>