<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 20:53 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149155</link><description>游댮 20:53 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.#Kryvyi Rih Ri This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 17:53:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:52 Air alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149154</link><description>游댮 20:52 Air alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.#Nikopol_ Region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 17:52:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:29 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149153</link><description>游릭 20:29 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 17:29:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:03 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149152</link><description>游릭 20:03 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 17:03:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:03 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149151</link><description>游릭 20:03 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #M_Nikopol_ti_nikopol_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 17:03:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:19 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149150</link><description>游댮 19:19 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 16:19:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 19:17 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin Novopavlivka</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149149</link><description>游 19:17 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin Novopavlivka #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 16:17:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:17 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149148</link><description>游댮 19:17 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 16:17:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:52 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149147</link><description>游릭 18:52 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia Oblast.Creck on further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 15:52:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 18:52 Attention !!! Notice, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149146</link><description>游리 18:52 Attention !!! Notice, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya region#Pologovsky_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 15:52:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:52 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Crete on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149145</link><description>游릭 18:52 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Crete on further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 15:52:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:52 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149144</link><description>游릭 18:52 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 15:52:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 18:16 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aircraft bombs (cabin). Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149143</link><description>游 18:16 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aircraft bombs (cabin). Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 15:16:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:11 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149142</link><description>游댮 18:11 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 15:11:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:11 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149141</link><description>游댮 18:11 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 15:11:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 17:45 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149140</link><description>游리 17:45 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 14:45:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:31 Driven the alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149139</link><description>游릭 17:31 Driven the alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 14:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:25 Reduce the threat of Artobstil to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149138</link><description>游릭 17:25 Reduce the threat of Artobstil to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 14:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:07 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149137</link><description>游댮 17:07 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 14:07:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:11 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149136</link><description>游릭 16:11 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 13:11:12 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>