<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 12:31 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139040</link><description>游 12:31 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 09:31:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:31 Provision of the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139039</link><description>游릭 12:31 Provision of the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 09:31:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:30 AMAGABIBIBIE ALREADY OF USED AVIRTED AVIRT BOMB (Kabiv).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139038</link><description>游릭 12:30 AMAGABIBIBIE ALREADY OF USED AVIRTED AVIRT BOMB (Kabiv).#Zaporizhzhia. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 09:30:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:30 Failure to alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139037</link><description>游릭 12:30 Failure to alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 09:30:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:30 Fragrance in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139036</link><description>游릭 12:30 Fragrance in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 09:30:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:30 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139035</link><description>游리 12:30 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 09:30:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:30 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139034</link><description>游리 12:30 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya district#Zaporizhzhya_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 09:30:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:29 Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139033</link><description>游리 12:29 Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 09:29:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:02 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, Novopavlivka area</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139032</link><description>游 12:02 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, Novopavlivka area#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 09:02:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:57 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack! Movement to the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139031</link><description>游 11:57 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack! Movement to the city#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial_ community This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 08:57:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:56 Threat of Artbill! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk to shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139030</link><description>游댮 11:56 Threat of Artbill! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk to shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 08:56:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:37 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, traffic in the direction of the third section</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139029</link><description>游 11:37 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, traffic in the direction of the third section#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 08:37:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:31 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, traffic to the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139028</link><description>游 11:31 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, traffic to the city#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 08:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:25 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139027</link><description>游댮 11:25 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 08:25:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:23 Return the threat of artobstil in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139026</link><description>游릭 11:23 Return the threat of artobstil in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 08:23:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:21 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, traffic in the direction of a lamp/third district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139025</link><description>游 11:21 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, traffic in the direction of a lamp/third district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 08:21:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:21 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139024</link><description>游댮 11:21 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 08:21:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:21 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139023</link><description>游댮 11:21 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 08:21:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:15 Auxiliary alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139022</link><description>游릭 11:15 Auxiliary alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 08:15:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:15 Run the threat of percussion bplavidbiy threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139021</link><description>游릭 11:15 Run the threat of percussion bplavidbiy threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 08:15:33 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>