<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 01:25 Drive alarm to Cherkasy district.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149192</link><description>游릭 01:25 Drive alarm to Cherkasy district.Creck on further reports.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 22:25:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:25 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149191</link><description>游릭 01:25 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creat by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 22:25:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:20 Failure to alarm to Nikopol district.This followed by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149190</link><description>游릭 01:20 Failure to alarm to Nikopol district.This followed by subsequent messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 22:20:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:20 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsk District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149189</link><description>游댮 01:20 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsk District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 22:20:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:18 Air alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149188</link><description>游댮 01:18 Air alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.#Nikopol_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 22:18:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:11 Air alarm in the Dnieper District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149187</link><description>游댮 01:11 Air alarm in the Dnieper District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 22:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:57 Air anxiety in Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149186</link><description>游댮 00:57 Air anxiety in Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.#Pavlograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 21:57:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:55 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149185</link><description>游댮 00:55 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.#M_kiiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 21:55:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:49 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149184</link><description>游댮 00:49 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 21:49:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:47 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149183</link><description>游댮 00:47 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporizhia_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 21:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:14 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149182</link><description>游댮 00:14 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 21:14:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:50 pm a alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149181</link><description>游릭 23:50 pm a alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 20:50:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:30 Air alarm to Cherkasy district to care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149180</link><description>游댮 23:30 Air alarm to Cherkasy district to care for further messages.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 20:30:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:30 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149179</link><description>游댮 23:30 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 20:30:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:28 Driven Alarm to Nikopol District. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149178</link><description>游릭 23:28 Driven Alarm to Nikopol District. Watch for further messages.#Nikopol_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 20:28:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:27 Driven the alarm to Kryvyi Rih District. Stop the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149177</link><description>游릭 23:27 Driven the alarm to Kryvyi Rih District. Stop the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 20:27:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:27 Driven the anxiety in the Dnieper district.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149176</link><description>游릭 23:27 Driven the anxiety in the Dnieper district.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 20:27:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:27 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsk District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149175</link><description>游릭 23:27 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsk District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 20:27:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:27 Draw alarms in Kamyansky District.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149174</link><description>游릭 23:27 Draw alarms in Kamyansky District.Creck on further messages.#Kamyan_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 20:27:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:03 Driven anxiety in the Kherson region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149173</link><description>游릭 23:03 Driven anxiety in the Kherson region. Since further reports.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 20:03:04 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>