<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 23:22 The threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143103</link><description>游댮 23:22 The threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 20:22:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 22:52 The threat of use of the copecreal use of managed aviation bombs</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143102</link><description>游 22:52 The threat of use of the copecreal use of managed aviation bombs#m_harkiv_that_harkivskay This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 19:52:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:52 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143101</link><description>游댮 22:52 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 19:52:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:52 Air Air In Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143100</link><description>游댮 22:52 Air Air In Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 19:52:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:55 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143099</link><description>游댮 21:55 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 18:55:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:29 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143098</link><description>游댮 21:29 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 18:29:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮11</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143097</link><description>游댮11 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 18:15:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 19:47 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143096</link><description>游릭 19:47 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 16:47:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:20 Return the threat of artebors in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143095</link><description>游릭 18:20 Return the threat of artebors in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 15:20:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:06 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143094</link><description>游릭 18:06 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 15:06:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:58 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143093</link><description>游릭 17:58 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 14:58:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:58 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143092</link><description>游릭 17:58 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia Oblast.Creck on further messages.#Zaporozhye This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 14:58:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:15 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143091</link><description>游댮 17:15 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 14:15:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:56 Driven the alarm to Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143090</link><description>游릭 16:56 Driven the alarm to Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 13:56:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:49 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143089</link><description>游댮 16:49 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 13:49:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:46 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143088</link><description>游댮 16:46 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 13:46:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:58 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143087</link><description>游릭 15:58 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 12:58:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:58 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143086</link><description>游릭 15:58 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 12:58:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 15:54 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143085</link><description>游리 15:54 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 12:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 15:16 Attack Drones-Camikadzethip Prayer</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143084</link><description>游 15:16 Attack Drones-Camikadzethip Prayer #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 12:16:15 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>