<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 13:42 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137615</link><description>游릭 13:42 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 10:42:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:40 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137614</link><description>游릭 13:40 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 10:40:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 13:38 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137613</link><description>游리 13:38 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 10:38:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:37 Air anxiety in Vinnytsia region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137612</link><description>游댮 13:37 Air anxiety in Vinnytsia region follow the following messages.#Vinnytsia_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 10:37:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:37 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137611</link><description>游댮 13:37 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 10:37:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:37 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137610</link><description>游댮 13:37 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 10:37:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:37 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137609</link><description>游댮 13:37 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 10:37:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:37 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137608</link><description>游댮 13:37 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 10:37:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:37 Air Alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137607</link><description>游댮 13:37 Air Alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Cherkasy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 10:37:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:37 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137606</link><description>游댮 13:37 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 10:37:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:37 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137605</link><description>游댮 13:37 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 10:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:36 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137604</link><description>游댮 13:36 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 10:36:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:36 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137603</link><description>游댮 13:36 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 10:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:36 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137602</link><description>游댮 13:36 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 10:36:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:36 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137601</link><description>游댮 13:36 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 10:36:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:35 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137600</link><description>游댮 13:35 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 10:35:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:32 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137599</link><description>游댮 13:32 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 10:32:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:30 Draft in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137598</link><description>游릭 13:30 Draft in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 10:30:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 13:27 The threat of artobrats to Pokrovskaya territorial community. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137597</link><description>游리 13:27 The threat of artobrats to Pokrovskaya territorial community. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region#Pokrovskaya_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 10:27:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:15 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137596</link><description>游릭 13:15 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 10:15:09 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>