<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 12:04 The threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132136</link><description>游릭 12:04 The threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 10:04:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:04 Draw an alarm to Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132135</link><description>游릭 12:04 Draw an alarm to Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 10:04:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:54 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132134</link><description>游댮 11:54 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 09:54:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:37 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132133</link><description>游댮 11:37 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 09:37:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:34 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132132</link><description>游릭 11:34 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 09:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:31 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132131</link><description>游댮 11:31 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 09:31:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:17 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132130</link><description>游댮 11:17 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 09:17:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:01 Driven the alarm to the Sumy region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132129</link><description>游릭 11:01 Driven the alarm to the Sumy region.Creat by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 09:01:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 10:58 pm a alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetsky territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132128</link><description>游리 10:58 pm a alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetsky territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 08:58:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:57 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132127</link><description>游릭 10:57 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region.Creck on further reports.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 08:57:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:57 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132126</link><description>游릭 10:57 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 08:57:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:44 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132125</link><description>游댮 10:44 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 08:44:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:43 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132124</link><description>游댮 10:43 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 08:43:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:34 Close the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132123</link><description>游릭 10:34 Close the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 08:34:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:33 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132122</link><description>游릭 10:33 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 08:33:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132121</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 08:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:44 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132120</link><description>游댮 09:44 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 07:44:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 9:44</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132119</link><description>游댮 9:44 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 07:44:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:08 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132118</link><description>游댮 09:08 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 07:08:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:55 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132117</link><description>游댮 08:55 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 06:55:47 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>