<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 07:39 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the old part</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143411</link><description>游 07:39 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the old part This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 04:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:39 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143410</link><description>游댮 07:39 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 04:39:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:38 Air anxiety in the Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143409</link><description>游댮 07:38 Air anxiety in the Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Chernihiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 04:38:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:38 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143408</link><description>游댮 07:38 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 04:38:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:27 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143407</link><description>游릭 07:27 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 04:27:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:09 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Stop after further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143406</link><description>游릭 07:09 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Stop after further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 04:09:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:48 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143405</link><description>游댮 06:48 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 03:48:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:27 Dumping anxiety in the Zhytomyr region.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143404</link><description>游릭 05:27 Dumping anxiety in the Zhytomyr region.Creck on further reports.#Zhytomyr This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 02:27:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:10 Driven the alarm to Vinnytsia region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143403</link><description>游릭 05:10 Driven the alarm to Vinnytsia region.Creat by further messages.#Vinnytsia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 02:10:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 5</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143402</link><description>游 5 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 02:00:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:59 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143401</link><description>游댮 04:59 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 01:59:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:59 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143400</link><description>游댮 04:59 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 01:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:58 Dumping anxiety in Zolotonsky District.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143399</link><description>游릭 04:58 Dumping anxiety in Zolotonsky District.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 01:58:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:58 Dumping anxiety in the Kiev region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143398</link><description>游릭 04:58 Dumping anxiety in the Kiev region. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 01:58:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:58 Driven the alarm to Cherkasy district. Stop after further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143397</link><description>游릭 04:58 Driven the alarm to Cherkasy district. Stop after further messages.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 01:58:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:58 Driven Alarm to Uman District.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143396</link><description>游릭 04:58 Driven Alarm to Uman District.Creck on Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 01:58:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:58 Failure to the Zvenigorod District. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143395</link><description>游릭 04:58 Failure to the Zvenigorod District. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 01:58:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:57 Driven the alarm in Kyiv. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143394</link><description>游릭 04:57 Driven the alarm in Kyiv. Stop by further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 01:57:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:55 Drive alarm to Poltava region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143393</link><description>游릭 04:55 Drive alarm to Poltava region.Creck on further messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 01:55:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:49 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143392</link><description>游릭 04:49 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further reports.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 01:49:02 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>