<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 20:15 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140373</link><description>游릭 20:15 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 17:15:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:45 The threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140372</link><description>游댮 19:45 The threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 16:45:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:04 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140371</link><description>游댮 19:04 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 16:04:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:55 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140370</link><description>游릭 18:55 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 15:55:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:55 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140369</link><description>游릭 18:55 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADze #M_Nikopol_ti_nikopol. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 15:55:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 18:30 WARNING! Drone-Kamikadze Dronov-type</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140368</link><description>游 18:30 WARNING! Drone-Kamikadze Dronov-type This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 15:30:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:30 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140367</link><description>游댮 18:30 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 15:30:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 18:28 Drawing of anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140366</link><description>游리 18:28 Drawing of anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 15:28:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:05 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140365</link><description>游릭 18:05 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region. Stop by further messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 15:05:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:05 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140364</link><description>游릭 18:05 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 15:05:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:04 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140363</link><description>游릭 18:04 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 15:04:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:56 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140362</link><description>游댮 17:56 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 14:56:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:34 Driven the alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140361</link><description>游릭 17:34 Driven the alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 14:34:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:21 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140360</link><description>游댮 17:21 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 14:21:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:20 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140359</link><description>游댮 17:20 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 14:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:20 Driven the alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140358</link><description>游릭 17:20 Driven the alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 14:20:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:19 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140357</link><description>游댮 17:19 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 14:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:09 Return the threat of Artobstil to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140356</link><description>游릭 17:09 Return the threat of Artobstil to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 14:09:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 16:55 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140355</link><description>游리 16:55 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 13:55:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:55 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140354</link><description>游릭 16:55 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 13:55:08 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>