<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游리 05:33 Flashing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135597</link><description>游리 05:33 Flashing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 02:33:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:33 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135596</link><description>游릭 05:33 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 02:33:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:33 Run the threat of shock Blividbium threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135595</link><description>游릭 05:33 Run the threat of shock Blividbium threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 02:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:33 Drive anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135594</link><description>游릭 05:33 Drive anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 02:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:10 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135593</link><description>游댮 03:10 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:10:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 02:53 Flashing anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Manganese and Marganetsky Territorial Community, Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Mirovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135592</link><description>游리 02:53 Flashing anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Manganese and Marganetsky Territorial Community, Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Mirovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 23:53:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:52 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creat for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135591</link><description>游릭 02:52 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creat for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 23:52:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:51 Drive anxiety in the Poltava region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135590</link><description>游릭 02:51 Drive anxiety in the Poltava region.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 23:51:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:47 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135589</link><description>游릭 02:47 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Of Zaporizhzhia_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 23:47:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:47 Axiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135588</link><description>游릭 02:47 Axiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 23:47:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:02 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135587</link><description>游릭 02:02 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creat by further messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 23:02:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:02 Drive alarm to the Kiev region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135586</link><description>游릭 01:02 Drive alarm to the Kiev region. Since further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 22:02:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:01 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creck on subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135585</link><description>游릭 01:01 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creck on subsequent messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 22:01:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:01 Driven the alarm to Cherkasy district.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135584</link><description>游릭 01:01 Driven the alarm to Cherkasy district.Creck on further messages.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 22:01:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:50 pm alarm in Kyiv. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135583</link><description>游릭 00:50 pm alarm in Kyiv. Salt for further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 21:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮33</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135582</link><description>游댮33 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 20:33:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:16 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135581</link><description>游댮 23:16 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 20:16:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:05 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135580</link><description>游댮 23:05 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 20:05:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:43 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135579</link><description>游댮 22:43 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:43:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:43 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135578</link><description>游댮 22:43 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:43:39 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>