<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 02:19 Air anxiety in Kryvyi Rih District Surveat as Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148642</link><description>游댮 02:19 Air anxiety in Kryvyi Rih District Surveat as Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 23:19:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:12 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148641</link><description>游댮 02:12 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 23:12:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:02 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148640</link><description>游댮 02:02 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 23:02:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:51 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148639</link><description>游댮 01:51 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 22:51:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:45 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148638</link><description>游댮 01:45 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kirovograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 22:45:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:44 Air anxiety in the Rivne region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148637</link><description>游댮 01:44 Air anxiety in the Rivne region follow the following messages.#Rivne_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 22:44:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:40 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148636</link><description>游댮 01:40 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 22:40:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:28 Air alarm to the Khmelnytsky region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148635</link><description>游댮 01:28 Air alarm to the Khmelnytsky region follow the following messages.#Khmelnitskaya This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 22:28:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:22 Air anxiety in Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148634</link><description>游댮 01:22 Air anxiety in Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.#Pavlograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 22:22:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:21 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148633</link><description>游댮 01:21 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 22:21:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:07 Air anxiety in the Dnieper District care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148632</link><description>游댮 01:07 Air anxiety in the Dnieper District care for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 22:07:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:54 Failure to alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148631</link><description>游릭 00:54 Failure to alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 21:54:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:39 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148630</link><description>游댮 00:39 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 21:39:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:43 Air alarm to Zhytomyr Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148629</link><description>游댮 23:43 Air alarm to Zhytomyr Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zhytomyr_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 20:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:39 Air alarm to Vinnytsia region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148628</link><description>游댮 23:39 Air alarm to Vinnytsia region follow the following messages.#Vinnytsia_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 20:39:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 23:33 Drawing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetsky territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148627</link><description>游리 23:33 Drawing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetsky territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 20:33:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:14 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148626</link><description>游댮 23:14 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 20:14:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:56 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148625</link><description>游댮 22:56 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kirovograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 19:56:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:55 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148624</link><description>游댮 22:55 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 19:55:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:55 Air alarm in Zvenigorod District Survene from further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148623</link><description>游댮 22:55 Air alarm in Zvenigorod District Survene from further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 19:55:47 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>