<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 07:44 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153961</link><description>游댮 07:44 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 04:44:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 07:32 Driven Alarm to Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153960</link><description>游리 07:32 Driven Alarm to Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 04:32:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:32 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153959</link><description>游릭 07:32 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 04:32:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:32 Drive the threat of shock bplavidbium threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153958</link><description>游릭 07:32 Drive the threat of shock bplavidbium threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 04:32:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:23 Air Alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153957</link><description>游댮 07:23 Air Alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 04:23:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 07:22 The threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Pray"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153956</link><description>游 07:22 The threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Pray"#m_harkiv_that_harkivskaya_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 04:22:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:21 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153955</link><description>游댮 07:21 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 04:21:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:15 Plowing the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153954</link><description>游릭 07:15 Plowing the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 04:15:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:10 Drawing anxiety in the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153953</link><description>游릭 07:10 Drawing anxiety in the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 04:10:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:54 Driven anxiety in Donetsk Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153952</link><description>游릭 06:54 Driven anxiety in Donetsk Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Donetsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 03:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:53 Driven an alarm to Sinelnikov District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153951</link><description>游릭 06:53 Driven an alarm to Sinelnikov District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 03:53:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:52 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153950</link><description>游릭 06:52 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region. Since further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 03:52:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:13 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153949</link><description>游댮 06:13 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporozhye_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 03:13:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:05 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153948</link><description>游댮 06:05 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.#Sinelnikov. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 03:05:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:00 pm alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153947</link><description>游릭 06:00 pm alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 03:00:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:00 Down the threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153946</link><description>游릭 06:00 Down the threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 03:00:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 06:00 pm alarm to Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153945</link><description>游리 06:00 pm alarm to Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 03:00:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:00 pm alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153944</link><description>游릭 06:00 pm alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 03:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 05:46 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153943</link><description>游 05:46 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_that_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 02:46:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:46 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial COMMUNICATIONS FALSE.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153942</link><description>游댮 05:46 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial COMMUNICATIONS FALSE. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 02:46:09 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>