<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 09:19 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin of the old part</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149621</link><description>游 09:19 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin of the old part #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 06:19:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:19 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149620</link><description>游댮 09:19 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 06:19:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:07 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149619</link><description>游댮 09:07 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 06:07:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:02 Air anxiety in Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149618</link><description>游댮 09:02 Air anxiety in Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 06:02:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:24 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149617</link><description>游릭 08:24 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 05:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:24 WARNING! DRONES DRONI-KAMKADze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149616</link><description>游릭 08:24 WARNING! DRONES DRONI-KAMKADze #m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 05:24:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 07:45 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149615</link><description>游 07:45 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 04:45:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:45 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149614</link><description>游댮 07:45 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 04:45:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:42 WARNING !!! DONE ALREADY OF USED AVIRTED AVIRIA BOMB (Kabiv).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149613</link><description>游릭 07:42 WARNING !!! DONE ALREADY OF USED AVIRTED AVIRIA BOMB (Kabiv).#Zaporizhzhia. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 04:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:41 WARNING !!! Drive the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149612</link><description>游릭 07:41 WARNING !!! Drive the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 04:41:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:40 Auxiliary in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149611</link><description>游릭 07:40 Auxiliary in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 04:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 07:39 Flow to the Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety continues in:- Zaporizhzhya district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149610</link><description>游리 07:39 Flow to the Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety continues in:- Zaporizhzhya district#Zaporizhzhya_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 04:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:36 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149609</link><description>游릭 07:36 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 04:36:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 07:35 Axiety in the Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149608</link><description>游리 07:35 Axiety in the Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community#Kharkiv_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 04:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:35 Dumping anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creach for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149607</link><description>游릭 07:35 Dumping anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creach for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 04:35:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:33 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149606</link><description>游릭 07:33 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 04:33:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 05:54 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149605</link><description>游 05:54 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 02:54:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 05:52 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149604</link><description>游 05:52 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 02:52:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:47 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149603</link><description>游댮 05:47 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 02:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:47 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149602</link><description>游댮 05:47 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 02:47:44 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>