<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 23:49 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149384</link><description>游댮 23:49 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 20:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:36 Air alarm in the Dnieper District care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149383</link><description>游댮 23:36 Air alarm in the Dnieper District care for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 20:36:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:36 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149382</link><description>游댮 23:36 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 20:36:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:22 Driven the alarm to the Kyiv region. Further in further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149381</link><description>游릭 23:22 Driven the alarm to the Kyiv region. Further in further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 20:22:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:22 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149380</link><description>游릭 23:22 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 20:22:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:22 Driven Alarm to the Chernihiv Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149379</link><description>游릭 23:22 Driven Alarm to the Chernihiv Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 20:22:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:22 Driven the alarm to Cherkasy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149378</link><description>游릭 23:22 Driven the alarm to Cherkasy region.Creck on further messages.#Cherkasy_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 20:22:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:19 Threat of Arteball! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149377</link><description>游댮 23:19 Threat of Arteball! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 20:19:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:19 Air alarm to Nikopol District Survene from further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149376</link><description>游댮 23:19 Air alarm to Nikopol District Survene from further reports.#Nikopol_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 20:19:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:13 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149375</link><description>游댮 23:13 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 20:13:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 23:06 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149374</link><description>游 23:06 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 20:06:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:04 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149373</link><description>游댮 23:04 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 20:04:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:03 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149372</link><description>游댮 23:03 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 20:03:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:03 Air alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149371</link><description>游댮 23:03 Air alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Cherkasy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 20:03:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:01 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149370</link><description>游댮 23:01 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 20:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:01 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149369</link><description>游댮 23:01 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 20:01:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:01 Air alarm to Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149368</link><description>游댮 23:01 Air alarm to Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Chernihiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 20:01:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:00 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149367</link><description>游댮 23:00 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 20:00:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:00 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149366</link><description>游댮 23:00 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 20:00:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:49 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149365</link><description>游댮 22:49 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 19:49:46 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>