<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 14:21 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141265</link><description>游릭 14:21 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region. Since further reports.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 11:21:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:21 Driven the alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141264</link><description>游릭 14:21 Driven the alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 11:21:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:20 Drawing anxiety in the Poltava region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141263</link><description>游릭 14:20 Drawing anxiety in the Poltava region.Creck on further messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 11:20:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141262</link><description>游 14:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 11:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:59 Driven the alarm in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141261</link><description>游릭 13:59 Driven the alarm in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:59:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:59 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141260</link><description>游릭 13:59 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the subsequent messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:59:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:49 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141259</link><description>游댮 13:49 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:49 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141258</link><description>游댮 13:49 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:49:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:49 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141257</link><description>游댮 13:49 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:49:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:48 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141256</link><description>游댮 13:48 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:48:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:41 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141255</link><description>游댮 13:41 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:31 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141254</link><description>游릭 13:31 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:31:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:23 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141253</link><description>游릭 13:23 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:23:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:04 The threat of artobustril in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141252</link><description>游릭 13:04 The threat of artobustril in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:04:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:04 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141251</link><description>游릭 13:04 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:04:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:49 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141250</link><description>游댮 12:49 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 09:49:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:49 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141249</link><description>游댮 12:49 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 09:49:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:33 Drawing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district-Lipetsk territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141248</link><description>游리 12:33 Drawing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district-Lipetsk territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community#Kharkiv_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 09:33:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:24 Supervise threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141247</link><description>游릭 12:24 Supervise threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 09:24:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:24 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141246</link><description>游리 12:24 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district#Zaporizhzhya_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 09:24:06 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>