<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 09:47 Attention! Drone attack! Perhaps discharges of explosive items!  Be in shelters!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144373</link><description>游 09:47 Attention! Drone attack! Perhaps discharges of explosive items!  Be in shelters! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 06:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:32 Air anxiety in the Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144372</link><description>游댮 09:32 Air anxiety in the Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Chernihiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 06:32:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:32 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144371</link><description>游댮 09:32 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 06:32:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:31 Draw an alarm to Zaporizhzhya region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144370</link><description>游릭 09:31 Draw an alarm to Zaporizhzhya region. Since further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 06:31:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:12 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144369</link><description>游댮 09:12 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 06:12:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:11 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144368</link><description>游댮 09:11 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 06:11:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:01 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144367</link><description>游댮 09:01 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 06:01:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:56 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144366</link><description>游댮 08:56 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 05:56:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 08:40 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144365</link><description>游 08:40 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 05:40:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 08:29 Attack drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144364</link><description>游 08:29 Attack drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 05:29:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 08:27 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144363</link><description>游 08:27 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 05:27:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:19 Threat of Artebil Still! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144362</link><description>游댮 08:19 Threat of Artebil Still! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 05:19:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:15 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144361</link><description>游릭 08:15 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 05:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:15 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144360</link><description>游릭 08:15 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #M_Nikopol_ti_nikopol_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 05:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 07:36 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack is ongoing, movement to the old part</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144359</link><description>游 07:36 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack is ongoing, movement to the old part This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 04:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:34 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144358</link><description>游댮 07:34 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 04:34:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 07:20 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh in the direction</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144357</link><description>游 07:20 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh in the direction This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 04:20:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 07:17 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on Novopavlivka</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144356</link><description>游 07:17 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on Novopavlivka #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 04:17:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 07:16 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack continues</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144355</link><description>游 07:16 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack continues This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 04:16:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 07:13 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the old part</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144354</link><description>游 07:13 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the old part This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 04:13:35 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>