<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 06:44 Dumping anxiety in the Khmelnytsky region.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139370</link><description>游릭 06:44 Dumping anxiety in the Khmelnytsky region.Creck on further reports.#Khmelnitskaya This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 03:44:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:41 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139369</link><description>游댮 06:41 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 03:41:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:38 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139368</link><description>游댮 06:38 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 03:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:11 Pleasure the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139367</link><description>游릭 06:11 Pleasure the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 03:11:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:10 Air alarm to the Khmelnytsky region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139366</link><description>游댮 06:10 Air alarm to the Khmelnytsky region follow the following messages.#Khmelnitskaya This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 03:10:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:10 Air alarm in Zvenigorod District to care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139365</link><description>游댮 06:10 Air alarm in Zvenigorod District to care for further reports.#Zvenigorod_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 03:10:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:10 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139364</link><description>游댮 06:10 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 03:10:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:54 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Posts.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139363</link><description>游댮 05:54 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Posts. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 02:54:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 05:53 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139362</link><description>游 05:53 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_tha_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 02:53:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:53 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139361</link><description>游댮 05:53 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 02:53:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:27 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139360</link><description>游댮 05:27 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 02:27:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:21 Driven anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139359</link><description>游릭 05:21 Driven anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 02:21:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:21 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139358</link><description>游릭 05:21 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Watch for further messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 02:21:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:20 Done alarm to Donetsk region. Follow the subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139357</link><description>游릭 05:20 Done alarm to Donetsk region. Follow the subsequent messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 02:20:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:19 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139356</link><description>游릭 05:19 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 02:19:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:19 Driven the anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139355</link><description>游릭 05:19 Driven the anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 02:19:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:19 Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139354</link><description>游리 05:19 Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 02:19:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:19 Draw an alarm to Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139353</link><description>游릭 05:19 Draw an alarm to Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporozhye This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 02:19:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:19 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139352</link><description>游릭 05:19 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region.Creck on further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 02:19:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:19 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139351</link><description>游릭 05:19 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 02:19:33 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>