<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 05:40 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143038</link><description>游릭 05:40 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 02:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:38 Driven your alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143037</link><description>游릭 05:38 Driven your alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Stop by further messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 02:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:38 Dumping anxiety in the Uman District.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143036</link><description>游릭 05:38 Dumping anxiety in the Uman District.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 02:38:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:38 Driven the alarm to Zvenigorod district. Stop after further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143035</link><description>游릭 05:38 Driven the alarm to Zvenigorod district. Stop after further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 02:38:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:38 Drive alarm to Vinnytsia region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143034</link><description>游릭 05:38 Drive alarm to Vinnytsia region. Watch for further messages.#Vinnytsia_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 02:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:26 Driven the threat of artebrow to Pokrovskaya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143033</link><description>游릭 05:26 Driven the threat of artebrow to Pokrovskaya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 02:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:57 Air anxiety in Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143032</link><description>游댮 02:57 Air anxiety in Donetsk Region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 23:57:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:55 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143031</link><description>游릭 02:55 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 23:55:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:54 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143030</link><description>游릭 02:54 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 23:54:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:54 Dumping anxiety in Kryvyi Rih District. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143029</link><description>游릭 02:54 Dumping anxiety in Kryvyi Rih District. Watch for further messages.#Kryvyi Rih Ri This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 23:54:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:54 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143028</link><description>游릭 02:54 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District.Creck on further reports.#Pavlograd_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 23:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:54 Driven anxiety in the Dnieper District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143027</link><description>游릭 02:54 Driven anxiety in the Dnieper District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 23:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:54 Alarm to Novomoskovsk District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143026</link><description>游릭 02:54 Alarm to Novomoskovsk District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 23:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:54 Driven Alarm to Kamyansky District. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143025</link><description>游릭 02:54 Driven Alarm to Kamyansky District. Salt for further messages.#Kamyan_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 23:54:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:54 Driven the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143024</link><description>游릭 02:54 Driven the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). Salt for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 23:54:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:53 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143023</link><description>游릭 02:53 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region. Since further reports.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 23:53:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 02:53 Flashing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Chervonohrigor Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143022</link><description>游리 02:53 Flashing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Chervonohrigor Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 23:53:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:53 Return the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143021</link><description>游릭 02:53 Return the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 23:53:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:53 Flowing anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143020</link><description>游릭 02:53 Flowing anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 23:53:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 02:53 Flashing anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143019</link><description>游리 02:53 Flashing anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community#Kharkiv_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 23:53:20 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>