<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 07:44 Air anxiety in the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145854</link><description>游댮 07:44 Air anxiety in the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 04:44:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:44 Air Air In Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145853</link><description>游댮 07:44 Air Air In Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Cherkasy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 04:44:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:44 Air anxiety in Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145852</link><description>游댮 07:44 Air anxiety in Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kirovograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 04:44:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:44 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145851</link><description>游댮 07:44 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 04:44:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:36 Failure to alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145850</link><description>游릭 07:36 Failure to alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 04:36:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:36 Return the threat of shock Blividbium threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145849</link><description>游릭 07:36 Return the threat of shock Blividbium threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 04:36:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:12 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145848</link><description>游릭 07:12 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 04:12:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:11 TRAVEL! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145847</link><description>游릭 07:11 TRAVEL! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 04:11:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 06:47 The threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145846</link><description>游 06:47 The threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"#m_harkiv_that_harkivskaya_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 03:47:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:47 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145845</link><description>游댮 06:47 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 03:47:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:47 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial COMMUNICATIONS FALSE.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145844</link><description>游댮 06:47 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial COMMUNICATIONS FALSE. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 03:47:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 06:41 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145843</link><description>游 06:41 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 03:41:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:40 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145842</link><description>游릭 06:40 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region. Since further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 03:40:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:39 Driven the anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145841</link><description>游릭 06:39 Driven the anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 03:39:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:39 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145840</link><description>游릭 06:39 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the subsequent messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 03:39:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 06:39 Return the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145839</link><description>游리 06:39 Return the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 03:39:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:38 Driven Alarm to the Kiev region. Follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145838</link><description>游릭 05:38 Driven Alarm to the Kiev region. Follow the following messages.#Kyiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 02:38:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 05:19 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145837</link><description>游 05:19 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 02:19:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:11 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145836</link><description>游릭 05:11 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 02:11:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:11 Driven the threat of shock bplavidbiy threat of percussion UAV</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145835</link><description>游릭 05:11 Driven the threat of shock bplavidbiy threat of percussion UAV#M_Kharkiv_tha_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 02:11:44 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>