<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 16:48 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142267</link><description>游댮 16:48 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 13:48:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 16:42 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142266</link><description>游리 16:42 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 13:42:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:07 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142265</link><description>游릭 16:07 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 13:07:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:07 Drive the threat of shock bpadbius threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142264</link><description>游릭 16:07 Drive the threat of shock bpadbius threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 13:07:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 15:55 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142263</link><description>游 15:55 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:55:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:55 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142262</link><description>游댮 15:55 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:55:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:50 PM threats of artobrats to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142261</link><description>游릭 15:50 PM threats of artobrats to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:32 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142260</link><description>游릭 15:32 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:32:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:20 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142259</link><description>游댮 15:20 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:20:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:14 Draw an alarm to the Zaporizhzhia region. Follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142258</link><description>游릭 15:14 Draw an alarm to the Zaporizhzhia region. Follow the following messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:14:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:14 Drawing of anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142257</link><description>游릭 15:14 Drawing of anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:14:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:13 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142256</link><description>游릭 15:13 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:13:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:13 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142255</link><description>游릭 15:13 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:13:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:57 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142254</link><description>游댮 14:57 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 11:57:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:57 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142253</link><description>游댮 14:57 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 11:57:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:54 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142252</link><description>游댮 14:54 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 11:54:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:52 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142251</link><description>游댮 14:52 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 11:52:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:49 Attack Drones-Camikadzethip Prayer</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142250</link><description>游 14:49 Attack Drones-Camikadzethip Prayer This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 11:49:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:49 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142249</link><description>游댮 14:49 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 11:49:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:49 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142248</link><description>游댮 14:49 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 11:49:12 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>