<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 20:41 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151051</link><description>游댮 20:41 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 17:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:41 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District to care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151050</link><description>游댮 20:41 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District to care for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 17:41:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:32 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Survene from further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151049</link><description>游댮 20:32 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Survene from further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 17:32:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:31 Air alarm to Nikopol District Survene from further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151048</link><description>游댮 20:31 Air alarm to Nikopol District Survene from further reports.#Nikopol_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 17:31:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:31 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151047</link><description>游댮 20:31 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.#Kryvyi Rih Ri This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 17:31:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:31 Air anxiety in the Dnieper District Surveat for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151046</link><description>游댮 20:31 Air anxiety in the Dnieper District Surveat for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 17:31:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:31 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151045</link><description>游댮 20:31 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 17:31:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:27 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151044</link><description>游댮 20:27 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 17:27:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:13 Air alarm to Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151043</link><description>游댮 20:13 Air alarm to Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.#Pavlograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 17:13:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:06 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsk District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151042</link><description>游댮 20:06 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsk District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 17:06:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:38 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151041</link><description>游댮 19:38 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 16:38:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:23 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151040</link><description>游댮 19:23 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 16:23:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 19:22 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151039</link><description>游 19:22 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_tha_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 16:22:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:08 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151038</link><description>游댮 19:08 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 16:08:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:07 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151037</link><description>游댮 19:07 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 16:07:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:37 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151036</link><description>游댮 18:37 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 15:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:16 Failure to alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151035</link><description>游릭 18:16 Failure to alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 15:16:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:16 Drives the threat of shock bpadbius threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151034</link><description>游릭 18:16 Drives the threat of shock bpadbius threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 15:16:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 18:15 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151033</link><description>游리 18:15 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 15:15:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:55 Driven alarm to Sinelnikov District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151032</link><description>游릭 17:55 Driven alarm to Sinelnikov District. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 14:55:27 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>