<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 14:50 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151367</link><description>游댮 14:50 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 11:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:18 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151366</link><description>游릭 14:18 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 11:18:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>?</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151365</link><description>? This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 11:10:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:10 The threat of percussion bplavidbium threat of percussion UAV</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151364</link><description>游릭 14:10 The threat of percussion bplavidbium threat of percussion UAV#M_Kharkiv_tha_harkivskaya_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 11:10:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>?</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151363</link><description>? This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 11:10:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>?</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151362</link><description>? This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 11:09:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:07 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151361</link><description>游릭 14:07 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 11:07:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:02 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151360</link><description>游 14:02 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 11:02:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:57 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151359</link><description>游릭 13:57 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on subsequent messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 10:57:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:57 Driven Alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151358</link><description>游릭 13:57 Driven Alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 10:57:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:57 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151357</link><description>游릭 13:57 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region. Since further reports.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 10:57:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 13:56 Flashing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151356</link><description>游리 13:56 Flashing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 10:56:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:56 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151355</link><description>游릭 13:56 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 10:56:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:49 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151354</link><description>游댮 13:49 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 10:49:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:46 Drive alarm to the Kiev region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151353</link><description>游릭 13:46 Drive alarm to the Kiev region. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 10:46:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:35 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151352</link><description>游댮 13:35 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 10:35:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:35 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151351</link><description>游댮 13:35 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 10:35:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:34 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151350</link><description>游댮 13:34 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 10:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:34 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151349</link><description>游댮 13:34 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 10:34:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:33 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151348</link><description>游댮 13:33 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 10:33:57 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>