<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 05:54 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149605</link><description>游 05:54 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 02:54:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 05:52 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149604</link><description>游 05:52 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 02:52:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:47 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149603</link><description>游댮 05:47 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 02:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:47 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149602</link><description>游댮 05:47 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 02:47:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:18 WARNING !!! DONE ASKRIGHT ACCEPTED AVIRTEVER BOMB (Kabiv).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149601</link><description>游릭 04:18 WARNING !!! DONE ASKRIGHT ACCEPTED AVIRTEVER BOMB (Kabiv). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 01:18:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:16 Drive alarm to Poltava region. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149600</link><description>游릭 04:16 Drive alarm to Poltava region. Salt for further reports.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 01:16:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:15 Driven the alarm to Kamyansky District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149599</link><description>游릭 04:15 Driven the alarm to Kamyansky District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 01:15:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:15 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsky District. Stop after further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149598</link><description>游릭 04:15 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsky District. Stop after further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 01:15:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:15 Driven anxiety in the Dnieper district.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149597</link><description>游릭 04:15 Driven anxiety in the Dnieper district.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 01:15:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:15 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149596</link><description>游릭 04:15 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 01:15:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:15 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149595</link><description>游릭 04:15 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District. Watch for further reports.#Pavlograd_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 01:15:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 04:15 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149594</link><description>游리 04:15 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district#Zaporizhzhia_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 01:15:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:15 Driven anxiety in Kryvyi Rih District.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149593</link><description>游릭 04:15 Driven anxiety in Kryvyi Rih District.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 01:15:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:15 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149592</link><description>游릭 04:15 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 01:15:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:15 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149591</link><description>游릭 04:15 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 01:15:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:13 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149590</link><description>游릭 04:13 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 01:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:13 Run the threat of shock bplavidbium threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149589</link><description>游릭 04:13 Run the threat of shock bplavidbium threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 01:13:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:11 Dumping anxiety in the Kiev region. Follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149588</link><description>游릭 04:11 Dumping anxiety in the Kiev region. Follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 01:11:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:10 Driven the alarm to the Kherson region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149587</link><description>游릭 04:10 Driven the alarm to the Kherson region. Watch for further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 01:10:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:10 Drawing anxiety in Ternopil region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149586</link><description>游릭 04:10 Drawing anxiety in Ternopil region. Watch for further messages.#Ternopil_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 01:10:29 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>