<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 11:43 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138803</link><description>游댮 11:43 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 08:43:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:36 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138802</link><description>游댮 11:36 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 08:36:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:27 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138801</link><description>游 11:27 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 08:27:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:21 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138800</link><description>游릭 11:21 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 08:21:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:18 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138799</link><description>游 11:18 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 08:18:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:10 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138798</link><description>游릭 11:10 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 08:10:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:10 Attention! Droze Dronov-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138797</link><description>游릭 11:10 Attention! Droze Dronov-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 08:10:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:04 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138796</link><description>游댮 11:04 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 08:04:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:04 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138795</link><description>游댮 11:04 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 08:04:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:48 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, traffic in the direction of the third section!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138794</link><description>游 10:48 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, traffic in the direction of the third section! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 07:48:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:46 Threat of Artebating! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138793</link><description>游댮 10:46 Threat of Artebating! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 07:46:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:43 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138792</link><description>游릭 10:43 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 07:43:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 10:24 Auxiliary in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138791</link><description>游리 10:24 Auxiliary in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 07:24:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:11 a alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138790</link><description>游릭 10:11 a alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 07:11:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:11 Lock the threat of using Cabbaths The threat of application</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138789</link><description>游릭 10:11 Lock the threat of using Cabbaths The threat of application This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 07:11:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138788</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 07:00:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 9</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138787</link><description>游 9 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 06:51:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:50 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138786</link><description>游댮 09:50 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 06:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:46 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138785</link><description>游 09:46 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 06:46:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:32 Return the threat of artobrats in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138784</link><description>游릭 09:32 Return the threat of artobrats in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 06:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>