<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 06:52 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region. Follow the subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134713</link><description>游릭 06:52 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region. Follow the subsequent messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 04:52:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:52 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134712</link><description>游릭 06:52 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 04:52:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:52 Return the threat of the use of Cabbaths The threat of application</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134711</link><description>游릭 06:52 Return the threat of the use of Cabbaths The threat of application This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 04:52:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 06:52 Dumping anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134710</link><description>游리 06:52 Dumping anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 04:52:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:41 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134709</link><description>游릭 06:41 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 04:41:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:04 Close the threat of Artobhstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134708</link><description>游릭 06:04 Close the threat of Artobhstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 04:04:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:57 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134707</link><description>游댮 05:57 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 03:57:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:52 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134706</link><description>游댮 04:52 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 02:52:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:41 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Further in further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134705</link><description>游릭 04:41 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Further in further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 02:41:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 04:36 The threat of use of the cope proportion of the use</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134704</link><description>游 04:36 The threat of use of the cope proportion of the use This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 02:36:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:36 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134703</link><description>游댮 04:36 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 02:36:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:35 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134702</link><description>游댮 04:35 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 02:35:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:58 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134701</link><description>游댮 02:58 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:58:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:42 Drive alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134700</link><description>游릭 02:42 Drive alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:42:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:04 Drive alarm to the Khmelnytsky region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134699</link><description>游릭 02:04 Drive alarm to the Khmelnytsky region. Watch for further reports.#Khmelnitskaya This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:04:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:03 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134698</link><description>游릭 02:03 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Watch for further messages.#Odessa_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:03:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:59 Dumping anxiety in the Zhytomyr region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134697</link><description>游릭 01:59 Dumping anxiety in the Zhytomyr region.Creck on further messages.#Zhytomyr_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 23:59:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:27 Air alarm to the Khmelnytsky region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134696</link><description>游댮 01:27 Air alarm to the Khmelnytsky region follow the following messages.#Khmelnitskaya This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 23:27:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:24 Dumping anxiety in Donetsk region. Follow the subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134695</link><description>游릭 01:24 Dumping anxiety in Donetsk region. Follow the subsequent messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 23:24:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:24 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134694</link><description>游릭 01:24 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 23:24:15 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>