<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 13:27 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153356</link><description>游댮 13:27 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 10:27:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:27 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153355</link><description>游댮 13:27 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 10:27:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:25 Fragrance in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153354</link><description>游릭 13:25 Fragrance in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 10:25:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:25 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153353</link><description>游릭 13:25 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporozhye This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 10:25:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:14 Driven the threat of artobrats in the Chervonohrigor territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153352</link><description>游릭 13:14 Driven the threat of artobrats in the Chervonohrigor territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 10:14:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:13 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creb</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153351</link><description>游릭 13:13 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creb This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 10:13:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:13 Driven anxiety in the Odesa region. Follow the subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153350</link><description>游릭 13:13 Driven anxiety in the Odesa region. Follow the subsequent messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 10:13:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 13:12 Flashing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153349</link><description>游리 13:12 Flashing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 10:12:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:12 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153348</link><description>游릭 13:12 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 10:12:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:12 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153347</link><description>游릭 13:12 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 10:12:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:12 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153346</link><description>游릭 13:12 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 10:12:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:12 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153345</link><description>游릭 13:12 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 10:12:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:12 Driven your alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153344</link><description>游릭 13:12 Driven your alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 10:12:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 13:12 Driven anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153343</link><description>游리 13:12 Driven anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region#Sinelnikovsky_RAIN This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 10:12:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:12 Drive alarm to Cherkasy region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153342</link><description>游릭 13:12 Drive alarm to Cherkasy region. Watch for further messages.#Cherkasy_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 10:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 13:12 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153341</link><description>游리 13:12 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 10:12:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:12 Driven the alarm to the Poltava region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153340</link><description>游릭 13:12 Driven the alarm to the Poltava region.Creck on further messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 10:12:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:57 Attack drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153339</link><description>游 12:57 Attack drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 09:57:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:57 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153338</link><description>游댮 12:57 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 09:57:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:55 The threat of artobrats to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Cont attention, anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153337</link><description>游리 12:55 The threat of artobrats to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Cont attention, anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region#Pokrovskaya_T territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 09:55:28 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>