<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 15:27 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137330</link><description>游릭 15:27 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 12:27:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:10 Air alarm to the Donetsk region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137329</link><description>游댮 15:10 Air alarm to the Donetsk region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 12:10:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:47 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137328</link><description>游댮 14:47 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 11:47:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:40 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Observe by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137327</link><description>游릭 14:40 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Observe by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 11:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:40 Drive alarm to the Odesa region. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137326</link><description>游릭 14:40 Drive alarm to the Odesa region. Stop by further messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 11:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:39 Driven to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137325</link><description>游릭 14:39 Driven to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 11:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:38 Return the threat of Artobzhtlil to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137324</link><description>游릭 14:38 Return the threat of Artobzhtlil to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 11:38:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:34 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137323</link><description>游릭 14:34 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 11:34:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:25 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137322</link><description>游댮 14:25 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 11:25:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:25 Return the threat of artobrats in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137321</link><description>游릭 14:25 Return the threat of artobrats in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 11:25:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:24 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137320</link><description>游댮 14:24 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 11:24:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:21 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137319</link><description>游댮 14:21 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 11:21:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:01 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137318</link><description>游 14:01 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 11:01:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:55 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137317</link><description>游댮 13:55 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 10:55:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 13:55 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137316</link><description>游 13:55 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"#m_harkiv_that_harkivskaya_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 10:55:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:54 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137315</link><description>游댮 13:54 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 10:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:38 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137314</link><description>游릭 13:38 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 10:38:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:38 Shock the threat of shock bpadbius threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137313</link><description>游릭 13:38 Shock the threat of shock bpadbius threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 10:38:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 13:38 Dumping anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137312</link><description>游리 13:38 Dumping anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 10:38:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:37 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137311</link><description>游릭 13:37 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region. Since further messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 10:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>