<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>🔴 22:36 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138924</link><description>🔴 22:36 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 19:36:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 22:34 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138923</link><description>🟠 22:34 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).#Vasylivsky_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 19:34:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 22:30 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138922</link><description>🟠 22:30 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_that_harkivskaya_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 19:30:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 22:30 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138921</link><description>🔴 22:30 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 19:30:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 22:23 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138920</link><description>🔴 22:23 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 19:23:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 22:12 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138919</link><description>🟠 22:12 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 19:12:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 22:12 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze Dronov Drohni Type</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138918</link><description>🟠 22:12 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze Dronov Drohni Type This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 19:12:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 22:10 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138917</link><description>🟠 22:10 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 19:10:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 22:05 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138916</link><description>🔴 22:05 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 19:05:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 22:00 Air alarm in Zvenigorod District to care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138915</link><description>🔴 22:00 Air alarm in Zvenigorod District to care for further reports.#Zvenigorod_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 19:00:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟡 21:59 Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganets Territorial Community, Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138914</link><description>🟡 21:59 Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganets Territorial Community, Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:59:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:57 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138913</link><description>🔴 21:57 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:57:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:57 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138912</link><description>🔴 21:57 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:57:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:55 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138911</link><description>🔴 21:55 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:55:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:29 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138910</link><description>🔴 21:29 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:29:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:29 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138909</link><description>🔴 21:29 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:29:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:18 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138908</link><description>🔴 21:18 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:18:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:18 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138907</link><description>🔴 21:18 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:18:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:08 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138906</link><description>🔴 21:08 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:08:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:08 Air Air In Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138905</link><description>🔴 21:08 Air Air In Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>