<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游리 05:59 The threat of a shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139159</link><description>游리 05:59 The threat of a shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 02:59:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:59 Attention! Note, anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139158</link><description>游리 05:59 Attention! Note, anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 02:59:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:23 Drive anxiety in the Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139157</link><description>游릭 05:23 Drive anxiety in the Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 02:23:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:50 Dumplings in the Kiev region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139156</link><description>游릭 04:50 Dumplings in the Kiev region. Since further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 01:50:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:19 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139155</link><description>游댮 04:19 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 01:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:19 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139154</link><description>游댮 04:19 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 01:19:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:54 Alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139153</link><description>游릭 03:54 Alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:54:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:54 Draw an alarm to Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139152</link><description>游릭 03:54 Draw an alarm to Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporozhye This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:54:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:53 Driven an alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139151</link><description>游릭 03:53 Driven an alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:53:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:53 Drive alarm to Cherkasy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139150</link><description>游릭 03:53 Drive alarm to Cherkasy region.Creck on further messages.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:53:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 3</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139149</link><description>游릭 3 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:53:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:53 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139148</link><description>游릭 03:53 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:53:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:52 Driven anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139147</link><description>游릭 03:52 Driven anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:52:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:34 Air Alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139146</link><description>游댮 03:34 Air Alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Cherkasy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:34:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:33 Air anxiety in Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139145</link><description>游댮 03:33 Air anxiety in Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:33:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:33 Air anxiety in the Kherson Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139144</link><description>游댮 03:33 Air anxiety in the Kherson Oblast follow the following messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:33:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:33 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139143</link><description>游댮 03:33 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:33:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:32 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139142</link><description>游댮 03:32 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:32:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:32 Air anxiety in Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139141</link><description>游댮 03:32 Air anxiety in Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kirovograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:32:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:32 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139140</link><description>游댮 03:32 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:32:40 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>