<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 04:41 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132627</link><description>游릭 04:41 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region. Stop by further messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 02:41:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:26 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132626</link><description>游댮 04:26 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 02:26:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:25 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132625</link><description>游댮 04:25 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 02:25:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:18 Drive alarm to the Khmelnytsky region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132624</link><description>游릭 04:18 Drive alarm to the Khmelnytsky region. Watch for further messages.#Khmelnitskaya This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 02:18:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:16 Drive alarm to Vinnytsia region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132623</link><description>游릭 04:16 Drive alarm to Vinnytsia region. Watch for further messages.#Vinnytsia_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 02:16:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:44 Air alarm to the Khmelnytsky region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132622</link><description>游댮 03:44 Air alarm to the Khmelnytsky region follow the following messages.#Khmelnitskaya This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 01:44:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:22 Drive alarm to the Kiev region. Stop by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132621</link><description>游릭 03:22 Drive alarm to the Kiev region. Stop by subsequent messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 01:22:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:22 Drive alarm to Uman District.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132620</link><description>游릭 03:22 Drive alarm to Uman District.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 01:22:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:08 Drive alarm to Zolotonsky District. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132619</link><description>游릭 03:08 Drive alarm to Zolotonsky District. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 01:08:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:08 Driven the alarm to Cherkasy district.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132618</link><description>游릭 03:08 Driven the alarm to Cherkasy district.Creck on further messages.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 01:08:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:08 Driven the anxiety in Zvenigorod district. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132617</link><description>游릭 03:08 Driven the anxiety in Zvenigorod district. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 01:08:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:00 pleasure in the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132616</link><description>游릭 03:00 pleasure in the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 01:00:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:43 Air anxiety in the Vinnytsia region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132615</link><description>游댮 02:43 Air anxiety in the Vinnytsia region follow the following messages.#Vinnytsia_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 00:43:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:41 Driven the alarm in Kyiv. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132614</link><description>游릭 02:41 Driven the alarm in Kyiv. Stop by further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 00:41:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:31 Dumping anxiety in the Vinnytsia region.Crete on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132613</link><description>游릭 02:31 Dumping anxiety in the Vinnytsia region.Crete on further messages.#Vinnytsia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 00:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:22 Air anxiety in the Vinnytsia region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132612</link><description>游댮 02:22 Air anxiety in the Vinnytsia region follow the following messages.#Vinnytsia_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 00:22:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:55 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132611</link><description>游릭 01:55 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 23:55:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:55 Dumping anxiety in the Odesa region. Follow the subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132610</link><description>游릭 01:55 Dumping anxiety in the Odesa region. Follow the subsequent messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 23:55:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:05 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132609</link><description>游댮 01:05 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 23:05:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:05 Air alarm in Zvenigorod district to care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132608</link><description>游댮 01:05 Air alarm in Zvenigorod district to care for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 23:05:49 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>