<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游리 23:39 Dumping anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151452</link><description>游리 23:39 Dumping anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 20:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:30 Fragrant anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151451</link><description>游릭 23:30 Fragrant anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 20:30:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:30 Done to Donetsk Oblast. Since Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151450</link><description>游릭 23:30 Done to Donetsk Oblast. Since Further Messages.#Donetsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 20:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:30 Fragrant anxiety in Pavlograd District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151449</link><description>游릭 23:30 Fragrant anxiety in Pavlograd District. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 20:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:27 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151448</link><description>游릭 23:27 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 20:27:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:14 Auxiliary in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151447</link><description>游릭 23:14 Auxiliary in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 20:14:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:14 Draw an alarm to the Zaporizhzhia region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151446</link><description>游릭 23:14 Draw an alarm to the Zaporizhzhia region. Since further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 20:14:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:44 Drawing anxiety in the Dnieper District. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151445</link><description>游릭 22:44 Drawing anxiety in the Dnieper District. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 19:44:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:43 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsk District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151444</link><description>游릭 22:43 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsk District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 19:43:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:41 Driven the alarm to the Poltava region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151443</link><description>游릭 22:41 Driven the alarm to the Poltava region. Since further reports.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 19:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:41 Driven the alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151442</link><description>游릭 22:41 Driven the alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 19:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:58 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151441</link><description>游댮 21:58 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 18:58:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:57 Air alarm to Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151440</link><description>游댮 21:57 Air alarm to Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.#Pavlograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 18:57:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:57 Air alarm in the Dnieper District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151439</link><description>游댮 21:57 Air alarm in the Dnieper District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 18:57:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:57 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsk District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151438</link><description>游댮 21:57 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsk District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 18:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 21:57 Flashing anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Manganese and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivska Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151437</link><description>游리 21:57 Flashing anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Manganese and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivska Territorial Community#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 18:57:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:55 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151436</link><description>游댮 21:55 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 18:55:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 21:50 pm alarm to the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151435</link><description>游릭 21:50 pm alarm to the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 18:50:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 21:50 pm alarm to the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151434</link><description>游릭 21:50 pm alarm to the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 18:50:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:38 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151433</link><description>游댮 21:38 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 18:38:36 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>