<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 11:58 PM threats of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150732</link><description>游릭 11:58 PM threats of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 08:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:58 Attention! Rap off the attack of drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150731</link><description>游릭 11:58 Attention! Rap off the attack of drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 08:58:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:52 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150730</link><description>游릭 11:52 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 08:52:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:51 Auxiliary in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150729</link><description>游릭 11:51 Auxiliary in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 08:52:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:51 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150728</link><description>游릭 11:51 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region. Since further reports.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 08:51:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:51 Drawing of anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150727</link><description>游리 11:51 Drawing of anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 08:51:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:51 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150726</link><description>游댮 11:51 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 08:51:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:51 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150725</link><description>游릭 11:51 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 08:51:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:51 plouting anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marhanetsky Territorial Community, Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150724</link><description>游리 11:51 plouting anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marhanetsky Territorial Community, Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 08:51:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:51 Driven the alarm to Cherkasy region.Creck on subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150723</link><description>游릭 11:51 Driven the alarm to Cherkasy region.Creck on subsequent messages.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 08:51:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:51 Driven to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150722</link><description>游릭 11:51 Driven to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 08:51:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:06 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150721</link><description>游 11:06 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 08:06:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:06 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150720</link><description>游댮 11:06 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 08:06:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:05 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Manganese territorial community artillery shelling. Walk to shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150719</link><description>游댮 11:05 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Manganese territorial community artillery shelling. Walk to shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 08:05:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:57 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150718</link><description>游댮 10:57 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 07:57:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:57 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150717</link><description>游댮 10:57 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 07:57:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:57 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150716</link><description>游댮 10:57 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 07:57:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:57 Air Alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150715</link><description>游댮 10:57 Air Alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Cherkasy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 07:57:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:56 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150714</link><description>游댮 10:56 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 07:56:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:51 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150713</link><description>游댮 10:51 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 07:51:22 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>