<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 11:27 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135313</link><description>游댮 11:27 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 08:27:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:08 PM threats of artobrats in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135312</link><description>游릭 10:08 PM threats of artobrats in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 07:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135311</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 07:00:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:50 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135310</link><description>游댮 09:50 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 06:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:49 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135309</link><description>游댮 09:49 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 06:49:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:42 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135308</link><description>游댮 09:42 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 06:42:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:26 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135307</link><description>游댮 09:26 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 06:26:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:20 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135306</link><description>游댮 09:20 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 06:20:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:47 Close the threat of Artobzhtill to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135305</link><description>游릭 08:47 Close the threat of Artobzhtill to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 05:47:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:47 Return the threat of artobrats in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135304</link><description>游릭 08:47 Return the threat of artobrats in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 05:47:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:02 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135303</link><description>游릭 07:02 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 04:02:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:40 Driven the threat of Artobstil to Pokrovskaya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135302</link><description>游릭 06:40 Driven the threat of Artobstil to Pokrovskaya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 03:40:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:31 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135301</link><description>游릭 06:31 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region. Since further messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 03:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:35 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135300</link><description>游릭 05:35 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 02:35:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:35 Driven anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135299</link><description>游릭 05:35 Driven anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 02:35:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:35 Return the threat of using Cabbaths The threat of application</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135298</link><description>游릭 05:35 Return the threat of using Cabbaths The threat of application This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 02:35:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:34 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135297</link><description>游리 05:34 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 02:34:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 04:44 Auxiliary in Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-mirovsk territorial community-Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivska Territorial Community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135296</link><description>游리 04:44 Auxiliary in Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-mirovsk territorial community-Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivska Territorial Community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 01:44:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:43 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135295</link><description>游릭 04:43 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 01:43:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:13 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135294</link><description>游댮 03:13 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 00:13:22 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>