<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>?</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151193</link><description>? This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 16:17:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 19:09 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151192</link><description>游릭 19:09 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 16:09:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:08 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151191</link><description>游댮 19:08 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 16:08:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 19:08 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151190</link><description>游릭 19:08 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 16:08:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:55 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151189</link><description>游릭 18:55 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 15:55:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 18:55 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151188</link><description>游리 18:55 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 15:55:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:25 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151187</link><description>游댮 18:25 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 15:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:19 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151186</link><description>游릭 18:19 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 15:19:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:19 WARNING! DRAWING OF DRONNESS</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151185</link><description>游릭 18:19 WARNING! DRAWING OF DRONNESS This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 15:19:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:18 Close the threat of Artobzhtlil to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151184</link><description>游릭 18:18 Close the threat of Artobzhtlil to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 15:18:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:00 Air anxiety in the Zaporizhzhia region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151183</link><description>游댮 18:00 Air anxiety in the Zaporizhzhia region follow the following messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 15:00:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 17:50 AM attack of drones, possible discharges of ammunition to the center</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151182</link><description>游 17:50 AM attack of drones, possible discharges of ammunition to the center This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 14:50:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 17:49 attack drones, possible discharges of ammunition district of the old part</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151181</link><description>游 17:49 attack drones, possible discharges of ammunition district of the old part #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 14:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:49 Threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151180</link><description>游댮 17:49 Threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 14:49:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:48 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151179</link><description>游릭 17:48 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 14:48:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:48 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast. Since Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151178</link><description>游릭 17:48 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast. Since Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 14:48:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:48 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151177</link><description>游릭 17:48 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District. Solve for further reports.#Pavlograd_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 14:48:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 17:47 Flashing of anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Pavlograd district-Sinelnikovsky rayon- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivska Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151176</link><description>游리 17:47 Flashing of anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Pavlograd district-Sinelnikovsky rayon- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivska Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk_Oblast. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 14:47:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 17:47 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151175</link><description>游리 17:47 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 14:47:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:36 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151174</link><description>游댮 17:36 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 14:36:55 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>