<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 10:16 Air alarm to Vinnytsia Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137096</link><description>游댮 10:16 Air alarm to Vinnytsia Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Vinnytsia_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 07:16:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:13 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137095</link><description>游댮 10:13 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 07:13:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:13 Air Alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137094</link><description>游댮 10:13 Air Alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Cherkasy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 07:13:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:13 Air Alarm to Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137093</link><description>游댮 10:13 Air Alarm to Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Chernihiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 07:13:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:13 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137092</link><description>游댮 10:13 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 07:13:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:13 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137091</link><description>游댮 10:13 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 07:13:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:13 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137090</link><description>游댮 10:13 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 07:13:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:13 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137089</link><description>游댮 10:13 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 07:13:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:13 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137088</link><description>游댮 10:13 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 07:13:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:12 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137087</link><description>游댮 10:12 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 07:12:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:12 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137086</link><description>游댮 10:12 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.#M_kiiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 07:12:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:59 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137085</link><description>游 09:59 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 06:59:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:48 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137084</link><description>游댮 09:48 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 06:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:43 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137083</link><description>游댮 09:43 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 06:43:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:38 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137082</link><description>游릭 09:38 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 06:38:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:08 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137081</link><description>游댮 09:08 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 06:08:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:06 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137080</link><description>游댮 09:06 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 06:06:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:48 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137079</link><description>游댮 08:48 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 05:48:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:42 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137078</link><description>游댮 08:42 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 05:42:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:57 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137077</link><description>游릭 06:57 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 03:57:06 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>