<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 16:34 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138154</link><description>游댮 16:34 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 13:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:28 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138153</link><description>游댮 16:28 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 13:28:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:27 Close the threat of artobustril in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138152</link><description>游릭 16:27 Close the threat of artobustril in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 13:27:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:22 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138151</link><description>游댮 16:22 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 13:22:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:05 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138150</link><description>游댮 16:05 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 13:05:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:02 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138149</link><description>游릭 16:02 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 13:02:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:59 Driven the alarm in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138148</link><description>游릭 15:59 Driven the alarm in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 12:59:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:59 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138147</link><description>游릭 15:59 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the following messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 12:59:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 15:59 Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-mirovskaya territorial community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138146</link><description>游리 15:59 Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-mirovskaya territorial community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 12:59:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:58 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138145</link><description>游릭 15:58 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 12:58:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:47 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138144</link><description>游댮 15:47 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 12:47:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:33 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138143</link><description>游댮 15:33 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 12:33:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:24 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138142</link><description>游댮 15:24 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 12:24:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:24 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138141</link><description>游댮 15:24 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 12:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:24 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138140</link><description>游댮 15:24 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 12:24:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:01 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138139</link><description>游댮 15:01 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 12:01:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:33 Driven your alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138138</link><description>游릭 14:33 Driven your alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 11:33:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>?</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138137</link><description>? This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 11:32:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 14:32 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138136</link><description>游리 14:32 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 11:32:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:32 Driven the anxiety in the Zhytomyr region. Stop by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138135</link><description>游릭 14:32 Driven the anxiety in the Zhytomyr region. Stop by subsequent messages.#Zhytomyr_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 11:32:18 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>