<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 21:11 The threat of shelling! Pokrovskaya territorial community is artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142347</link><description>游댮 21:11 The threat of shelling! Pokrovskaya territorial community is artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 18:11:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:59 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142346</link><description>游댮 20:59 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:59:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:57 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142345</link><description>游릭 20:57 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:57:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:57 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142344</link><description>游릭 20:57 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:57:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:55 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142343</link><description>游댮 20:55 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:55:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 20:27 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142342</link><description>游 20:27 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:27:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:27 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142341</link><description>游댮 20:27 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:27:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:13 The threat of shelling! The Chervonohrigor Territorial Community is now Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142340</link><description>游댮 20:13 The threat of shelling! The Chervonohrigor Territorial Community is now Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:13:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 20:13 Flashing anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Manganese and Marganets Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142339</link><description>游리 20:13 Flashing anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Manganese and Marganets Territorial Community#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:13:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:09 Fragrance in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142338</link><description>游릭 20:09 Fragrance in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:09 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142337</link><description>游릭 20:09 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the following messages.#Of Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:09:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:09 Driven the alarm to Ternopil region. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142336</link><description>游릭 20:09 Driven the alarm to Ternopil region. Salt for further messages.#Ternopil_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:09:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:09 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142335</link><description>游릭 20:09 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:09:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:09 Draw alarms to Lviv region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142334</link><description>游릭 20:09 Draw alarms to Lviv region. Since further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:09:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:09 Dumping anxiety in the Rivne region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142333</link><description>游릭 20:09 Dumping anxiety in the Rivne region.Creck on further messages.#Rivne_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:09:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:09 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142332</link><description>游릭 20:09 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:09:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:09 Driven the alarm to the Kiev region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142331</link><description>游릭 20:09 Driven the alarm to the Kiev region. Since further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:09:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:09 Dumping anxiety in the Khmelnytsky region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142330</link><description>游릭 20:09 Dumping anxiety in the Khmelnytsky region. Watch for further reports.#Khmelnitskaya This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:09:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:08 Driven Alarm to Transcarpathian Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142329</link><description>游릭 20:08 Driven Alarm to Transcarpathian Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Transcarpathian_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:08:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:08 Driven anxiety in the Ivano-Frankivsk region.Crete on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142328</link><description>游릭 20:08 Driven anxiety in the Ivano-Frankivsk region.Crete on further reports.#Ivano-Frankivsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:08:57 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>