<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 3</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130698</link><description>游 3 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 01:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:40 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130697</link><description>游댮 03:40 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 01:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:40 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130696</link><description>游댮 03:40 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 01:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:32 Air anxiety in Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130695</link><description>游댮 03:32 Air anxiety in Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kirovograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 01:32:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:29 Drive alarm to Vinnytsia region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130694</link><description>游릭 03:29 Drive alarm to Vinnytsia region. Watch for further messages.#Vinnytsia_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 01:29:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:27 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130693</link><description>游댮 03:27 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 01:27:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:26 Air alarm to Cherkasy district carefully monitored.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130692</link><description>游댮 03:26 Air alarm to Cherkasy district carefully monitored. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 01:26:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:22 Driven to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130691</link><description>游릭 03:22 Driven to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 01:22:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:21 Drive anxiety in the Uman District.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130690</link><description>游릭 03:21 Drive anxiety in the Uman District.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 01:21:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:20 Driven the alarm to the Chernihiv region.Creck on subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130689</link><description>游릭 03:20 Driven the alarm to the Chernihiv region.Creck on subsequent messages.#Chernihiv_e This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 01:20:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 03:11 Failure to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky Territorial Community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivska Territorial Community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130688</link><description>游리 03:11 Failure to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky Territorial Community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivska Territorial Community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 01:11:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:11 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130687</link><description>游릭 03:11 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 01:11:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:11 Driven the threat of shock bplas.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130686</link><description>游릭 03:11 Driven the threat of shock bplas. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 01:11:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 03:11 Alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130685</link><description>游리 03:11 Alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 01:11:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:56 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130684</link><description>游댮 02:56 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kirovograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 00:56:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:54 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130683</link><description>游댮 02:54 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 00:54:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:35 Failure to the Zvenigorod District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130682</link><description>游릭 02:35 Failure to the Zvenigorod District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 00:35:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:34 Driven the alarm in Kyiv. Investigate by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130681</link><description>游릭 02:34 Driven the alarm in Kyiv. Investigate by subsequent messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 00:34:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:34 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130680</link><description>游릭 02:34 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 00:34:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:33 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130679</link><description>游릭 02:33 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 00:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>