<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 06:12 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142562</link><description>游댮 06:12 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 03:12:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:07 Dumping anxiety in the Lviv region. Follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142561</link><description>游릭 06:07 Dumping anxiety in the Lviv region. Follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 03:07:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:54 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142560</link><description>游릭 05:54 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region. Watch for further messages.#Poltava_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 02:54:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:20 Air alarm to Lviv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142559</link><description>游댮 05:20 Air alarm to Lviv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Lviv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 02:20:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:15 Air anxiety in the Volyn Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142558</link><description>游댮 05:15 Air anxiety in the Volyn Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Volyn_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 02:15:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:07 Air alarm to Chernivtsi region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142557</link><description>游댮 05:07 Air alarm to Chernivtsi region follow the following messages.#Chernivtsi_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 02:07:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 04:42 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142556</link><description>游리 04:42 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 01:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:42 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142555</link><description>游릭 04:42 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 01:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:41 Air alarm to Ivano-Frankivsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142554</link><description>游댮 04:41 Air alarm to Ivano-Frankivsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Ivano-Frankivsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 01:41:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:18 Air anxiety in Ternopil Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142553</link><description>游댮 04:18 Air anxiety in Ternopil Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Ternopil_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 01:18:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:16 Air alarm to the Rivne region follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142552</link><description>游댮 04:16 Air alarm to the Rivne region follow further messages.#Rivne_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 01:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:38 Driven the anxiety in the Chernihiv region. Stop by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142551</link><description>游릭 03:38 Driven the anxiety in the Chernihiv region. Stop by subsequent messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 00:38:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:38 Driven the alarm in Kyiv. Investigate by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142550</link><description>游릭 03:38 Driven the alarm in Kyiv. Investigate by subsequent messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 00:38:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:20 Air alarm to the Khmelnytsky region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142549</link><description>游댮 03:20 Air alarm to the Khmelnytsky region follow the following messages.#Khmelnitskaya This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 00:20:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:19 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142548</link><description>游릭 03:19 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 00:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:06 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142547</link><description>游댮 03:06 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 00:06:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:02 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142546</link><description>游댮 03:02 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 00:02:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:39 Air anxiety in Vinnytsia Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142545</link><description>游댮 02:39 Air anxiety in Vinnytsia Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Vinnytsia_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 23:39:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:20 Air alarm to the Zhytomyr region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142544</link><description>游댮 02:20 Air alarm to the Zhytomyr region follow the following messages.#Zhytomyr_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 23:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:16 Air anxiety in the Uman District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142543</link><description>游댮 02:16 Air anxiety in the Uman District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 23:16:08 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>