<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 10:39 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138443</link><description>游댮 10:39 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 07:39:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:38 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138442</link><description>游댮 10:38 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 07:38:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:38 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138441</link><description>游댮 10:38 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow the following messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 07:38:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:35 Plowing the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138440</link><description>游릭 10:35 Plowing the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 07:35:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:35 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138439</link><description>游릭 10:35 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 07:35:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:31 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Manganese territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138438</link><description>游댮 10:31 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Manganese territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 07:31:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:26 Return the threat of Artobrytile to Chervonohrigorivska Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138437</link><description>游릭 10:26 Return the threat of Artobrytile to Chervonohrigorivska Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 07:26:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 10:16 Flowing anxiety in Kupyansky District.Plear attention, anxiety is still in:- Kharkiv region- Kupyansky district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138436</link><description>游리 10:16 Flowing anxiety in Kupyansky District.Plear attention, anxiety is still in:- Kharkiv region- Kupyansky district#Kupyansky_dist This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 07:16:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:15 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138435</link><description>游댮 10:15 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 07:15:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:14 Air alarm to Kupyansky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138434</link><description>游댮 10:14 Air alarm to Kupyansky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 07:14:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:59 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138433</link><description>游 09:59 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 06:59:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:55 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138432</link><description>游 09:55 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 06:55:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:43 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138431</link><description>游릭 09:43 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 06:43:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:43 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138430</link><description>游릭 09:43 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 06:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:40 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138429</link><description>游 09:40 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 06:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:39 Threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138428</link><description>游댮 09:39 Threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 06:39:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:22 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138427</link><description>游릭 09:22 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 06:22:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:22 Updbium attack Dronov-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138426</link><description>游릭 09:22 Updbium attack Dronov-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 06:22:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:15 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, stadium area</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138425</link><description>游 09:15 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, stadium area #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 06:15:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 09:08 Fragrant anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138424</link><description>游리 09:08 Fragrant anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 06:08:47 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>