<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>🟢 18:32 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147458</link><description>🟢 18:32 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:32:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟡 18:32 Flashing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147457</link><description>🟡 18:32 Flashing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:32:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 18:32 Drive alarm to Poltava region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147456</link><description>🟢 18:32 Drive alarm to Poltava region. Watch for further reports.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:32:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 18:27 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147455</link><description>🔴 18:27 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:27:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 18:27 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147454</link><description>🔴 18:27 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:27:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 18:27 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147453</link><description>🔴 18:27 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:27:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 18:08 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147452</link><description>🔴 18:08 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:08:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 17:37 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147451</link><description>🟢 17:37 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 14:37:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 17:28 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147450</link><description>🟢 17:28 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporozhye This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 14:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 17:19 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147449</link><description>🔴 17:19 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 14:19:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 17:00 pleasure anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147448</link><description>🟢 17:00 pleasure anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 14:00:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 16:51 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147447</link><description>🔴 16:51 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 13:51:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 16:47 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147446</link><description>🔴 16:47 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 13:47:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 16:19 Driven anxiety in Sinelnikov District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147445</link><description>🟢 16:19 Driven anxiety in Sinelnikov District. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 13:19:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 16:19 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147444</link><description>🟢 16:19 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 13:19:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 16:19 WARNING! DROPS DRONNES-KAMKADE!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147443</link><description>🟢 16:19 WARNING! DROPS DRONNES-KAMKADE! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 13:19:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 15:36 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin of the central market-old part</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147442</link><description>🟠 15:36 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin of the central market-old part #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 12:36:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 15:32 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin Old part</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147441</link><description>🟠 15:32 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin Old part#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 12:32:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 15:25 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147440</link><description>🔴 15:25 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 12:25:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 15:25 Attacks Dronnivsbros ammunition, the area of ​​the old part</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147439</link><description>🟠 15:25 Attacks Dronnivsbros ammunition, the area of ​​the old part #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 12:25:17 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>