<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 20:16 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133282</link><description>游댮 20:16 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 18:16:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:13 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133281</link><description>游댮 20:13 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 18:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:06 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133280</link><description>游댮 20:06 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 18:06:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 19:52 The threat of shock UAVs The threat of UAV type "Shahhed"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133279</link><description>游 19:52 The threat of shock UAVs The threat of UAV type "Shahhed"#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 17:52:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:51 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133278</link><description>游댮 19:51 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 17:51:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:51 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133277</link><description>游댮 19:51 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 17:51:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:51 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133276</link><description>游댮 19:51 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 17:51:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:58 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133275</link><description>游댮 18:58 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 16:58:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:58 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133274</link><description>游댮 18:58 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 16:58:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:10 Done alarms to Donetsk Region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133273</link><description>游릭 18:10 Done alarms to Donetsk Region. Watch for further messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 16:10:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:52 The threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133272</link><description>游댮 17:52 The threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 15:52:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 17:23 Drawing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133271</link><description>游리 17:23 Drawing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 15:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:07 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133270</link><description>游릭 17:07 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporozhye This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 15:07:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:04 Driven the threat of artebing to Pokrovskaya Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133269</link><description>游릭 17:04 Driven the threat of artebing to Pokrovskaya Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 15:04:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:04 The threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133268</link><description>游릭 17:04 The threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 15:04:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:59 threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133267</link><description>游댮 16:59 threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 14:59:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:46 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133266</link><description>游릭 16:46 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 14:46:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:45 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133265</link><description>游릭 16:45 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Stop by further messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 14:45:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 16:43 Drawing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganets Territorial Community- Pokrovskaya Territorial Community- Dnepropetrovsk.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133264</link><description>游리 16:43 Drawing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganets Territorial Community- Pokrovskaya Territorial Community- Dnepropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 14:43:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:40 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133263</link><description>游댮 16:40 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 14:40:40 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>