<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 11:41 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150993</link><description>游 11:41 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 08:41:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:41 Threat of Arteball! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150992</link><description>游댮 11:41 Threat of Arteball! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 08:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:33 Driven the anxiety in the Dnieper district.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150991</link><description>游릭 11:33 Driven the anxiety in the Dnieper district.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 08:33:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:30 plowing the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150990</link><description>游릭 11:30 plowing the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 08:30:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:27 Air alarm in the Dnieper District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150989</link><description>游댮 11:27 Air alarm in the Dnieper District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 08:27:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:23 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150988</link><description>游 11:23 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 08:23:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:21 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150987</link><description>游댮 11:21 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 08:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:18 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150986</link><description>游 11:18 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 08:18:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:13 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150985</link><description>游댮 11:13 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 08:13:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:10 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150984</link><description>游댮 11:10 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 08:10:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:06 Attack Dronov-Kamikadze type laS</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150983</link><description>游 11:06 Attack Dronov-Kamikadze type laS This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 08:06:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:05 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150982</link><description>游댮 11:05 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 08:05:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:49 threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150981</link><description>游댮 10:49 threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 07:49:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:48 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150980</link><description>游릭 10:48 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 07:48:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 10:47 pumping anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150979</link><description>游리 10:47 pumping anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 07:47:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:39 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150978</link><description>游릭 10:39 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 07:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:39 WARNING! DRAWING OF DRONNES</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150977</link><description>游릭 10:39 WARNING! DRAWING OF DRONNES #M_NIKOPOL_TA_NIKOPOLSKA This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 07:39:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:17 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150976</link><description>游댮 10:17 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 07:17:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:17 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city center</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150975</link><description>游 10:17 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city center #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 07:17:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:04 AM attack of drones, possible discharges of ammunition district of the old part</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150974</link><description>游 10:04 AM attack of drones, possible discharges of ammunition district of the old part #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial_ community This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 07:04:56 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>