<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 12:38 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153586</link><description>游릭 12:38 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 09:38:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:38 WARNING !!! DONE ASKRIGHT OF USEED AVIRTED AVIRT Bombs (Kabiv).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153585</link><description>游릭 12:38 WARNING !!! DONE ASKRIGHT OF USEED AVIRTED AVIRT Bombs (Kabiv). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 09:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:36 Failure to alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153584</link><description>游릭 12:36 Failure to alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 09:36:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:36 Logging the threat of using Cabbaths The threat of use</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153583</link><description>游릭 12:36 Logging the threat of using Cabbaths The threat of use This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 09:36:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:36 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153582</link><description>游리 12:36 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district#Zaporizhzhya_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 09:36:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:35 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153581</link><description>游리 12:35 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 09:35:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:35 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153580</link><description>游릭 12:35 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 09:35:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:33 Air alarm to Vinnytsia region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153579</link><description>游댮 12:33 Air alarm to Vinnytsia region follow the following messages.#Vinnytsia_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 09:33:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:17 Air alarm to the Volyn Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153578</link><description>游댮 12:17 Air alarm to the Volyn Oblast follow the following messages.#Volyn_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 09:17:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:13 Threat of use of the cope proportion of the use</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153577</link><description>游 12:13 Threat of use of the cope proportion of the use This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 09:13:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:13 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153576</link><description>游댮 12:13 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 09:13:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:12 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153575</link><description>游댮 12:12 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 09:12:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:48 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153574</link><description>游 11:48 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 08:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:47 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153573</link><description>游댮 11:47 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 08:47:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:47 Air alarm in Zvenigorod District Survene from further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153572</link><description>游댮 11:47 Air alarm in Zvenigorod District Survene from further messages.#Zvenigorod_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 08:47:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:37 Air alarm to the Rivne region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153571</link><description>游댮 11:37 Air alarm to the Rivne region follow the following messages.#Rivne_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 08:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:33 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153570</link><description>游릭 11:33 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region. Since further reports.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 08:33:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:32 Driven the alarm to the Poltava region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153569</link><description>游릭 11:32 Driven the alarm to the Poltava region. Since further reports.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 08:32:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:30 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153568</link><description>游댮 11:30 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 08:30:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:29 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153567</link><description>游릭 11:29 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 08:29:48 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>