<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 14:32 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154005</link><description>游댮 14:32 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 11:32:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>?</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154004</link><description>? This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 11:32:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:32 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154003</link><description>游릭 14:32 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 11:32:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:32 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154002</link><description>游릭 14:32 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 11:32:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:22 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze Attack, Knyazh District</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154001</link><description>游 14:22 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze Attack, Knyazh District #M_Nikopol_that_nikopol_ Tertorial_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 11:22:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:14 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154000</link><description>游릭 14:14 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 11:14:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:08 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin Novopavlivka</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153999</link><description>游 14:08 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin Novopavlivka #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 11:08:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:08 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153998</link><description>游댮 14:08 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 11:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:02 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153997</link><description>游댮 14:02 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 11:02:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:00 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153996</link><description>游 14:00 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 11:00:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:54 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153995</link><description>游댮 13:54 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 10:54:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:52 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153994</link><description>游릭 13:52 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 10:52:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:52 WARNING! DRAWE DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153993</link><description>游릭 13:52 WARNING! DRAWE DRONNES-Kamikadze #M_Nikopol_ti_nikopol_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 10:52:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:52 Return the threat of Artobstil to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153992</link><description>游릭 13:52 Return the threat of Artobstil to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 10:52:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:49 Driven the alarm to the Sumy region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153991</link><description>游릭 13:49 Driven the alarm to the Sumy region.Creat by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 10:49:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:27 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153990</link><description>游댮 13:27 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 10:27:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:18 Supervise threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153989</link><description>游릭 13:18 Supervise threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).#Pologovsky_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 10:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:18 Driven the anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153988</link><description>游릭 13:18 Driven the anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 10:18:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:18 Dreaming of anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153987</link><description>游릭 13:18 Dreaming of anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 10:18:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 13:18 Flowing anxiety in the Zaporizhzhia region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153986</link><description>游리 13:18 Flowing anxiety in the Zaporizhzhia region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district#Zaporizhzhya_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 10:18:06 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>