<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 00:50 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152577</link><description>游댮 00:50 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 21:50:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:50 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152576</link><description>游댮 00:50 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 21:50:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:47 Air anxiety in the Zhytomyr Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152575</link><description>游댮 00:47 Air anxiety in the Zhytomyr Oblast follow the following messages.#Zhytomyr_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 21:47:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:42 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152574</link><description>游댮 00:42 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 21:42:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:06 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152573</link><description>游댮 00:06 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 21:06:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:59 Air alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152572</link><description>游댮 23:59 Air alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.#Nikopol. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 20:59:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:59 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152571</link><description>游댮 23:59 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.#Kryvyi Rih Ri This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 20:59:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:59 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152570</link><description>游댮 23:59 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 20:59:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:46 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152569</link><description>游댮 23:46 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 20:46:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:20 Air alarm to Cherkasy district care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152568</link><description>游댮 23:20 Air alarm to Cherkasy district care for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 20:20:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:20 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152567</link><description>游댮 23:20 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 20:20:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 23:00 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152566</link><description>游 23:00 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 20:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:51 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152565</link><description>游릭 22:51 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 19:51:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:50 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152564</link><description>游댮 22:50 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 19:50:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:39 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152563</link><description>游릭 22:39 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 19:39:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:24 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152562</link><description>游댮 22:24 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 19:24:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:07 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152561</link><description>游릭 22:07 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Since further reports.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 19:07:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:07 Dumping anxiety in the Kiev region. Follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152560</link><description>游릭 22:07 Dumping anxiety in the Kiev region. Follow the following messages.#Kyiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 19:07:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 22:07 Alarm to the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kamyansky district- Novomoskovsky district- Dniprovsky district- Pavlograd district- Sinelnikovsky rayon- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community and Nikopol Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152559</link><description>游리 22:07 Alarm to the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kamyansky district- Novomoskovsky district- Dniprovsky district- Pavlograd district- Sinelnikovsky rayon- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community and Nikopol Territorial Community This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 19:07:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:07 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152558</link><description>游댮 22:07 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 19:07:06 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>