<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 17:48 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast. Since Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141129</link><description>游릭 17:48 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast. Since Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 14:48:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:48 Driven Alarm to the Chernihiv Oblast. Follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141128</link><description>游릭 17:48 Driven Alarm to the Chernihiv Oblast. Follow the following messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 14:48:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 17:45 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141127</link><description>游 17:45 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 14:45:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:45 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141126</link><description>游댮 17:45 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 14:45:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 17:42 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141125</link><description>游 17:42 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 14:42:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:34 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141124</link><description>游댮 17:34 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 14:34:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:33 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141123</link><description>游릭 17:33 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 14:33:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:16 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141122</link><description>游댮 17:16 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 14:16:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:14 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141121</link><description>游댮 17:14 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 14:14:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:14 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141120</link><description>游댮 17:14 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 14:14:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:14 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141119</link><description>游댮 17:14 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 14:14:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:51 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141118</link><description>游댮 16:51 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 13:51:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:26 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141117</link><description>游릭 16:26 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 13:26:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:26 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141116</link><description>游릭 16:26 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 13:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:21 Return the threat of Artobstil to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141115</link><description>游릭 16:21 Return the threat of Artobstil to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 13:21:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 15:58 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141114</link><description>游 15:58 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:58:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:48 Threat of Artbuster! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141113</link><description>游댮 15:48 Threat of Artbuster! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:48:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:18 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141112</link><description>游댮 15:18 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:18:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:47 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141111</link><description>游릭 14:47 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 11:47:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 14:47 Failure to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Manganese and Marganetsky Territorial Community, Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141110</link><description>游리 14:47 Failure to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Manganese and Marganetsky Territorial Community, Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 11:47:36 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>