<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 10:13 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152925</link><description>游댮 10:13 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 07:13:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:13 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152924</link><description>游댮 10:13 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 07:13:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:13 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152923</link><description>游댮 10:13 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kirovograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 07:13:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:13 Air alarm to the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152922</link><description>游댮 10:13 Air alarm to the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 07:13:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:13 Air Alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152921</link><description>游댮 10:13 Air Alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Cherkasy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 07:13:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:12 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152920</link><description>游댮 10:12 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 07:12:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:12 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152919</link><description>游댮 10:12 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 07:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:11 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152918</link><description>游댮 10:11 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 07:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152917</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 07:00:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:51 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152916</link><description>游댮 09:51 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 06:51:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:48 Drone Attack -Kamikadzerin Novopavlivka</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152915</link><description>游 09:48 Drone Attack -Kamikadzerin Novopavlivka#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 06:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:47 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152914</link><description>游댮 09:47 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 06:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:46 Air Alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152913</link><description>游댮 09:46 Air Alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.#Nikopol_ Region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 06:46:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:31 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152912</link><description>游댮 09:31 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 06:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:29 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152911</link><description>游댮 09:29 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 06:29:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:27 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152910</link><description>游댮 09:27 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 06:27:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:19 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152909</link><description>游릭 09:19 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 06:19:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:18 Driven Alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152908</link><description>游릭 09:18 Driven Alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 06:18:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:18 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152907</link><description>游릭 09:18 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 06:18:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:18 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152906</link><description>游릭 09:18 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 06:18:01 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>