<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 04:47 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139502</link><description>游댮 04:47 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 01:47:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:45 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139501</link><description>游릭 04:45 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 01:45:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:38 Drive alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139500</link><description>游릭 04:38 Drive alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 01:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:12 Driven the anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139499</link><description>游릭 04:12 Driven the anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 01:12:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:12 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139498</link><description>游릭 04:12 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 01:12:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:58 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139497</link><description>游릭 03:58 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 00:58:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:58 Run the threat of percussion Blividbium threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139496</link><description>游릭 03:58 Run the threat of percussion Blividbium threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 00:58:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:16 Drive alarm to the Zhytomyr region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139495</link><description>游릭 03:16 Drive alarm to the Zhytomyr region.Creck on further messages.#Zhytomyr This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 00:16:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:15 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139494</link><description>游릭 03:15 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 00:15:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 3</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139493</link><description>游릭 3 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 00:14:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:12 Air anxiety in the Uman District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139492</link><description>游댮 03:12 Air anxiety in the Uman District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 00:12:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:12 Air alarm in Zvenigorod District to care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139491</link><description>游댮 03:12 Air alarm in Zvenigorod District to care for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 00:12:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:48 Air anxiety in the Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139490</link><description>游댮 02:48 Air anxiety in the Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kirovograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 23:48:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:46 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139489</link><description>游댮 02:46 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 23:46:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:34 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139488</link><description>游댮 02:34 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 23:34:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:31 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139487</link><description>游댮 02:31 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 23:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:07 Air anxiety in the Zhytomyr Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139486</link><description>游댮 02:07 Air anxiety in the Zhytomyr Oblast follow the following messages.#Zhytomyr_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 23:07:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:39 Air anxiety in Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139485</link><description>游댮 01:39 Air anxiety in Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 22:39:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:39 Air anxiety in Cherkasy District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139484</link><description>游댮 01:39 Air anxiety in Cherkasy District Surveat for Further Messages.#Cherkasy_ Region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 22:39:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:28 Drive alarm to the Kiev region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139483</link><description>游릭 01:28 Drive alarm to the Kiev region. Since further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 22:28:37 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>