<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游리 00:48 Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Mirovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133537</link><description>游리 00:48 Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Mirovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 22:48:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:46 Driven anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133536</link><description>游릭 00:46 Driven anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 22:46:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:26 Air anxiety in the Vinnytsia region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133535</link><description>游댮 00:26 Air anxiety in the Vinnytsia region follow the following messages.#Vinnytsia_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 22:26:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:26 Air anxiety in the Zhytomyr Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133534</link><description>游댮 00:26 Air anxiety in the Zhytomyr Oblast follow the following messages.#Zhytomyr_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 22:26:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:54 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133533</link><description>游릭 23:54 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 21:54:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:44 Draw an alarm to the Zaporizhzhia region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133532</link><description>游릭 23:44 Draw an alarm to the Zaporizhzhia region. Since further messages.#Zaporizhzhia_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 21:44:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:44 Auxiliary in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133531</link><description>游릭 23:44 Auxiliary in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 21:44:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:43 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133530</link><description>游릭 23:43 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 21:43:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 23:43 Drawing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133529</link><description>游리 23:43 Drawing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 21:43:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:43 Run the threat of shock bplavidbium threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133528</link><description>游릭 23:43 Run the threat of shock bplavidbium threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 21:43:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:32 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133527</link><description>游댮 23:32 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 21:32:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:55 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133526</link><description>游댮 21:55 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 19:55:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:21 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133525</link><description>游댮 21:21 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 19:21:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:21 Air alarm in Zvenigorod district to care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133524</link><description>游댮 21:21 Air alarm in Zvenigorod district to care for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 19:21:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:10 Air alarm to the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133523</link><description>游댮 21:10 Air alarm to the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 19:10:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:02 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133522</link><description>游댮 21:02 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 19:02:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:50 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133521</link><description>游댮 20:50 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 18:50:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:42 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133520</link><description>游댮 20:42 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 18:42:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 20:41 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133519</link><description>游 20:41 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 18:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:41 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133518</link><description>游댮 20:41 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 18:41:38 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>