<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>?</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145132</link><description>? This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 11:29:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:20 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145131</link><description>游댮 14:20 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 11:20:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>?</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145130</link><description>? This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 11:04:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:02 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145129</link><description>游 14:02 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 11:02:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:50 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145128</link><description>游댮 13:50 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 10:50:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:47 The threat of shelling! Now in the Bilenkovsky territorial community artillery firing.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145127</link><description>游댮 13:47 The threat of shelling! Now in the Bilenkovsky territorial community artillery firing. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 10:47:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:39 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145126</link><description>游릭 13:39 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 10:39:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:39 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145125</link><description>游릭 13:39 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADze #M_Nikopol_ti_nikopol_ Territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 10:39:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 13:21 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack continues</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145124</link><description>游 13:21 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack continues This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 10:21:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:55 plout alarm to the Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145123</link><description>游릭 12:55 plout alarm to the Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 09:55:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:28 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145122</link><description>游 12:28 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 09:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:28 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145121</link><description>游댮 12:28 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 09:28:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:11 plout anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Crete on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145120</link><description>游릭 12:11 plout anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Crete on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 09:11:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:11 pm alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145119</link><description>游릭 12:11 pm alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 09:11:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:11 TRAVEL !!! Drive the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145118</link><description>游릭 12:11 TRAVEL !!! Drive the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 09:11:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:08 Clear the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145117</link><description>游릭 12:08 Clear the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 09:08:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:08 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145116</link><description>游릭 12:08 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 09:08:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:08 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145115</link><description>游릭 12:08 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 09:08:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:07 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145114</link><description>游리 12:07 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 09:07:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:46 Attention! Drone attack! Discharged explosive items! Be in shelters!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145113</link><description>游 11:46 Attention! Drone attack! Discharged explosive items! Be in shelters! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 08:46:12 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>