<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 10:51 Attack Dronov-Kamikadze type of port larde</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147764</link><description>游 10:51 Attack Dronov-Kamikadze type of port larde This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 07:51:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:46 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147763</link><description>游릭 10:46 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Since further reports.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 07:46:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:46 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147762</link><description>游릭 10:46 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 07:46:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:44 Attack Dronov-Kamikadze type prayer</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147761</link><description>游 10:44 Attack Dronov-Kamikadze type prayer This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 07:44:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:40 The threat of use of the cope proportion of the use</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147760</link><description>游 10:40 The threat of use of the cope proportion of the use This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 07:40:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:39 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147759</link><description>游댮 10:39 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 07:39:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:39 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147758</link><description>游댮 10:39 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 07:39:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:36 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147757</link><description>游댮 10:36 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 07:36:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:35 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147756</link><description>游댮 10:35 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 07:35:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:32 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh from the old part to the center</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147755</link><description>游 10:32 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh from the old part to the center #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 07:32:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:31 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147754</link><description>游댮 10:31 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 07:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:14 The threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147753</link><description>游릭 10:14 The threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 07:14:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:14 Attention! Sleep Dronov-Kamikadze's attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147752</link><description>游릭 10:14 Attention! Sleep Dronov-Kamikadze's attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 07:14:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147751</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 07:00:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 09:54 Alarm to Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lajpetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147750</link><description>游리 09:54 Alarm to Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lajpetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 06:54:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:54 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147749</link><description>游릭 09:54 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 06:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 9</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147748</link><description>游릭 9 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 06:54:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:38 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin Center city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147747</link><description>游 09:38 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin Center city #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 06:38:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:36 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147746</link><description>游댮 09:36 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 06:36:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:28 The threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147745</link><description>游 09:28 The threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 06:28:59 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>