<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 11:52 Air alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138464</link><description>游댮 11:52 Air alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Cherkasy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 08:52:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:49 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138463</link><description>游댮 11:49 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:49 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138462</link><description>游댮 11:49 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 08:49:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:49 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138461</link><description>游댮 11:49 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 08:49:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:49 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138460</link><description>游댮 11:49 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 08:49:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:49 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138459</link><description>游댮 11:49 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 08:49:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:49 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138458</link><description>游댮 11:49 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 08:49:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:48 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138457</link><description>游댮 11:48 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 08:48:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:47 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138456</link><description>游댮 11:47 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 08:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:47 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138455</link><description>游댮 11:47 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow the following messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 08:47:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:43 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138454</link><description>游댮 11:43 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 08:43:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:15 plout anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Manganese and Marganets Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138453</link><description>游리 11:15 plout anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Manganese and Marganets Territorial Community#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 08:15:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:15 Pleasure anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138452</link><description>游릭 11:15 Pleasure anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 08:15:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:15 Pleasure in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138451</link><description>游릭 11:15 Pleasure in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 08:15:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:09 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138450</link><description>游릭 11:09 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 08:09:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:09 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138449</link><description>游릭 11:09 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 08:09:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 10:58 pm a alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138448</link><description>游리 10:58 pm a alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 07:58:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:55 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138447</link><description>游댮 10:55 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 07:55:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:48 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138446</link><description>游댮 10:48 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 07:48:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:48 Air alarm to the Kherson region keep track of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138445</link><description>游댮 10:48 Air alarm to the Kherson region keep track of further messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 07:48:54 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>