<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 12:50 pm alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152753</link><description>游릭 12:50 pm alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 09:50:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:50 pm alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152752</link><description>游리 12:50 pm alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 09:50:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:07 Drone attack, scribbled lamp</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152751</link><description>游 12:07 Drone attack, scribbled lamp This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 09:07:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:02 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152750</link><description>游릭 12:02 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 09:02:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:59 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152749</link><description>游릭 11:59 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further reports.#Nikopol_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 08:59:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:59 Dumping anxiety in the Kryvyi Rih District. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152748</link><description>游릭 11:59 Dumping anxiety in the Kryvyi Rih District. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 08:59:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:59 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152747</link><description>游릭 11:59 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region.Creck on further messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 08:59:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:59 Dumping anxiety in Pavlograd District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152746</link><description>游릭 11:59 Dumping anxiety in Pavlograd District. Watch for further reports.#Pavlograd_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 08:59:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:59 alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152745</link><description>游릭 11:59 alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 08:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:59 Driven in the Dnieper District. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152744</link><description>游릭 11:59 Driven in the Dnieper District. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 08:59:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:59 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152743</link><description>游릭 11:59 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the following messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 08:59:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:59 Dumping anxiety in Novomoskovsk District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152742</link><description>游릭 11:59 Dumping anxiety in Novomoskovsk District. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 08:59:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:58 Driven Alarm to Kamyansky District.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152741</link><description>游릭 11:58 Driven Alarm to Kamyansky District.Creck on Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 08:58:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:51 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin Center city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152740</link><description>游 11:51 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin Center city #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 08:51:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:49 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152739</link><description>游 11:49 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 08:49:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:35 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152738</link><description>游댮 11:35 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 08:35:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:34 Air Alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152737</link><description>游댮 11:34 Air Alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.#Nikopol_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 08:34:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:34 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152736</link><description>游댮 11:34 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 08:34:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:34 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsk District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152735</link><description>游댮 11:34 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsk District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 08:34:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:34 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152734</link><description>游댮 11:34 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 08:34:02 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>