<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 16:55 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city center</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147176</link><description>游 16:55 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city center #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 13:55:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 16:53 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the old part</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147175</link><description>游 16:53 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the old part This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 13:53:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:53 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147174</link><description>游댮 16:53 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 13:53:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:40 Air anxiety in Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147173</link><description>游댮 16:40 Air anxiety in Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.#Pavlograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 13:40:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:38 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147172</link><description>游릭 16:38 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 13:38:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:38 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147171</link><description>游릭 16:38 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 13:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:30 Driven the alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147170</link><description>游릭 16:30 Driven the alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 13:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 16:29 Alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147169</link><description>游리 16:29 Alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 13:29:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:24 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147168</link><description>游릭 16:24 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 13:24:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:24 Drive the threat of using Cabbaths The threat of application</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147167</link><description>游릭 16:24 Drive the threat of using Cabbaths The threat of application This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 13:24:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 16:07 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147166</link><description>游 16:07 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 13:07:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 15:57 Attack drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147165</link><description>游 15:57 Attack drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 12:57:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:56 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147164</link><description>游댮 15:56 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 12:56:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 15:43 Threat of use of the CI threat of use of managed aviation bombs</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147163</link><description>游 15:43 Threat of use of the CI threat of use of managed aviation bombs This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 12:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:42 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147162</link><description>游댮 15:42 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 12:42:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:42 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147161</link><description>游댮 15:42 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 12:42:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 15:36 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147160</link><description>游리 15:36 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 12:36:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:31 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147159</link><description>游릭 15:31 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 12:31:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:31 WARNING.! Rap off the attacks of drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147158</link><description>游릭 15:31 WARNING.! Rap off the attacks of drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 12:31:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 15:21 Dronivok attack on the bakery, possible discharges of ammunition</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147157</link><description>游 15:21 Dronivok attack on the bakery, possible discharges of ammunition #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial_ community This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 12:21:23 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>