<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 21:46 Air alarm to the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149163</link><description>游댮 21:46 Air alarm to the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 18:46:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:44 Air alarm to Dniprovskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149162</link><description>游댮 21:44 Air alarm to Dniprovskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 18:44:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:44 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149161</link><description>游댮 21:44 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 18:44:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:31 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149160</link><description>游댮 21:31 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 18:31:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:30 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149159</link><description>游댮 21:30 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 18:30:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:17 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149158</link><description>游댮 21:17 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 18:17:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:04 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149157</link><description>游댮 21:04 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 18:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:59 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149156</link><description>游댮 20:59 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 17:59:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:53 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149155</link><description>游댮 20:53 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.#Kryvyi Rih Ri This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 17:53:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:52 Air alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149154</link><description>游댮 20:52 Air alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.#Nikopol_ Region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 17:52:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:29 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149153</link><description>游릭 20:29 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 17:29:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:03 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149152</link><description>游릭 20:03 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 17:03:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:03 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149151</link><description>游릭 20:03 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #M_Nikopol_ti_nikopol_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 17:03:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:19 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149150</link><description>游댮 19:19 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 16:19:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 19:17 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin Novopavlivka</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149149</link><description>游 19:17 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin Novopavlivka #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 16:17:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:17 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149148</link><description>游댮 19:17 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 16:17:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:52 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149147</link><description>游릭 18:52 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia Oblast.Creck on further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 15:52:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 18:52 Attention !!! Notice, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149146</link><description>游리 18:52 Attention !!! Notice, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya region#Pologovsky_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 15:52:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:52 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Crete on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149145</link><description>游릭 18:52 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Crete on further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 15:52:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:52 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149144</link><description>游릭 18:52 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 15:52:20 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>