<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游리 06:44 Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Manganese and Marganetsky territorial community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139166</link><description>游리 06:44 Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Manganese and Marganetsky territorial community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 03:44:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:43 Pleasure in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139165</link><description>游릭 06:43 Pleasure in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 03:43:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:43 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139164</link><description>游릭 06:43 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 03:43:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:42 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139163</link><description>游릭 06:42 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 03:42:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:42 Drive the threat of shock bplas.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139162</link><description>游릭 06:42 Drive the threat of shock bplas. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 03:42:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:42 Drive alarm to Poltava region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139161</link><description>游릭 06:42 Drive alarm to Poltava region. Watch for further reports.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 03:42:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 06:42 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139160</link><description>游리 06:42 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community#Kharkiv_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 03:42:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:59 The threat of a shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139159</link><description>游리 05:59 The threat of a shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 02:59:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:59 Attention! Note, anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139158</link><description>游리 05:59 Attention! Note, anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 02:59:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:23 Drive alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139157</link><description>游릭 05:23 Drive alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 02:23:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:50 A. Return to the Kiev region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139156</link><description>游릭 04:50 A. Return to the Kiev region. Since further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 01:50:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:19 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139155</link><description>游댮 04:19 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 01:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:19 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139154</link><description>游댮 04:19 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 01:19:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:54 Axiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139153</link><description>游릭 03:54 Axiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:54:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:54 Draw an alarm to Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139152</link><description>游릭 03:54 Draw an alarm to Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporozhye This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:54:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:53 Driven to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139151</link><description>游릭 03:53 Driven to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:53:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:53 Drive alarm to Cherkasy region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139150</link><description>游릭 03:53 Drive alarm to Cherkasy region. Watch for further messages.#Cherkasy_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:53:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 3</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139149</link><description>游릭 3 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:53:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:53 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139148</link><description>游릭 03:53 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:53:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:52 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139147</link><description>游릭 03:52 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:52:47 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>