<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 18:45 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136898</link><description>游댮 18:45 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 15:45:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:45 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136897</link><description>游댮 18:45 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 15:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:45 Air alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136896</link><description>游댮 18:45 Air alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Cherkasy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 15:45:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:45 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136895</link><description>游댮 18:45 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 15:45:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:45 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136894</link><description>游댮 18:45 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 15:45:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:45 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136893</link><description>游댮 18:45 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 15:45:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:45 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136892</link><description>游댮 18:45 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 15:45:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:45 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136891</link><description>游댮 18:45 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 15:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:44 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136890</link><description>游댮 18:44 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 15:44:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:44 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136889</link><description>游댮 18:44 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.#M_kiiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 15:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:36 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136888</link><description>游릭 18:36 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 15:36:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:03 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136887</link><description>游댮 18:03 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 15:03:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:54 Close the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136886</link><description>游릭 17:54 Close the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 14:54:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:52 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136885</link><description>游릭 17:52 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 14:52:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:11 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136884</link><description>游댮 17:11 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 14:11:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:37 Return of the threat of Artobstil to Chervonohrigorivska Territorial Community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136883</link><description>游릭 16:37 Return of the threat of Artobstil to Chervonohrigorivska Territorial Community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 13:37:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:35 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136882</link><description>游댮 16:35 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 13:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 16:35 The threat of use of the cope proportion of the use of managed aviation bombs</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136881</link><description>游 16:35 The threat of use of the cope proportion of the use of managed aviation bombs This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 13:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:35 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136880</link><description>游댮 16:35 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 13:35:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:24 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136879</link><description>游댮 16:24 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 13:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>