<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 14:48 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143523</link><description>游댮 14:48 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 11:48:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:35 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143522</link><description>游릭 14:35 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 11:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:35 WARNING! DROPS DRONNIA-KAMKADze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143521</link><description>游릭 14:35 WARNING! DROPS DRONNIA-KAMKADze #M_Nikopol_ti_nikopol_ Territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 11:35:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:28 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzeruch in the direction</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143520</link><description>游 14:28 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzeruch in the direction This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 11:28:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:20 Attack drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143519</link><description>游 14:20 Attack drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 11:20:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:15 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh in the direction</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143518</link><description>游 14:15 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh in the direction This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 11:15:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:15 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143517</link><description>游댮 14:15 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 11:15:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:14 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143516</link><description>游댮 14:14 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 11:14:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143515</link><description>游 14:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 11:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:56 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143514</link><description>游릭 13:56 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:56:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:56 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143513</link><description>游릭 13:56 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:56:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:42 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143512</link><description>游댮 13:42 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:42:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:41 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Crete on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143511</link><description>游릭 13:41 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Crete on further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:41:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:40 Driven anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143510</link><description>游릭 13:40 Driven anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:40:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:40 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143509</link><description>游릭 13:40 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Creat by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 13:29 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the old part</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143508</link><description>游 13:29 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the old part This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:29 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143507</link><description>游댮 13:29 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:29:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:07 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143506</link><description>游댮 13:07 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:07:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:56 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143505</link><description>游댮 12:56 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 09:56:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:54 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143504</link><description>游릭 12:54 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region. Since further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 09:54:58 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>