<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 12:13 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, traffic in the direction of Novopavlivka</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139428</link><description>游 12:13 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, traffic in the direction of Novopavlivka #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 09:13:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:05 Attention !!! Drives the threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139427</link><description>游릭 12:05 Attention !!! Drives the threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 09:05:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:05 WARNING !!! DONE ASKRIGHT ACCEPTED AVIRTEVER BOMB (Kabiv).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139426</link><description>游릭 12:05 WARNING !!! DONE ASKRIGHT ACCEPTED AVIRTEVER BOMB (Kabiv). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 09:05:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:05 Return the threat of arteblow to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139425</link><description>游릭 12:05 Return the threat of arteblow to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 09:05:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:03 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139424</link><description>游릭 12:03 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 09:03:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:03 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Cont attention, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district- Zaporizhzhya district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139423</link><description>游리 12:03 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Cont attention, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district- Zaporizhzhya district#Zaporizhzhya_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 09:03:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:55 attack Dronov-Kamikadze type laS</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139422</link><description>游 11:55 attack Dronov-Kamikadze type laS This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 08:55:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:50 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze Dronov-Type Type</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139421</link><description>游 11:50 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze Dronov-Type Type This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 08:50:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:50 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery firing.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139420</link><description>游댮 11:50 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery firing. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 08:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:50 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139419</link><description>游댮 11:50 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 08:50:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:40 PM threats of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139418</link><description>游릭 11:40 PM threats of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 08:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:40 WARNING! DROVIA DRONNE-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139417</link><description>游릭 11:40 WARNING! DROVIA DRONNE-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 08:40:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:33 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139416</link><description>游 11:33 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 08:33:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:31 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139415</link><description>游 11:31 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 08:31:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:30 A. Run in the Kherson region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139414</link><description>游릭 11:30 A. Run in the Kherson region. Watch for further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 08:30:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:21 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139413</link><description>游 11:21 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 08:21:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:19 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139412</link><description>游리 11:19 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 08:19:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:17 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139411</link><description>游릭 11:17 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 08:17:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:11 PM Dronov-Kamikadzerukh in the direction of city center</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139410</link><description>游 11:11 PM Dronov-Kamikadzerukh in the direction of city center #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 08:11:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:59 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze Attack continues</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139409</link><description>游 10:59 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze Attack continues This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 07:59:59 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>