<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 00:52 Air anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140225</link><description>游댮 00:52 Air anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 21:52:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:45 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140224</link><description>游릭 00:45 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 21:45:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:45 Failure to alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140223</link><description>游릭 00:45 Failure to alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 21:45:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:45 Driven anxiety in Cherkasy district.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140222</link><description>游릭 00:45 Driven anxiety in Cherkasy district.Creck on further reports.#Cherkasy_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 21:45:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:45 Driven anxiety in the Uman District. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140221</link><description>游릭 00:45 Driven anxiety in the Uman District. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 21:45:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:45 Failure to alarm in Zvenigorod district.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140220</link><description>游릭 00:45 Failure to alarm in Zvenigorod district.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 21:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:42 Threat of Artebating! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140219</link><description>游댮 00:42 Threat of Artebating! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 21:42:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:38 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Follow the subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140218</link><description>游릭 00:38 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Follow the subsequent messages.#Odessa_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 21:38:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:37 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140217</link><description>游릭 00:37 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 21:37:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:30 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140216</link><description>游댮 00:30 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 21:30:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:58 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140215</link><description>游댮 23:58 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 20:58:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 23:52 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140214</link><description>游리 23:52 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 20:52:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 23:25 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140213</link><description>游 23:25 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 20:25:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:24 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140212</link><description>游댮 23:24 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 20:24:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:13 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140211</link><description>游릭 23:13 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 20:13:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:12 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140210</link><description>游댮 23:12 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 20:12:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:12 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140209</link><description>游댮 23:12 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 20:12:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 23:02 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack continues</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140208</link><description>游 23:02 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack continues This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 20:02:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:57 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140207</link><description>游댮 22:57 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 19:57:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:52 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140206</link><description>游릭 22:52 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 19:52:18 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>