<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 22:16 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135059</link><description>游댮 22:16 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 19:16:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:54 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135058</link><description>游댮 21:54 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 18:54:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 21:28 Drive alarms in Cherkasy district. Stop after further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135057</link><description>游릭 21:28 Drive alarms in Cherkasy district. Stop after further messages.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 18:28:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 21:28 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creck on subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135056</link><description>游릭 21:28 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creck on subsequent messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 18:28:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:43 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135055</link><description>游댮 20:43 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 17:43:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:39 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135054</link><description>游댮 20:39 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 17:39:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:38 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135053</link><description>游댮 20:38 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 17:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:38 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135052</link><description>游댮 20:38 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 17:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:37 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135051</link><description>游댮 20:37 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 17:37:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 20:35 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135050</link><description>游 20:35 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_that_harkivskaya_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 17:35:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:34 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135049</link><description>游댮 20:34 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 17:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:34 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135048</link><description>游댮 20:34 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 17:34:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:23 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135047</link><description>游댮 20:23 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 17:23:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:56 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135046</link><description>游댮 19:56 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 16:56:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:56 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135045</link><description>游댮 19:56 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 16:56:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 19:44 The threat of artobrats in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Consider, alarm is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135044</link><description>游리 19:44 The threat of artobrats in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Consider, alarm is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region#M_MAMARANETS_AMA_AMA_AMACA_AMARGANETSKA This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 16:44:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 19:26 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135043</link><description>游리 19:26 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 16:26:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 19:20 Download anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135042</link><description>游릭 19:20 Download anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on subsequent messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 16:20:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 19:19 Driven anxiety in the Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135041</link><description>游릭 19:19 Driven anxiety in the Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 16:19:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:09 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135040</link><description>游댮 19:09 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 16:09:33 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>