<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 12:38 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146081</link><description>游릭 12:38 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 09:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:38 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146080</link><description>游릭 12:38 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #M_Nikopol_ti_nikopol_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 09:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:01 Attack drones-Kamikadzerukh in the direction of Novopavlivka</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146079</link><description>游 12:01 Attack drones-Kamikadzerukh in the direction of Novopavlivka #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 09:01:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:00 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146078</link><description>游 12:00 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 09:00:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:46 Auxiliary alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146077</link><description>游릭 11:46 Auxiliary alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:46:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:46 Show the threat of percussion bplavidbium threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146076</link><description>游릭 11:46 Show the threat of percussion bplavidbium threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:39 threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV indefinite type</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146075</link><description>游 11:39 threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV indefinite type#m_harkiv_that_tham_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:39:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:38 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146074</link><description>游댮 11:38 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:32 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh in the direction of Novopavlivka</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146073</link><description>游 11:32 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh in the direction of Novopavlivka #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:32:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:23 Attack of drones-camikadzenaprats of movement Novopavlivka</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146072</link><description>游 11:23 Attack of drones-camikadzenaprats of movement Novopavlivka#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:23:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:15 Failure to alarm to Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146071</link><description>游릭 11:15 Failure to alarm to Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:13 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh in the direction of Novopavlivka</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146070</link><description>游 11:13 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh in the direction of Novopavlivka #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:13:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:12 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146069</link><description>游 11:12 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:10 plout alarm to Sumy region. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146068</link><description>游릭 11:10 plout alarm to Sumy region. Stop by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:10:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:00 pm the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146067</link><description>游릭 11:00 pm the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:00:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:43 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146066</link><description>游릭 10:43 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 07:43:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 10:43 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetsky territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146065</link><description>游리 10:43 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetsky territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community#Kharkiv_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 07:43:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:41 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze Drone-Type</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146064</link><description>游 10:41 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze Drone-Type This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 07:41:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:32 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146063</link><description>游댮 10:32 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 07:32:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:27 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146062</link><description>游릭 10:27 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 07:27:05 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>