<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 18:07 The threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149920</link><description>游댮 18:07 The threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 15:07:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:03 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149919</link><description>游릭 18:03 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the following messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 15:03:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:03 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149918</link><description>游릭 18:03 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 15:03:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:31 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149917</link><description>游릭 17:31 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 14:31:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:29 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149916</link><description>游릭 17:29 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 14:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:29 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149915</link><description>游릭 17:29 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 14:29:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:29 Driven anxiety in the Odesa region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149914</link><description>游릭 17:29 Driven anxiety in the Odesa region. Watch for further messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 14:29:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:29 Driven to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149913</link><description>游릭 17:29 Driven to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 14:29:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:27 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149912</link><description>游릭 17:27 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 14:27:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:27 WARNING! DRAWE DRONNIA-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149911</link><description>游릭 17:27 WARNING! DRAWE DRONNIA-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 14:27:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:23 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149910</link><description>游릭 17:23 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Solve for further reports.#Nikopol_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 14:23:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:23 Driven anxiety in Kryvyi Rih District.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149909</link><description>游릭 17:23 Driven anxiety in Kryvyi Rih District.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 14:23:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:22 Driven the alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149908</link><description>游릭 17:22 Driven the alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 14:22:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:59 Air Alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149907</link><description>游댮 16:59 Air Alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.#Nikopol_ Region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 13:59:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:59 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149906</link><description>游댮 16:59 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 13:59:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:59 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149905</link><description>游댮 16:59 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.#Kryvyi Rih. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 13:59:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:59 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149904</link><description>游댮 16:59 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 13:59:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:59 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149903</link><description>游댮 16:59 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 13:59:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:49 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149902</link><description>游릭 16:49 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region. Since further reports.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 13:49:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:49 Dumping anxiety in the Kyiv region. Follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149901</link><description>游릭 16:49 Dumping anxiety in the Kyiv region. Follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 13:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>