<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 13:37 Driven an alarm to the Odesa region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149868</link><description>游릭 13:37 Driven an alarm to the Odesa region.Creat by further messages.#Odessa This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 10:37:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:20 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149867</link><description>游릭 13:20 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 10:20:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:20 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149866</link><description>游릭 13:20 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #M_Nikopol_ti_nikopol. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 10:20:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:11 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149865</link><description>游댮 13:11 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 10:11:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:22 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149864</link><description>游릭 12:22 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 09:22:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:21 Driven anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149863</link><description>游릭 12:21 Driven anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 09:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:40 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149862</link><description>游릭 11:40 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 08:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:40 pumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149861</link><description>游릭 11:40 pumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 08:40:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:38 Plow anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149860</link><description>游릭 11:38 Plow anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporozhye This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 08:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:38 A.c.38 Fault attention.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149859</link><description>游리 11:38 A.c.38 Fault attention. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 08:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:38 Pleasure in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149858</link><description>游릭 11:38 Pleasure in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 08:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:38 Redeem the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149857</link><description>游리 11:38 Redeem the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 08:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:38 Fragrance in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetsky territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149856</link><description>游리 11:38 Fragrance in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetsky territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 08:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:38 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149855</link><description>游릭 11:38 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 08:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:38 Driven the alarm to the Cherkasy region.Creat on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149854</link><description>游릭 11:38 Driven the alarm to the Cherkasy region.Creat on further messages.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 08:38:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:38 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149853</link><description>游릭 11:38 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 08:38:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:38 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149852</link><description>游릭 11:38 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region.Creck on further reports.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 08:38:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:36 Failure in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149851</link><description>游릭 11:36 Failure in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 08:36:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:27 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Follow the subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149850</link><description>游릭 11:27 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Follow the subsequent messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 08:27:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:27 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149849</link><description>游댮 11:27 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 08:27:20 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>