<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 11:45 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142451</link><description>游 11:45 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 08:45:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:45 threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142450</link><description>游댮 11:45 threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 08:45:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:21 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142449</link><description>游댮 11:21 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast follow the following messages.#Kharkiv_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 08:21:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:19 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142448</link><description>游릭 11:19 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 08:19:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:19 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142447</link><description>游릭 11:19 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #M_Nikopol_ti_nikopol_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 08:19:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:17 pumping anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142446</link><description>游리 11:17 pumping anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 08:17:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:29 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marhanetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142445</link><description>游댮 10:29 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marhanetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 07:29:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:26 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142444</link><description>游댮 10:26 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 07:26:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:02 The threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142443</link><description>游댮 10:02 The threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 07:02:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142442</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#KUDYANSKY This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 07:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:52 Return the threat of artobrats in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142441</link><description>游릭 09:52 Return the threat of artobrats in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 06:52:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 9</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142440</link><description>游 9 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 06:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:41 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142439</link><description>游댮 09:41 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 06:41:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:26 Return the threat of Artobstil to the Chervonohrigor territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142438</link><description>游릭 09:26 Return the threat of Artobstil to the Chervonohrigor territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 06:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:11 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142437</link><description>游댮 09:11 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 06:11:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:11 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142436</link><description>游댮 09:11 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 06:11:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:37 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142435</link><description>游댮 08:37 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 05:37:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:23 Return the threat of artobrats in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142434</link><description>游릭 08:23 Return the threat of artobrats in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 05:23:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:32 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142433</link><description>游릭 07:32 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 04:32:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:32 WARNING! DRAWE DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142432</link><description>游릭 07:32 WARNING! DRAWE DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 04:32:48 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>