<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 13:21 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135323</link><description>游댮 13:21 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 10:21:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:20 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135322</link><description>游댮 13:20 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 10:20:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:19 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135321</link><description>游댮 13:19 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 10:19:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:50 PM The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135320</link><description>游릭 12:50 PM The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 09:50:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:38 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135319</link><description>游댮 12:38 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 09:38:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:35 Driven anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135318</link><description>游릭 12:35 Driven anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 09:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:35 Failure to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganets Territorial Community- Mirorsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135317</link><description>游리 12:35 Failure to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganets Territorial Community- Mirorsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 09:35:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:35 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135316</link><description>游리 12:35 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 09:35:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:35 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135315</link><description>游릭 12:35 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 09:35:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:22 The threat of shelling! The Chervonohrigor Territorial Community is now Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135314</link><description>游댮 12:22 The threat of shelling! The Chervonohrigor Territorial Community is now Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 09:22:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:27 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135313</link><description>游댮 11:27 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 08:27:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:08 PM threats of artobrats in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135312</link><description>游릭 10:08 PM threats of artobrats in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 07:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135311</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 07:00:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:50 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135310</link><description>游댮 09:50 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 06:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:49 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135309</link><description>游댮 09:49 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 06:49:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:42 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135308</link><description>游댮 09:42 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 06:42:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:26 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135307</link><description>游댮 09:26 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 06:26:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:20 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135306</link><description>游댮 09:20 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 06:20:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:47 Close the threat of Artobzhtill to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135305</link><description>游릭 08:47 Close the threat of Artobzhtill to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 05:47:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:47 Return the threat of artobrats in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135304</link><description>游릭 08:47 Return the threat of artobrats in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 05:47:47 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>