<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 16:59 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150063</link><description>游 16:59 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 13:59:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:52 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150062</link><description>游릭 16:52 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Since further reports.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 13:52:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:49 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150061</link><description>游댮 16:49 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 13:49:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:48 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150060</link><description>游댮 16:48 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 13:48:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:43 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150059</link><description>游댮 16:43 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 13:43:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:39 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150058</link><description>游댮 16:39 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 13:39:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:32 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150057</link><description>游릭 16:32 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 13:32:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:32 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADE!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150056</link><description>游릭 16:32 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADE! #m_nikopol_tay_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 13:32:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 16:01 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on Novopavlivka</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150055</link><description>游 16:01 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on Novopavlivka #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 13:01:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:00 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150054</link><description>游댮 16:00 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 13:00:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:56 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150053</link><description>游릭 15:56 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 12:56:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:08 Driven the anxiety to the Odesa region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150052</link><description>游릭 15:08 Driven the anxiety to the Odesa region.Creck on further messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 12:08:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:07 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150051</link><description>游릭 15:07 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Watch for further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 12:07:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:06 Failure to alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150050</link><description>游릭 15:06 Failure to alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 12:06:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 15:06 Fragrant alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150049</link><description>游리 15:06 Fragrant alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 12:06:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:06 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150048</link><description>游릭 15:06 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 12:06:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:06 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150047</link><description>游릭 15:06 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporozhye This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 12:06:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:06 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Stop after further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150046</link><description>游릭 15:06 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Stop after further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 12:06:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:06 Flow to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150045</link><description>游릭 15:06 Flow to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 12:06:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:06 Driven the alarm to Cherkasy region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150044</link><description>游릭 15:06 Driven the alarm to Cherkasy region. Watch for further messages.#Cherkasy_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 12:06:01 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>