<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 12:28 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145122</link><description>游 12:28 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 09:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:28 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145121</link><description>游댮 12:28 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 09:28:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:11 pm alarm to Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145120</link><description>游릭 12:11 pm alarm to Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporozhye This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 09:11:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:11 pm alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145119</link><description>游릭 12:11 pm alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 09:11:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:11 TRAVEL !!! Drive the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145118</link><description>游릭 12:11 TRAVEL !!! Drive the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 09:11:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:08 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145117</link><description>游릭 12:08 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 09:08:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:08 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145116</link><description>游릭 12:08 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 09:08:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:08 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145115</link><description>游릭 12:08 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 09:08:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:07 Alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145114</link><description>游리 12:07 Alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 09:07:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:46 Attention! Drone attack! Discharged explosive items! Be in shelters!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145113</link><description>游 11:46 Attention! Drone attack! Discharged explosive items! Be in shelters! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 08:46:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:13 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145112</link><description>游 11:13 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 08:13:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:11 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145111</link><description>游댮 11:11 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 08:11:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:55 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145110</link><description>游댮 10:55 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 07:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:51 Attention! Drone attack! Perhaps discharges of explosive items!  Be in shelters!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145109</link><description>游 10:51 Attention! Drone attack! Perhaps discharges of explosive items!  Be in shelters! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 07:51:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:30 Fragrant anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145108</link><description>游릭 10:30 Fragrant anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 07:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:30 plowing anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145107</link><description>游릭 10:30 plowing anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on subsequent messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:29 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145106</link><description>游댮 10:29 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 07:29:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:27 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145105</link><description>游릭 10:27 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 07:27:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:27 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145104</link><description>游릭 10:27 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 07:27:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 10:26 Flashing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky Territorial Community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/145103</link><description>游리 10:26 Flashing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky Territorial Community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 07:26:35 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>