<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 23:18 Drive alarm to Vinnytsia region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127658</link><description>游릭 23:18 Drive alarm to Vinnytsia region. Watch for further messages.#Vinnytsia_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 21:18:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:18 Dumping anxiety in the Zhytomyr region.Crete on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127657</link><description>游릭 23:18 Dumping anxiety in the Zhytomyr region.Crete on further messages.#Zhytomyr This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 21:18:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:56 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127656</link><description>游댮 22:56 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 20:56:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:28 Air alarm to the Khmelnytsky region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127655</link><description>游댮 22:28 Air alarm to the Khmelnytsky region follow the following messages.#Khmelnitskaya This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 20:28:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 22:12 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kharkiv region- Kharkiv district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127654</link><description>游리 22:12 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kharkiv region- Kharkiv district#m_harkiv_tha_tha_harkivska_harkivska_Tharkivska_The community This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 20:12:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 22:11 The threat of percussion BLAZPLESS, anxiety is still in:- Kharkiv region- Kharkiv district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127653</link><description>游리 22:11 The threat of percussion BLAZPLESS, anxiety is still in:- Kharkiv region- Kharkiv district#m_harkiv_tha_tha_harkivskay This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 20:11:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:57 Air alarm to Vinnytsia region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127652</link><description>游댮 21:57 Air alarm to Vinnytsia region follow the following messages.#Vinnytsia_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 19:57:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 21:55 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127651</link><description>游 21:55 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 19:55:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:54 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127650</link><description>游댮 21:54 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 19:54:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:44 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127649</link><description>游댮 21:44 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 19:44:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:40 Air Alarm to Zhytomyr Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127648</link><description>游댮 21:40 Air Alarm to Zhytomyr Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zhytomyr_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 19:40:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:08 Air alarm in Zvenigorod district to care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127647</link><description>游댮 21:08 Air alarm in Zvenigorod district to care for further reports.#Zvenigorod_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 19:08:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:06 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127646</link><description>游댮 21:06 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kirovograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 19:06:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:54 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127645</link><description>游댮 20:54 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 18:54:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:46 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127644</link><description>游댮 20:46 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 18:46:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:45 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127643</link><description>游댮 20:45 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 18:45:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:36 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127642</link><description>游댮 20:36 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 18:36:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:31 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127641</link><description>游댮 20:31 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 18:31:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:20 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127640</link><description>游댮 20:20 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 18:20:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:19 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/127639</link><description>游댮 20:19 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 18:19:31 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>