<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 21:29 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138910</link><description>游댮 21:29 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:29:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:29 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138909</link><description>游댮 21:29 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:29:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:18 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138908</link><description>游댮 21:18 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:18:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:18 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138907</link><description>游댮 21:18 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:18:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:08 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138906</link><description>游댮 21:08 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:08:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:08 Air Air In Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138905</link><description>游댮 21:08 Air Air In Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 21:04 Auxiliary in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138904</link><description>游릭 21:04 Auxiliary in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:04:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 21:04 Show the threat of percussion bplavidbium threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138903</link><description>游릭 21:04 Show the threat of percussion bplavidbium threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:04:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 21:04 Auxiliary in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138902</link><description>游리 21:04 Auxiliary in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:04:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:43 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138901</link><description>游릭 20:43 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 17:43:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:31 The threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138900</link><description>游댮 20:31 The threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 17:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:13 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138899</link><description>游댮 20:13 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 17:13:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:57 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138898</link><description>游댮 19:57 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:57:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>?</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138897</link><description>? This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:55:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 19:55 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138896</link><description>游릭 19:55 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:55:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 19:35 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138895</link><description>游 19:35 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:35:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:35 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138894</link><description>游댮 19:35 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:35:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 19:25 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, OKKO traffic</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138893</link><description>游 19:25 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, OKKO traffic This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:25:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:24 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138892</link><description>游댮 19:24 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 19:11 Driven the threat of artebors in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138891</link><description>游릭 19:11 Driven the threat of artebors in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:11:28 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>