<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>🔴 21:13 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149941</link><description>🔴 21:13 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 18:13:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:12 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149940</link><description>🔴 21:12 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 18:12:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:11 Air alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149939</link><description>🔴 21:11 Air alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Cherkasy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 18:11:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:11 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149938</link><description>🔴 21:11 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 18:11:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:11 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149937</link><description>🔴 21:11 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 18:11:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 21:03 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149936</link><description>🟠 21:03 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_that_harkivskaya_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 18:03:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:03 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149935</link><description>🔴 21:03 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 18:03:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:03 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149934</link><description>🔴 21:03 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 18:03:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:02 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149933</link><description>🔴 21:02 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 18:02:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:01 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149932</link><description>🔴 21:01 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.#Kryvyi Rih. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 18:01:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:01 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149931</link><description>🔴 21:01 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 18:01:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 20:59 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149930</link><description>🔴 20:59 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 17:59:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 20:44 Air alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149929</link><description>🔴 20:44 Air alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.#Nikopol. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 17:44:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 20:44 Air alarm to Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149928</link><description>🔴 20:44 Air alarm to Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.#Pavlograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 17:44:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 20:43 Air alarm in the Dnieper District care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149927</link><description>🔴 20:43 Air alarm in the Dnieper District care for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 17:43:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 20:43 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsk District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149926</link><description>🔴 20:43 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsk District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 17:43:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 20:43 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149925</link><description>🔴 20:43 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 17:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 20:18 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149924</link><description>🔴 20:18 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 17:18:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 20:13 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149923</link><description>🔴 20:13 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 17:13:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 20:13 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149922</link><description>🔴 20:13 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 17:13:19 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>