<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 08:22 Run the threat of artebing in Marganets and Marhanetsky territorial community. Solve by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153719</link><description>游릭 08:22 Run the threat of artebing in Marganets and Marhanetsky territorial community. Solve by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 05:22:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:07 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153718</link><description>游댮 08:07 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 05:07:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:02 Return the threat of arteblow to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153717</link><description>游릭 08:02 Return the threat of arteblow to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 05:02:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:56 Air alarm to Cherkasy district observe further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153716</link><description>游댮 07:56 Air alarm to Cherkasy district observe further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 04:56:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:56 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153715</link><description>游댮 07:56 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 04:56:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:49 Air anxiety in the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153714</link><description>游댮 07:49 Air anxiety in the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 04:49:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:42 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153713</link><description>游댮 07:42 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 04:42:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:39 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153712</link><description>游릭 07:39 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region. Since further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 04:39:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:38 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153711</link><description>游릭 07:38 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 04:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:38 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153710</link><description>游릭 07:38 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District. Watch for further reports.#Pavlograd_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 04:38:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 07:38 PM Anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153709</link><description>游리 07:38 PM Anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 04:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:13 Air anxiety in the Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153708</link><description>游댮 07:13 Air anxiety in the Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Chernihiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 04:13:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:08 Auxiliary alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153707</link><description>游릭 07:08 Auxiliary alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 04:08:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:08 Driven the threat of percussion UAVs the threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153706</link><description>游릭 07:08 Driven the threat of percussion UAVs the threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 04:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:08 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153705</link><description>游릭 07:08 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 04:08:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:53 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153704</link><description>游릭 06:53 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 03:53:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:49 Driven the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153703</link><description>游릭 06:49 Driven the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 03:49:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:26 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153702</link><description>游댮 05:26 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 02:26:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:25 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153701</link><description>游댮 05:25 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporozhye_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 02:25:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 05:17 The threat of shock bplasagrasis of percussion UAV</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153700</link><description>游 05:17 The threat of shock bplasagrasis of percussion UAV#M_Kharkiv_tha_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 02:17:41 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>