<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 06:02 Drive alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creach for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149043</link><description>游릭 06:02 Drive alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creach for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 03:02:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:02 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149042</link><description>游릭 06:02 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 03:02:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 06:02 Fragrant anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149041</link><description>游리 06:02 Fragrant anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community#Kharkiv_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 03:02:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:02 Return the threat of use of the threat of use of the use</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149040</link><description>游릭 06:02 Return the threat of use of the threat of use of the use This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 03:02:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 04:53 The threat of use of the cope proportion of the use</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149039</link><description>游 04:53 The threat of use of the cope proportion of the use This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 01:53:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:53 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149038</link><description>游댮 04:53 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 01:53:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:11 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149037</link><description>游댮 04:11 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 01:11:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:01 Air anxiety in Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149036</link><description>游댮 04:01 Air anxiety in Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 01:01:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:57 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Posts.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149035</link><description>游댮 03:57 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Posts. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 00:57:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:44 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149034</link><description>游릭 03:44 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 00:44:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:44 Drive the threat of shock Blividbium threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149033</link><description>游릭 03:44 Drive the threat of shock Blividbium threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 00:44:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:43 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149032</link><description>游릭 03:43 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 00:43:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 03:43 Drawing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149031</link><description>游리 03:43 Drawing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community#Kharkiv_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 00:43:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:29 Drive anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149030</link><description>游릭 02:29 Drive anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 23:29:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:29 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149029</link><description>游릭 02:29 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 23:29:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:29 Driven anxiety in the Dnieper district.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149028</link><description>游릭 02:29 Driven anxiety in the Dnieper district.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 23:29:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:28 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsky District. Stop after further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149027</link><description>游릭 02:28 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsky District. Stop after further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 23:28:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:28 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149026</link><description>游릭 02:28 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region. Since further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 23:28:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:28 Plowing of anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149025</link><description>游릭 02:28 Plowing of anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 23:28:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 02:14 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149024</link><description>游 02:14 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 23:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>