<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 06:55 Attention !!! Drive the threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148869</link><description>游릭 06:55 Attention !!! Drive the threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 03:55:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 06:54 Fragrant anxiety in the Zaporizhzhia region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148868</link><description>游리 06:54 Fragrant anxiety in the Zaporizhzhia region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district#Zaporizhzhia_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 03:54:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:50 pm a alarm to Sinelnikovsky district.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148867</link><description>游릭 06:50 pm a alarm to Sinelnikovsky district.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 03:50:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:50 pm a alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148866</link><description>游릭 06:50 pm a alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 03:50:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:43 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148865</link><description>游릭 06:43 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 03:43:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:43 Driven anxiety in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take the following reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148864</link><description>游릭 06:43 Driven anxiety in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take the following reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 03:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:43 Attention! Droze Dronov-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148863</link><description>游릭 06:43 Attention! Droze Dronov-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_ti_nikopol. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 03:43:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:09 Dumping anxiety in the Kiev region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148862</link><description>游릭 06:09 Dumping anxiety in the Kiev region. Since further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 03:09:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:08 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148861</link><description>游릭 06:08 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creat by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 03:08:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:08 Drive alarm to Cherkasy district.This followed by further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148860</link><description>游릭 06:08 Drive alarm to Cherkasy district.This followed by further reports.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 03:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:08 Alarm in Zvenigorod district. Stop after further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148859</link><description>游릭 06:08 Alarm in Zvenigorod district. Stop after further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 03:08:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:08 Drive alarm to the Poltava region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148858</link><description>游릭 06:08 Drive alarm to the Poltava region. Watch for further reports.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 03:08:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:08 Dumping anxiety in the Uman District.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148857</link><description>游릭 06:08 Dumping anxiety in the Uman District.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 03:08:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:08 Driven Alarm to Chernihiv Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148856</link><description>游릭 06:08 Driven Alarm to Chernihiv Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Chernihiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 03:08:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:06 Frame alarm in Kyiv. Investigate by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148855</link><description>游릭 06:06 Frame alarm in Kyiv. Investigate by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 03:06:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 06:03 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148854</link><description>游 06:03 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 03:03:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:56 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhia region follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148853</link><description>游댮 05:56 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhia region follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 02:56:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:28 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148852</link><description>游댮 05:28 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.#Sinelnikov. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 02:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:18 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148851</link><description>游릭 05:18 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Watch for further messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 02:18:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:16 Failure in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148850</link><description>游릭 05:16 Failure in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 02:16:13 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>