<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 13:26 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139436</link><description>游릭 13:26 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 10:26:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 13:22 Attack Dronov-Kamikadze type laS</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139435</link><description>游 13:22 Attack Dronov-Kamikadze type laS This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 10:22:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 13:17 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze Dronovian attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139434</link><description>游 13:17 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze Dronovian attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 10:17:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:17 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139433</link><description>游댮 13:17 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 10:17:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:11 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139432</link><description>游댮 13:11 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 10:11:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:49 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139431</link><description>游릭 12:49 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 09:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:49 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139430</link><description>游릭 12:49 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 09:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:41 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139429</link><description>游릭 12:41 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 09:41:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:13 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, traffic in the direction of Novopavlivka</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139428</link><description>游 12:13 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, traffic in the direction of Novopavlivka #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 09:13:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:05 Attention !!! Drives the threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139427</link><description>游릭 12:05 Attention !!! Drives the threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 09:05:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:05 WARNING !!! DONE ASKRIGHT ACCEPTED AVIRTEVER BOMB (Kabiv).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139426</link><description>游릭 12:05 WARNING !!! DONE ASKRIGHT ACCEPTED AVIRTEVER BOMB (Kabiv). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 09:05:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:05 Return the threat of arteblow to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139425</link><description>游릭 12:05 Return the threat of arteblow to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 09:05:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:03 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139424</link><description>游릭 12:03 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 09:03:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:03 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Cont attention, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district- Zaporizhzhya district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139423</link><description>游리 12:03 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Cont attention, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district- Zaporizhzhya district#Zaporizhzhya_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 09:03:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:55 attack Dronov-Kamikadze type laS</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139422</link><description>游 11:55 attack Dronov-Kamikadze type laS This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 08:55:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:50 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze Dronov-Type Type</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139421</link><description>游 11:50 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze Dronov-Type Type This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 08:50:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:50 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery firing.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139420</link><description>游댮 11:50 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery firing. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 08:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:50 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139419</link><description>游댮 11:50 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 08:50:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:40 PM threats of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139418</link><description>游릭 11:40 PM threats of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 08:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:40 WARNING! DROVIA DRONNE-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139417</link><description>游릭 11:40 WARNING! DROVIA DRONNE-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 08:40:03 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>