<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 23:45 Driven the alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141567</link><description>游릭 23:45 Driven the alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 20:45:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:21 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141566</link><description>游댮 23:21 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 20:21:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:15 Driven your alarm to Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141565</link><description>游릭 23:15 Driven your alarm to Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 20:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:07 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141564</link><description>游릭 23:07 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 20:07:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:34 Draw an alarm to the Zaporizhzhia region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141563</link><description>游릭 22:34 Draw an alarm to the Zaporizhzhia region. Since further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 19:34:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:34 Auxiliary in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141562</link><description>游릭 22:34 Auxiliary in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 19:34:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:34 Dumping anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141561</link><description>游릭 22:34 Dumping anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 19:34:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:59 Threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141560</link><description>游댮 21:59 Threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 18:59:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:42 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141559</link><description>游댮 21:42 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 18:42:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 21:42 Drawing of anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141558</link><description>游리 21:42 Drawing of anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 18:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 21:40 Driven Alarm to Kyiv Oblast. Since Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141557</link><description>游릭 21:40 Driven Alarm to Kyiv Oblast. Since Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 18:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 21:40 Driven Alarm to the Chernihiv Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141556</link><description>游릭 21:40 Driven Alarm to the Chernihiv Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 18:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 21:40 Auxiliary alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141555</link><description>游릭 21:40 Auxiliary alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 18:40:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 21:40 Auxiliary in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141554</link><description>游리 21:40 Auxiliary in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 18:40:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 21:40 Dumping anxiety in Cherkasy region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141553</link><description>游릭 21:40 Dumping anxiety in Cherkasy region. Since further messages.#Cherkasy_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 18:40:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 21:40 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141552</link><description>游릭 21:40 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Follow the following messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 18:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 21:40 Driven Alarm to Poltava Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141551</link><description>游릭 21:40 Driven Alarm to Poltava Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 18:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 21:38 Driven the alarm in Kyiv.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141550</link><description>游릭 21:38 Driven the alarm in Kyiv. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 18:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:14 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141549</link><description>游댮 21:14 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 18:14:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:14 Air alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141548</link><description>游댮 21:14 Air alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Cherkasy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 18:14:32 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>