<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 20:18 Driven your alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142856</link><description>游릭 20:18 Driven your alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on subsequent messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 17:18:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:55 Air Air In Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142855</link><description>游댮 19:55 Air Air In Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 16:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:37 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Crete on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142854</link><description>游릭 18:37 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Crete on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:37 Dumping anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142853</link><description>游릭 18:37 Dumping anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:36 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142852</link><description>游릭 18:36 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by subsequent messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:36:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:28 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142851</link><description>游릭 18:28 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:28:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:28 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142850</link><description>游릭 18:28 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:28:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 18:15 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142849</link><description>游 18:15 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:15:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:15 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142848</link><description>游댮 18:15 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:15:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:45 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142847</link><description>游댮 17:45 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:45:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:42 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Survene from further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142846</link><description>游댮 17:42 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Survene from further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:42:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:29 Driven in the Dnieper District. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142845</link><description>游릭 17:29 Driven in the Dnieper District. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:29:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:02 Air alarm to Donetsk Region Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142844</link><description>游댮 17:02 Air alarm to Donetsk Region Watch Further Messages.#Donetsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:02:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:58 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142843</link><description>游릭 16:58 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:58:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:57 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142842</link><description>游릭 16:57 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:57:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:55 Driven Alarm to Kamyansky District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142841</link><description>游릭 16:55 Driven Alarm to Kamyansky District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:55:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 15:54 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142840</link><description>游리 15:54 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 12:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:54 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142839</link><description>游릭 15:54 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 12:54:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:45 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142838</link><description>游댮 15:45 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 12:45:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:45 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142837</link><description>游댮 15:45 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 12:45:21 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>