<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 04:55 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153489</link><description>游댮 04:55 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 01:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:52 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153488</link><description>游릭 04:52 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 01:52:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:40 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153487</link><description>游댮 04:40 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 01:40:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:39 Driven anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153486</link><description>游릭 04:39 Driven anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 01:39:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:39 Drive anxiety in the Poltava region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153485</link><description>游릭 04:39 Drive anxiety in the Poltava region. Watch for further messages.#Poltava_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 01:39:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:42 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153484</link><description>游댮 03:42 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:42:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:40 Driven to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153483</link><description>游릭 03:40 Driven to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:39 Drive anxiety in the Vinnytsia region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153482</link><description>游릭 03:39 Drive anxiety in the Vinnytsia region. Watch for further messages.#Vinnytsia_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:39:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 3</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153481</link><description>游릭 3 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:36:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 03:35 Attention !!! Notice, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153480</link><description>游리 03:35 Attention !!! Notice, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya region#Vasylivsky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:35:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:35 Flowing anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153479</link><description>游릭 03:35 Flowing anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:35:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:35 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153478</link><description>游릭 03:35 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:35 Dumping anxiety in the Kryvyi Rih District. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153477</link><description>游릭 03:35 Dumping anxiety in the Kryvyi Rih District. Watch for further messages.#Kryvyi Rih district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:35:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:35 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153476</link><description>游릭 03:35 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:35:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:35 WARNING !!! Drive the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153475</link><description>游릭 03:35 WARNING !!! Drive the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:35:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:35 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd district.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153474</link><description>游릭 03:35 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd district.Creck on further reports.#Pavlograd_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:35:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:35 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153473</link><description>游릭 03:35 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:35:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:35 Return the threat of the use of cards of use of the use</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153472</link><description>游릭 03:35 Return the threat of the use of cards of use of the use This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:35:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:35 Driven anxiety in the Dnieper district.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153471</link><description>游릭 03:35 Driven anxiety in the Dnieper district.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:35:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:35 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsky District. Stop by further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153470</link><description>游릭 03:35 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsky District. Stop by further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>