<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游리 14:28 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Find out, the alarm is still in:- Nikopol district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152175</link><description>游리 14:28 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Find out, the alarm is still in:- Nikopol district#m_nikopol_that_nikopol. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 11:28:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 14:28 Attention! Please note that the alarm is still in:- Nikopol district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152174</link><description>游리 14:28 Attention! Please note that the alarm is still in:- Nikopol district#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 11:28:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:11 Drones attack, ammunition from the city center</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152173</link><description>游 14:11 Drones attack, ammunition from the city center #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 11:11:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:10 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152172</link><description>游댮 14:10 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 11:10:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:09 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152171</link><description>游댮 14:09 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 11:09:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:06 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152170</link><description>游 14:06 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 11:06:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:04 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152169</link><description>游댮 14:04 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 11:04:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:03 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152168</link><description>游댮 14:03 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 11:03:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:03 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152167</link><description>游댮 14:03 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 11:03:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:03 Air alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152166</link><description>游댮 14:03 Air alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.#Nikopol_ Region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 11:03:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:03 Air alarm to the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152165</link><description>游댮 14:03 Air alarm to the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 11:03:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:03 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152164</link><description>游댮 14:03 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 11:03:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:03 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152163</link><description>游댮 14:03 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 11:03:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:03 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152162</link><description>游댮 14:03 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.#Kryvyi Rih Ri This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 11:03:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:03 Air alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152161</link><description>游댮 14:03 Air alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Cherkasy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 11:03:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:03 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152160</link><description>游댮 14:03 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 11:03:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:03 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152159</link><description>游댮 14:03 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 11:03:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:03 Air alarm to Vinnytsia Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152158</link><description>游댮 14:03 Air alarm to Vinnytsia Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Vinnytsia_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 11:03:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:03 Air Alarm to Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152157</link><description>游댮 14:03 Air Alarm to Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.#Pavlograd_ Region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 11:03:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:03 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152156</link><description>游댮 14:03 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 11:03:15 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>