<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 21:42 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130222</link><description>游릭 21:42 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 19:42:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:37 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130221</link><description>游댮 21:37 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 19:37:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:35 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130220</link><description>游댮 21:35 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 19:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:35 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130219</link><description>游댮 21:35 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 19:35:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 21:22 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130218</link><description>游릭 21:22 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 19:22:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 21:22 Run the threat of shock bpadbius threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130217</link><description>游릭 21:22 Run the threat of shock bpadbius threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 19:22:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:02 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130216</link><description>游댮 21:02 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 19:02:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:01 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130215</link><description>游댮 21:01 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 19:01:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:50 Air alarm to the Nikolaev area follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130214</link><description>游댮 20:50 Air alarm to the Nikolaev area follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 18:50:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:48 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130213</link><description>游댮 20:48 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 18:48:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:48 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130212</link><description>游댮 20:48 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow the following messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 18:48:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:23 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130211</link><description>游댮 19:23 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 17:23:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:14 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130210</link><description>游댮 19:14 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 17:14:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 19:08 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130209</link><description>游 19:08 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 17:08:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:07 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130208</link><description>游댮 19:07 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 17:07:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:07 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130207</link><description>游댮 19:07 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 17:07:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:04 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130206</link><description>游댮 19:04 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 17:04:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:04 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130205</link><description>游릭 18:04 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 16:04:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 18:04 Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganets Territorial Community- March Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130204</link><description>游리 18:04 Alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganets Territorial Community- March Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 16:04:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:04 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Crete on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130203</link><description>游릭 18:04 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Crete on further messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 16:04:02 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>