<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 11:22 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135624</link><description>游댮 11:22 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 08:22:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:00 AM Threat of Artebating! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135623</link><description>游댮 11:00 AM Threat of Artebating! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 08:00:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 10:42 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135622</link><description>游리 10:42 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 07:42:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:18 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135621</link><description>游릭 10:18 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 07:18:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:08 plout alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135620</link><description>游릭 10:08 plout alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 07:08:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:08 punch alarm to Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135619</link><description>游릭 10:08 punch alarm to Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporozhye This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 07:08:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:08 Auxiliary alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135618</link><description>游릭 10:08 Auxiliary alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 07:08:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 10:08 pm a alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-mirorskaya territorial community-Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135617</link><description>游리 10:08 pm a alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-mirorskaya territorial community-Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 07:08:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:07 pumping anxiety in the Poltava region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135616</link><description>游릭 10:07 pumping anxiety in the Poltava region. Watch for further messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 07:07:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:02 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135615</link><description>游 10:02 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 07:02:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:48 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135614</link><description>游댮 09:48 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 06:48:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:48 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135613</link><description>游댮 09:48 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 06:48:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:48 Air anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135612</link><description>游댮 09:48 Air anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 06:48:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:42 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135611</link><description>游댮 09:42 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 06:42:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:42 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marhanetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk to shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135610</link><description>游댮 09:42 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marhanetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk to shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 06:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:42 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135609</link><description>游댮 09:42 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 06:42:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:24 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135608</link><description>游댮 09:24 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 06:24:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:24 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135607</link><description>游댮 09:24 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 06:24:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:22 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135606</link><description>游댮 09:22 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 06:22:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:19 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135605</link><description>游댮 09:19 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 06:19:43 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>