<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 09:12 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135445</link><description>游댮 09:12 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 06:12:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:11 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135444</link><description>游댮 09:11 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 06:11:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 07:40 Auxiliary alarm to Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135443</link><description>游리 07:40 Auxiliary alarm to Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 04:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:38 Auxiliary alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135442</link><description>游릭 07:38 Auxiliary alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 04:38:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:38 Drive the threat of shock Blividbium threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135441</link><description>游릭 07:38 Drive the threat of shock Blividbium threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 04:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 07:33 The threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135440</link><description>游 07:33 The threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 04:33:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:33 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135439</link><description>游댮 07:33 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 04:33:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:33 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135438</link><description>游댮 07:33 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 04:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:12 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135437</link><description>游릭 07:12 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 04:12:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:58 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast. Since Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135436</link><description>游릭 06:58 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast. Since Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 03:58:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:22 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135435</link><description>游릭 06:22 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 03:22:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:53 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135434</link><description>游릭 05:53 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 02:53:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:53 Return the threat of the use of cards of use of the use</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135433</link><description>游릭 05:53 Return the threat of the use of cards of use of the use This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 02:53:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:53 Driven anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135432</link><description>游리 05:53 Driven anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 02:53:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:52 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135431</link><description>游댮 05:52 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 02:52:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:36 Drive alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creach for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135430</link><description>游릭 05:36 Drive alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creach for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 02:36:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 04:44 The threat of use of the cope proportion of the use of managed aviation bombs</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135429</link><description>游 04:44 The threat of use of the cope proportion of the use of managed aviation bombs This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 01:44:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:43 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135428</link><description>游댮 04:43 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 01:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:43 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135427</link><description>游댮 04:43 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 01:43:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:18 Air anxiety in Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/135426</link><description>游댮 03:18 Air anxiety in Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 00:18:49 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>