<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 01:14 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139641</link><description>游댮 01:14 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 22:14:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 23:33 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139640</link><description>游 23:33 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_tha_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 20:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮33</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139639</link><description>游댮33 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 20:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮33</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139638</link><description>游댮33 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 20:33:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮33</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139637</link><description>游댮33 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 20:33:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:08 Draw alarm to Zaporizhzhya region. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139636</link><description>游릭 23:08 Draw alarm to Zaporizhzhya region. Stop by further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 20:08:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:08 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139635</link><description>游릭 23:08 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 20:08:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 23:08 Redeem the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139634</link><description>游리 23:08 Redeem the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 20:08:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:08 Driven the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139633</link><description>游릭 23:08 Driven the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 20:08:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:59 Threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139632</link><description>游댮 22:59 Threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 19:59:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 22:31 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139631</link><description>游리 22:31 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 19:31:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:31 Driven the alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139630</link><description>游릭 22:31 Driven the alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 19:31:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:31 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139629</link><description>游릭 22:31 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 19:31:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 22:25 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139628</link><description>游 22:25 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 19:25:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 22:25 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139627</link><description>游 22:25 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 19:25:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:23 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139626</link><description>游댮 22:23 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 19:23:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:19 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139625</link><description>游댮 22:19 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 19:19:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:54 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139624</link><description>游댮 21:54 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 18:54:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:49 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139623</link><description>游댮 21:49 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 18:49:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 21:37 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139622</link><description>游릭 21:37 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 18:37:20 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>