<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 09:48 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136162</link><description>游댮 09:48 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 06:48:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:28 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136161</link><description>游댮 09:28 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 06:28:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:26 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136160</link><description>游댮 09:26 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 06:26:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:19 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136159</link><description>游댮 09:19 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 06:19:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:52 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136158</link><description>游댮 08:52 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 05:52:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:49 Return the threat of artobrats in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136157</link><description>游릭 08:49 Return the threat of artobrats in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 05:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:46 Return the threat of artebors to the Mirovskaya Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136156</link><description>游릭 08:46 Return the threat of artebors to the Mirovskaya Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 05:46:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:33 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136155</link><description>游릭 08:33 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 05:33:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 08:31 Drawing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-mirorskaya territorial community-Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136154</link><description>游리 08:31 Drawing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-mirorskaya territorial community-Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 05:31:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:31 Driven anxiety in the Kiev region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136153</link><description>游릭 08:31 Driven anxiety in the Kiev region.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 05:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:31 Drive anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136152</link><description>游릭 08:31 Drive anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 05:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:31 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136151</link><description>游릭 08:31 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 05:31:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 08:31 Drawing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136150</link><description>游리 08:31 Drawing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community#Kharkiv_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 05:31:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:31 Driven an alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136149</link><description>游릭 08:31 Driven an alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 05:31:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:31 Drive anxiety in Zolotonsky District.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136148</link><description>游릭 08:31 Drive anxiety in Zolotonsky District.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 05:31:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:31 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136147</link><description>游릭 08:31 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 05:31:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:31 Driven anxiety in Poltava region.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136146</link><description>游릭 08:31 Driven anxiety in Poltava region.Creck on further reports.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 05:31:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:31 Drive anxiety in Cherkasy district.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136145</link><description>游릭 08:31 Drive anxiety in Cherkasy district.Creck on further messages.#Cherkasy_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 05:31:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:30 Fragrant anxiety in Kyiv. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136144</link><description>游릭 08:30 Fragrant anxiety in Kyiv. Salt for further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 05:30:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 08:11 Dumping anxiety in the Cherkasy region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Cherkasy district- Zolotonsky district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136143</link><description>游리 08:11 Dumping anxiety in the Cherkasy region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Cherkasy district- Zolotonsky district#Cherkasy_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 05:11:28 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>