<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 12:05 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140674</link><description>游댮 12:05 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast follow the following messages.#Kharkiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 09:05:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:59 Attack drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140673</link><description>游 11:59 Attack drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 08:59:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:58 pm alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140672</link><description>游리 11:58 pm alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 08:58:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:51 Attack drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140671</link><description>游 11:51 Attack drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 08:51:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:42 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140670</link><description>游 11:42 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 08:42:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:31 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140669</link><description>游댮 11:31 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 08:31:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:17 Auxiliary alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140668</link><description>游릭 11:17 Auxiliary alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 08:17:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:17 Reduce threatening Cabbaths The threat of application</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140667</link><description>游릭 11:17 Reduce threatening Cabbaths The threat of application This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 08:17:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:17 pumping anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140666</link><description>游리 11:17 pumping anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 08:17:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:16 Driven the alarm to the Sumy Oblast.Creck on subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140665</link><description>游릭 11:16 Driven the alarm to the Sumy Oblast.Creck on subsequent messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 08:16:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:12 Driven the threat of artebing to Pokrovskaya Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140664</link><description>游릭 11:12 Driven the threat of artebing to Pokrovskaya Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 08:12:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:12 Driven the alarm to Kryvyi Rih District. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140663</link><description>游릭 11:12 Driven the alarm to Kryvyi Rih District. Solve for further messages.#Kryvyi Rih_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 08:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:09 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140662</link><description>游 11:09 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 08:09:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:04 pumping anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140661</link><description>游릭 11:04 pumping anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 08:04:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:04 Dumping anxiety in the Odesa region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140660</link><description>游릭 11:04 Dumping anxiety in the Odesa region.Creck on further messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 08:04:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:04 pursuance of anxiety in the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140659</link><description>游릭 11:04 pursuance of anxiety in the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 08:04:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:57 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140658</link><description>游댮 10:57 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 07:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:52 The threat of use of the cope proportion of the use</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140657</link><description>游 10:52 The threat of use of the cope proportion of the use This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 07:52:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:52 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140656</link><description>游댮 10:52 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 07:52:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:51 attack drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140655</link><description>游 10:51 attack drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 07:51:47 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>