<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 18:47 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154460</link><description>游릭 18:47 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 15:47:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:47 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154459</link><description>游릭 18:47 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 15:47:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 18:25 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin Novopavlivka</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154458</link><description>游 18:25 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin Novopavlivka #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 15:25:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:25 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154457</link><description>游댮 18:25 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 15:25:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:20 Failure to alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154456</link><description>游릭 18:20 Failure to alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 15:20:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:20 Reduce threatening Cabbaths The threat of application</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154455</link><description>游릭 18:20 Reduce threatening Cabbaths The threat of application This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 15:20:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:16 WARNING !!! DONE ASKRIGHT OF USEED AVIRTED AVIRIA BOMB (Kabiv).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154454</link><description>游릭 18:16 WARNING !!! DONE ASKRIGHT OF USEED AVIRTED AVIRIA BOMB (Kabiv). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 15:16:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 18:15 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Cont attention, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154453</link><description>游리 18:15 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Cont attention, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district#Zaporizhzhya_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 15:15:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:15 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District to follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154452</link><description>游댮 18:15 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District to follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 15:15:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:15 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154451</link><description>游댮 18:15 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 15:15:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 17:55 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154450</link><description>游 17:55 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 14:55:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:49 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154449</link><description>游댮 17:49 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 14:49:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:47 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154448</link><description>游댮 17:47 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporozhye_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 14:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:47 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154447</link><description>游댮 17:47 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 14:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:40 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154446</link><description>游릭 17:40 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 14:40:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:39 WARNING! DRAWE DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154445</link><description>游릭 17:39 WARNING! DRAWE DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 14:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:22 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154444</link><description>游댮 17:22 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 14:22:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 17:00 The threat of use of the cope proportion of the use</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154443</link><description>游 17:00 The threat of use of the cope proportion of the use This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 14:00:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:59 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154442</link><description>游댮 16:59 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 13:59:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:56 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154441</link><description>游댮 16:56 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 13:56:34 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>