<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 16:46 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141621</link><description>游 16:46 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 13:46:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:45 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141620</link><description>游댮 16:45 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 13:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:27 Close the threat of artobustril in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141619</link><description>游릭 16:27 Close the threat of artobustril in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 13:27:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:27 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADE!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141618</link><description>游릭 16:27 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADE! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 13:27:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:19 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141617</link><description>游댮 16:19 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 13:19:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 16:06 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin OKKO</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141616</link><description>游 16:06 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin OKKO#M_NIKOPOL_TA_NIKOPOLSKA_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 13:06:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:36 Threat of Artbuster! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141615</link><description>游댮 15:36 Threat of Artbuster! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 12:36:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:14 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141614</link><description>游댮 15:14 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 12:14:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:54 Dumping anxiety in the Odesa region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141613</link><description>游릭 14:54 Dumping anxiety in the Odesa region. Watch for further messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 11:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:37 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141612</link><description>游댮 14:37 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 11:37:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:04 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141611</link><description>游댮 14:04 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 11:04:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:00 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141610</link><description>游 14:00 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 11:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:15 Reduce the threat of artebing in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141609</link><description>游릭 13:15 Reduce the threat of artebing in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 10:15:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:54 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141608</link><description>游릭 12:54 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 09:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:53 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creb</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141607</link><description>游릭 12:53 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creb This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 09:53:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:05 Threat of Artebil Still! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141606</link><description>游댮 12:05 Threat of Artebil Still! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 09:05:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:56 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141605</link><description>游댮 11:56 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 08:56:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:05 pumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141604</link><description>游릭 11:05 pumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region. Watch for further messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 08:05:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:04 A.c.04 Axiety</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141603</link><description>游리 11:04 A.c.04 Axiety This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 08:04:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:04 pumping anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141602</link><description>游릭 11:04 pumping anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 08:04:46 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>