<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 11:25 The threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142804</link><description>游릭 11:25 The threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:25 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142803</link><description>游릭 11:25 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:25:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:23 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142802</link><description>游릭 11:23 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:23:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:23 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142801</link><description>游릭 11:23 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Of Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:23:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:23 The threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142800</link><description>游리 11:23 The threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:04 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast. Since Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142799</link><description>游릭 11:04 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast. Since Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:04:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:57 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142798</link><description>游댮 10:57 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:57:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:48 WARNING !!! TAMINS OF USEED AVIRTED AVIRT BOMB (Kabiv).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142797</link><description>游 10:48 WARNING !!! TAMINS OF USEED AVIRTED AVIRT BOMB (Kabiv). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:48:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:46 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142796</link><description>游 10:46 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:46:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:45 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142795</link><description>游댮 10:45 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:45:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:37 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142794</link><description>游릭 10:37 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:37:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 10:37 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142793</link><description>游리 10:37 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:37:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:37 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142792</link><description>游릭 10:37 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the following messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:37:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:24 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142791</link><description>游댮 10:24 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:24:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:23 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142790</link><description>游댮 10:23 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:23:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:09 threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142789</link><description>游댮 10:09 threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:09:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:05 Plowing of the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142788</link><description>游릭 10:05 Plowing of the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:05:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:05 Attention! Rap off the attack of drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142787</link><description>游릭 10:05 Attention! Rap off the attack of drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:05:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142786</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#KUDYANSKY This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:50 Attack drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142785</link><description>游 09:50 Attack drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:50:25 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>