<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 11:20 Return of the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150525</link><description>游릭 11:20 Return of the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 08:20:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:20 WARNING! DRAWE DRONNES-Kamikadze attack!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150524</link><description>游릭 11:20 WARNING! DRAWE DRONNES-Kamikadze attack! #m_nikopol_tay_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 08:20:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:10 A.c.10 Flags attention.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150523</link><description>游리 11:10 A.c.10 Flags attention. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 08:10:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:05 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150522</link><description>游댮 11:05 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 08:05:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:02 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150521</link><description>游댮 11:02 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 08:02:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:57 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150520</link><description>游댮 10:57 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 07:57:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:39 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150519</link><description>游 10:39 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 07:39:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:26 Dronov-Kamikadze attack! Movement on the city!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150518</link><description>游 10:26 Dronov-Kamikadze attack! Movement on the city! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 07:26:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:26 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150517</link><description>游댮 10:26 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 07:26:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150516</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 07:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:56 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150515</link><description>游릭 09:56 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 06:56:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:48 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150514</link><description>游댮 09:48 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 06:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:13 Driven the threat of artobrats to the Chervonohrigor territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150513</link><description>游릭 09:13 Driven the threat of artobrats to the Chervonohrigor territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 06:13:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:12 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150512</link><description>游댮 09:12 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 06:12:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:03 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150511</link><description>游댮 09:03 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 06:03:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:21 Return the threat of artebors in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150510</link><description>游릭 08:21 Return the threat of artebors in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 05:21:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:25 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150509</link><description>游릭 07:25 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 04:25:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:20 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150508</link><description>游릭 07:20 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporozhye This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 04:20:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:20 Failure to alarm to Sinelnikov District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150507</link><description>游릭 07:20 Failure to alarm to Sinelnikov District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 04:20:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:05 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150506</link><description>游릭 07:05 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 04:05:03 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>