<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 20:10 plout alarm to Poltava region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141531</link><description>游릭 20:10 plout alarm to Poltava region. Since further reports.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 17:10:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:09 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141530</link><description>游릭 20:09 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 17:09:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 19:50 pm alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapets Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141529</link><description>游리 19:50 pm alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapets Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 16:50:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 19:32 Drive alarms in the Kiev region. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141528</link><description>游릭 19:32 Drive alarms in the Kiev region. Salt for further messages.#Kyiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 16:32:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 19:06 Driven the alarm to Kamyansky District. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141527</link><description>游릭 19:06 Driven the alarm to Kamyansky District. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 16:06:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 19:05 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creb</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141526</link><description>游릭 19:05 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creb This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 16:05:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 19:05 Driven anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141525</link><description>游릭 19:05 Driven anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 16:05:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 19:05 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141524</link><description>游릭 19:05 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporozhye This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 16:05:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>?</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141523</link><description>? This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 16:05:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:52 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141522</link><description>游릭 18:52 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 15:52:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:52 Run the threat of shock bplavidbium threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141521</link><description>游릭 18:52 Run the threat of shock bplavidbium threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 15:52:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:49 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141520</link><description>游댮 18:49 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 15:49:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 18:48 pumping anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kamyansky rayon-Sinelnikovsky rayon- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community- Chervono-Grigorivsk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141519</link><description>游리 18:48 pumping anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kamyansky rayon-Sinelnikovsky rayon- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community- Chervono-Grigorivsk Territorial Community#of Dnipropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 15:48:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:46 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141518</link><description>游댮 18:46 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 15:46:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 18:45 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District.Plear attention, anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141517</link><description>游리 18:45 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District.Plear attention, anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region#Pavlograd_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 15:45:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:42 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141516</link><description>游댮 18:42 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 15:42:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:36 Dumping anxiety in the Kiev region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141515</link><description>游릭 18:36 Dumping anxiety in the Kiev region. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 15:36:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:29 Air alarm in Zvenigorod district to care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141514</link><description>游댮 18:29 Air alarm in Zvenigorod district to care for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 15:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:22 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141513</link><description>游댮 18:22 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 15:22:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 18:12 The threat of a shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141512</link><description>游리 18:12 The threat of a shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 15:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>