<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 09:27 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143658</link><description>游댮 09:27 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 06:27:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:25 Driven the alarm to Poltava region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143657</link><description>游릭 09:25 Driven the alarm to Poltava region. Watch for further reports.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 06:25:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:22 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city center</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143656</link><description>游 09:22 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city center #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 06:22:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:13 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143655</link><description>游댮 09:13 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 06:13:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:01 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143654</link><description>游릭 09:01 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 06:01:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 08:58 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143653</link><description>游 08:58 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 05:58:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:58 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143652</link><description>游댮 08:58 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 05:58:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:44 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143651</link><description>游릭 08:44 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 05:44:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:40 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143650</link><description>游릭 08:40 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 05:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:39 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creat for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143649</link><description>游릭 08:39 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creat for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 05:39:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:36 Driven the anxiety in Kyiv. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143648</link><description>游릭 08:36 Driven the anxiety in Kyiv. Salt for further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 05:36:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:34 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143647</link><description>游댮 08:34 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 05:34:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:27 Drive alarm to Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143646</link><description>游릭 08:27 Drive alarm to Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 05:27:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:24 The threat of shelling in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Solid by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143645</link><description>游릭 08:24 The threat of shelling in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Solid by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 05:24:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:19 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143644</link><description>游댮 08:19 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 05:19:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:19 Air Alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143643</link><description>游댮 08:19 Air Alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 05:19:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:08 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143642</link><description>游댮 08:08 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 05:08:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:08 Air alarm in Zvenigorod district to care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143641</link><description>游댮 08:08 Air alarm in Zvenigorod district to care for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 05:08:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:47 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143640</link><description>游댮 07:47 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kirovograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 04:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:47 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143639</link><description>游릭 07:47 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 04:47:02 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>