<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>🔴 15:53 ​​Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130017</link><description>🔴 15:53 ​​Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 13:53:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 15:53 ​​Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130016</link><description>🔴 15:53 ​​Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 13:53:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 15:53 ​​Air Alarm to Poltava Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130015</link><description>🔴 15:53 ​​Air Alarm to Poltava Oblast Watch Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 13:53:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 15:52 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130014</link><description>🔴 15:52 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 13:52:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 15:28 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130013</link><description>🔴 15:28 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 13:28:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 15:14 Dumping anxiety in the Odesa region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130012</link><description>🟢 15:14 Dumping anxiety in the Odesa region. Watch for further messages.#Odessa_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 13:14:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 15:13 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130011</link><description>🔴 15:13 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 13:13:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 15:03 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130010</link><description>🟢 15:03 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 13:03:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟡 15:03 Failure to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Manganese and Marganetsky Territorial Community, Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Community Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130009</link><description>🟡 15:03 Failure to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Manganese and Marganetsky Territorial Community, Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Community Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 13:03:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 14:55 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130008</link><description>🔴 14:55 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 12:55:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 14:43 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Crete on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130007</link><description>🟢 14:43 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Crete on further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 12:43:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 14:42 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130006</link><description>🔴 14:42 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 12:42:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟡 14:28 The threat of a shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130005</link><description>🟡 14:28 The threat of a shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 12:28:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 14:27 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130004</link><description>🔴 14:27 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 12:27:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 14:13 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130003</link><description>🔴 14:13 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 12:13:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 14:05 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130002</link><description>🟠 14:05 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 12:05:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 13:54 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130001</link><description>🔴 13:54 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 11:54:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 13:50 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130000</link><description>🔴 13:50 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 11:50:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 13:30 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129999</link><description>🟢 13:30 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 11:30:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 13:09 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129998</link><description>🔴 13:09 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 11:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>