<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 11:38 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144206</link><description>游댮 11:38 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 08:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:37 Pleasure the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144205</link><description>游릭 11:37 Pleasure the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 08:37:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:34 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144204</link><description>游댮 11:34 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 08:34:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:30 AM ATTENTION! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144203</link><description>游 11:30 AM ATTENTION! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 08:30:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:30 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144202</link><description>游댮 11:30 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 08:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:28 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144201</link><description>游댮 11:28 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 08:28:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:21 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144200</link><description>游릭 11:21 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region.Creck on further messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 08:21:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:19 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144199</link><description>游릭 11:19 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 08:19:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:08 plouting anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144198</link><description>游리 11:08 plouting anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 08:08:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:05 plete anxiety in Novomoskovsk district. Stop after further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144197</link><description>游릭 11:05 plete anxiety in Novomoskovsk district. Stop after further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 08:05:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:05 Driven the alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144196</link><description>游릭 11:05 Driven the alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 08:05:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:04 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144195</link><description>游댮 11:04 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 08:04:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:54 pm threats of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144194</link><description>游릭 10:54 pm threats of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 07:54:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:54 Attention! Droze Dronov-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144193</link><description>游릭 10:54 Attention! Droze Dronov-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 07:54:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:34 Dumping anxiety in the Cherkasy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144192</link><description>游릭 10:34 Dumping anxiety in the Cherkasy region.Creck on further messages.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 07:34:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:34 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144191</link><description>游릭 10:34 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 07:34:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:32 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd district.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144190</link><description>游릭 10:32 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd district.Creck on further reports.#Pavlograd_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 07:32:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:29 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh in the direction of Novopavlivka</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144189</link><description>游 10:29 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh in the direction of Novopavlivka #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 07:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:29 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144188</link><description>游댮 10:29 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 07:29:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:28 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsk District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144187</link><description>游댮 10:28 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsk District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 07:28:55 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>