<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 22:16 Air alarm to Cherkasy district to care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149539</link><description>游댮 22:16 Air alarm to Cherkasy district to care for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 19:16:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:16 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149538</link><description>游댮 22:16 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 19:16:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:13 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149537</link><description>游댮 22:13 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 19:13:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:00 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149536</link><description>游댮 22:00 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 19:00:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 21:59 The threat of shock UAVs The threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149535</link><description>游 21:59 The threat of shock UAVs The threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 18:59:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:59 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149534</link><description>游댮 21:59 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 18:59:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:44 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149533</link><description>游댮 21:44 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 18:44:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:39 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149532</link><description>游댮 21:39 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 18:39:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:16 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149531</link><description>游댮 21:16 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 18:16:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:15 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149530</link><description>游댮 21:15 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 18:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 21:01 The threat of artobrats to Pokrovskaya territorial community. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Nikopol district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149529</link><description>游리 21:01 The threat of artobrats to Pokrovskaya territorial community. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Nikopol district#Pokrovskaya_ territorial_ community This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 18:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:00 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149528</link><description>游댮 21:00 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 18:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:40 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149527</link><description>游댮 20:40 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 17:40:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:40 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149526</link><description>游댮 20:40 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 17:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:40 Air alarm to Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149525</link><description>游댮 20:40 Air alarm to Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.#Pavlograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 17:40:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:39 Air anxiety in Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149524</link><description>游댮 20:39 Air anxiety in Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.#Kryvyi Rih Ri This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 17:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:38 Air alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149523</link><description>游댮 20:38 Air alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.#Nikopol_ Region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 17:38:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:36 Air alarm to Dniprovskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149522</link><description>游댮 20:36 Air alarm to Dniprovskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 17:36:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:24 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149521</link><description>游댮 20:24 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 17:24:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:11 Return the threat of artebors in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149520</link><description>游릭 20:11 Return the threat of artebors in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 17:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>