<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 15:33 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129605</link><description>游릭 15:33 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 13:33:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 15:10 PM Anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kharkiv district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129604</link><description>游리 15:10 PM Anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kharkiv district#m_harkiv_tha_tha_harkivska_Tharkivska_The community This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 13:10:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 15:09 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Kharkiv Territorial Community and Kharkiv Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129603</link><description>游리 15:09 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Kharkiv Territorial Community and Kharkiv Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 13:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:57 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129602</link><description>游댮 14:57 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 12:57:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:57 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129601</link><description>游댮 14:57 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 12:57:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:47 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129600</link><description>游댮 14:47 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 12:47:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:35 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129599</link><description>游댮 14:35 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 12:35:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:30 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. Walk to the shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129598</link><description>游댮 14:30 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. Walk to the shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 12:30:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:26 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129597</link><description>游댮 14:26 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 12:26:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:00 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129596</link><description>游 14:00 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 12:00:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:47 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129595</link><description>游릭 13:47 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 11:47:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:35 Driven the alarm to Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129594</link><description>游릭 13:35 Driven the alarm to Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 11:35:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:31 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129593</link><description>游릭 13:31 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region. Since further reports.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 11:31:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 13:30 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kharkiv district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129592</link><description>游리 13:30 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kharkiv district#m_harkiv_that_tha_harkivska_The. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 11:30:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 13:30 Alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district-Lipetsk territorial community- Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129591</link><description>游리 13:30 Alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district-Lipetsk territorial community- Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 11:30:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:30 Fragrant anxiety in the Poltava region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129590</link><description>游릭 13:30 Fragrant anxiety in the Poltava region.Creck on further messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 11:30:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:27 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129589</link><description>游댮 13:27 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 11:27:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:19 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129588</link><description>游릭 13:19 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 11:19:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:06 Air Alarm to Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129587</link><description>游댮 13:06 Air Alarm to Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Chernihiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 11:06:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:04 The threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129586</link><description>游릭 13:04 The threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 11:04:33 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>