<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 10:30 plowing anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139923</link><description>游릭 10:30 plowing anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 07:30:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:23 Attack of drones-camikadzethip Prayer, traffic in the direction of Novopavlivka</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139922</link><description>游 10:23 Attack of drones-camikadzethip Prayer, traffic in the direction of Novopavlivka #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial_ community This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 07:23:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:21 Attack Drones-Camikadzethip Pracement</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139921</link><description>游 10:21 Attack Drones-Camikadzethip Pracement This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 07:21:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:12 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139920</link><description>游댮 10:12 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 07:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:08 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, traffic to the city center</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139919</link><description>游 10:08 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, traffic to the city center #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 07:08:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:06 Frame alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139918</link><description>游릭 10:06 Frame alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 07:06:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:00</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139917</link><description>游릭 10:00 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 07:06:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:00 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139916</link><description>游댮 10:00 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 07:00:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:00 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139915</link><description>游댮 10:00 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 07:00:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139914</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 07:00:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:52 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139913</link><description>游 09:52 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 06:52:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:45 Attack drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139912</link><description>游 09:45 Attack drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 06:45:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:40 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139911</link><description>游 09:40 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 06:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:39 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139910</link><description>游댮 09:39 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 06:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:32 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139909</link><description>游댮 09:32 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 06:32:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:29 Driven the threat of artobrats to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139908</link><description>游릭 09:29 Driven the threat of artobrats to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 06:29:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:13 Air Alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139907</link><description>游댮 09:13 Air Alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 06:13:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:03 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139906</link><description>游릭 09:03 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 06:03:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:03 WARNING! DROVIKAGE CONDERMACK-KAMKADE</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139905</link><description>游릭 09:03 WARNING! DROVIKAGE CONDERMACK-KAMKADE #M_NIKOPOL_TA_NIKOPOLSKA_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 06:03:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:58 Threat of Artbill! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139904</link><description>游댮 08:58 Threat of Artbill! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 05:58:50 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>