<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 17:39 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153644</link><description>游릭 17:39 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 14:39:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:34 Driven the alarm in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153643</link><description>游릭 17:34 Driven the alarm in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 14:34:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:34 Draw an alarm to Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153642</link><description>游릭 17:34 Draw an alarm to Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporozhye This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 14:34:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 17:33 Flashing anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153641</link><description>游리 17:33 Flashing anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 14:33:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:33 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153640</link><description>游릭 17:33 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 14:33:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 17:32 Flashing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Sinelnikovsky rayon- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community- Pokrovsk territorial community- Chervonohrigor Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153639</link><description>游리 17:32 Flashing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Sinelnikovsky rayon- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community- Pokrovsk territorial community- Chervonohrigor Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 14:32:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:32 Driven Alarm to the Chernihiv Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153638</link><description>游릭 17:32 Driven Alarm to the Chernihiv Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 14:32:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:32 Driven the alarm to the Poltava region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153637</link><description>游릭 17:32 Driven the alarm to the Poltava region. Watch for further messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 14:32:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:24 Driven anxiety in Kyiv. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153636</link><description>游릭 17:24 Driven anxiety in Kyiv. Salt for further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 14:24:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:23 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153635</link><description>游릭 17:23 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 14:23:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:23 Driven the alarm to the Kiev region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153634</link><description>游릭 17:23 Driven the alarm to the Kiev region.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 14:23:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:23 Drive alarm to Cherkasy region. Follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153633</link><description>游릭 17:23 Drive alarm to Cherkasy region. Follow the following messages.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 14:23:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:13 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153632</link><description>游댮 17:13 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 14:13:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:12 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153631</link><description>游댮 17:12 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.#M_kiiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 14:12:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:11 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153630</link><description>游댮 17:11 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast follow the following messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 14:11:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:11 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153629</link><description>游댮 17:11 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 14:11:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:11 Air alarm to Cherkasy region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153628</link><description>游댮 17:11 Air alarm to Cherkasy region follow the following messages.#Cherkasy_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 14:11:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:11 Air alarm to the Zaporizhzhia region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153627</link><description>游댮 17:11 Air alarm to the Zaporizhzhia region follow the following messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 14:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:11 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153626</link><description>游댮 17:11 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 14:11:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:11 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153625</link><description>游댮 17:11 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 14:11:14 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>