<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 08:32 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129378</link><description>游댮 08:32 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 06:32:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:25 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129377</link><description>游릭 08:25 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 06:25:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:21 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129376</link><description>游댮 08:21 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 06:21:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:19 Threat of Artebric! Pokrovskaya Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129375</link><description>游댮 08:19 Threat of Artebric! Pokrovskaya Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 06:19:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:16 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129374</link><description>游댮 08:16 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 06:16:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:10 Fleet the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129373</link><description>游릭 08:10 Fleet the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 06:10:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:53 Air Alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129372</link><description>游댮 07:53 Air Alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 05:53:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:53 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129371</link><description>游댮 07:53 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 05:53:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:53 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129370</link><description>游댮 07:53 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 05:53:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:56 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129369</link><description>游댮 06:56 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 04:56:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:34 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129368</link><description>游릭 06:34 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 04:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:42 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129367</link><description>游릭 05:42 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 03:42:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:18 Drive alarm to the Kiev region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129366</link><description>游릭 05:18 Drive alarm to the Kiev region. Since further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 03:18:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:17 Drive alarms in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129365</link><description>游릭 05:17 Drive alarms in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 03:17:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:17 Dumping anxiety in the Zhytomyr region.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129364</link><description>游릭 05:17 Dumping anxiety in the Zhytomyr region.Creck on further reports.#Zhytomyr This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 03:17:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:17 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129363</link><description>游릭 05:17 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on subsequent messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 03:17:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:17 Drive alarm to Poltava region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129362</link><description>游릭 05:17 Drive alarm to Poltava region. Watch for further reports.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 03:17:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:17 Alarm to Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129361</link><description>游리 05:17 Alarm to Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 03:17:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:16 Frouping anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kharkiv region- Kharkiv district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129360</link><description>游리 05:16 Frouping anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kharkiv region- Kharkiv district#m_harkiv_tha_tha_harkivska_harkivska_harkivska_harkivska_harkiv. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 03:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:16 Driven the anxiety in Kyiv. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129359</link><description>游릭 05:16 Driven the anxiety in Kyiv. Salt for further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 03:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>