<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 23:48 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146631</link><description>游댮 23:48 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 20:48:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:42 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146630</link><description>游댮 23:42 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 20:42:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:42 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146629</link><description>游댮 23:42 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 20:42:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:25 Air alarm in Zvenigorod District to care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146628</link><description>游댮 23:25 Air alarm in Zvenigorod District to care for further reports.#Zvenigorod_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 20:25:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 23:03 The threat of shock UAVs The threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146627</link><description>游 23:03 The threat of shock UAVs The threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 20:03:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:01 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146626</link><description>游댮 23:01 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 20:01:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:50 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146625</link><description>游댮 22:50 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 19:50:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:49 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146624</link><description>游댮 22:49 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 19:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:49 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146623</link><description>游댮 22:49 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 19:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:49 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146622</link><description>游댮 22:49 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 19:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:34 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146621</link><description>游댮 22:34 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 19:34:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:29 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146620</link><description>游댮 22:29 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.#Kryvyi Rih Ri This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 19:29:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:17 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146619</link><description>游릭 22:17 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 19:17:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:17 Run the threat of shock bplavidbium threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146618</link><description>游릭 22:17 Run the threat of shock bplavidbium threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 19:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:12 Air Air Anxiety in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146617</link><description>游댮 22:12 Air Air Anxiety in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 19:12:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:57 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146616</link><description>游댮 21:57 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 18:57:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:46 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146615</link><description>游댮 21:46 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 18:46:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 21:05 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146614</link><description>游 21:05 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 18:05:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:05 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146613</link><description>游댮 21:05 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 18:05:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:54 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146612</link><description>游댮 20:54 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:54:57 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>