<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 07:55 Flowing anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147075</link><description>游릭 07:55 Flowing anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 04:55:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:55 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147074</link><description>游릭 07:55 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 04:55:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:54 Plow anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147073</link><description>游릭 07:54 Plow anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Stop by further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 04:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 07:54 Attention !!! Notice, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147072</link><description>游리 07:54 Attention !!! Notice, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya region#Pologovsky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 04:54:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:51 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147071</link><description>游릭 07:51 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 04:51:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:19 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147070</link><description>游댮 07:19 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 04:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:18 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147069</link><description>游릭 07:18 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 04:18:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 06:12 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147068</link><description>游 06:12 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 03:12:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:07 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147067</link><description>游댮 06:07 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 03:07:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:43 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147066</link><description>游릭 05:43 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 02:43:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:40 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147065</link><description>游릭 05:40 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 02:40:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:39 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147064</link><description>游릭 05:39 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Stop by further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 02:39:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:22 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147063</link><description>游댮 05:22 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 02:22:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:14 Air anxiety in Sinelnikov District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147062</link><description>游댮 05:14 Air anxiety in Sinelnikov District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 02:14:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:43 Driven anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147061</link><description>游릭 04:43 Driven anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 01:43:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:43 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147060</link><description>游릭 04:43 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 01:43:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:43 Return the threat of the use of cards the threat of use</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147059</link><description>游릭 04:43 Return the threat of the use of cards the threat of use This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 01:43:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 04:43 Flashing anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147058</link><description>游리 04:43 Flashing anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 01:43:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:26 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147057</link><description>游댮 04:26 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 01:26:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:25 Air anxiety in the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147056</link><description>游댮 04:25 Air anxiety in the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 01:25:51 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>