<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>🔴 22:58 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130668</link><description>🔴 22:58 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 20:58:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 22:58 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130667</link><description>🔴 22:58 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 20:58:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 22:24 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130666</link><description>🔴 22:24 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 20:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 22:24 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130665</link><description>🔴 22:24 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 20:24:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 21:51 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130664</link><description>🟠 21:51 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 19:51:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:51 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130663</link><description>🔴 21:51 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 19:51:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:46 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130662</link><description>🔴 21:46 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 19:46:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 21:31 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130661</link><description>🟢 21:31 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 19:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:29 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130660</link><description>🔴 21:29 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 19:29:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:29 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130659</link><description>🔴 21:29 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 19:29:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:01 The threat of shelling! The Chervono -Grigorivska Territorial Community is now Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130658</link><description>🔴 21:01 The threat of shelling! The Chervono -Grigorivska Territorial Community is now Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 19:01:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 20:54 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130657</link><description>🔴 20:54 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 18:54:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 20:44 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130656</link><description>🔴 20:44 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 18:44:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 20:39 Air anxiety in the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130655</link><description>🔴 20:39 Air anxiety in the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 18:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 20:38 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130654</link><description>🔴 20:38 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 18:38:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 20:30 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130653</link><description>🔴 20:30 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 18:30:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 19:56 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130652</link><description>🟠 19:56 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 17:56:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 19:56 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130651</link><description>🔴 19:56 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 17:56:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 19:44 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130650</link><description>🔴 19:44 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 17:44:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 19:25 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130649</link><description>🔴 19:25 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 17:25:52 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>