<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 10:17 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city center</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150175</link><description>游 10:17 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city center #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 07:17:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:17 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin Novopavlivka</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150174</link><description>游 10:17 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin Novopavlivka #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 07:17:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:15 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the old part</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150173</link><description>游 10:15 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the old part This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 07:15:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 Drone attack, ammunition from city center</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150172</link><description>游 10:00 Drone attack, ammunition from city center #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial_ community is possible This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 07:00:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150171</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 07:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:56 Driven anxiety in the Kiev region. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150170</link><description>游릭 09:56 Driven anxiety in the Kiev region. Stop by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 06:56:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:54 Close the threat of Artobstil to Pokrovskaya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150169</link><description>游릭 09:54 Close the threat of Artobstil to Pokrovskaya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 06:54:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:40 Attack drones, possible discharges of ammunition city center</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150168</link><description>游 09:40 Attack drones, possible discharges of ammunition city center #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 06:40:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:39 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150167</link><description>游댮 09:39 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 06:39:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:33 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150166</link><description>游댮 09:33 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 06:33:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:24 Close the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150165</link><description>游릭 09:24 Close the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 06:24:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:15 Failure of the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150164</link><description>游릭 09:15 Failure of the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 06:15:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:15 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150163</link><description>游릭 09:15 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 06:15:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:10 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150162</link><description>游댮 09:10 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 06:10:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:08 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150161</link><description>游댮 09:08 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 06:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:48 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150160</link><description>游릭 08:48 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region. Watch for further reports.#Poltava_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 05:48:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 08:47 Attack drones, discharges of ammunition center</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150159</link><description>游 08:47 Attack drones, discharges of ammunition center #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 05:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:47 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150158</link><description>游댮 08:47 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 05:47:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:39 Threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150157</link><description>游댮 08:39 Threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 05:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:27 Return the threat of artobstil in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Solid by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150156</link><description>游릭 08:27 Return the threat of artobstil in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Solid by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 05:27:59 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>