<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 10:01 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151540</link><description>游릭 10:01 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Of Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 07:01:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:01 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151539</link><description>游릭 10:01 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 07:01:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:01 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151538</link><description>游릭 10:01 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 07:01:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:00 WARNING! DRAWING OF DRONNESS</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151537</link><description>游릭 10:00 WARNING! DRAWING OF DRONNESS This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 07:00:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 10:00 pm alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivsk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151536</link><description>游리 10:00 pm alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivsk Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 07:00:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:59 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151535</link><description>游릭 09:59 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 06:59:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 09:59 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151534</link><description>游리 09:59 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 06:59:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:59 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151533</link><description>游릭 09:59 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 06:59:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:59 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151532</link><description>游릭 09:59 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 06:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:59 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151531</link><description>游 09:59 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#KUDYANSKY This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 06:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:59 Driven to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151530</link><description>游릭 09:59 Driven to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 06:59:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:59 Dumping anxiety in the Cherkasy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151529</link><description>游릭 09:59 Dumping anxiety in the Cherkasy region.Creck on further messages.#Cherkasy_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 06:59:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:59 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151528</link><description>游릭 09:59 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region. Watch for further reports.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 06:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 09:49 The threat of a shelling in Pokrovskaya territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151527</link><description>游리 09:49 The threat of a shelling in Pokrovskaya territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 06:49:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:33 Drone attack, the old part of the old part</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151526</link><description>游 09:33 Drone attack, the old part of the old part #m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_ territorial_ community is possible This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 06:33:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:32 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151525</link><description>游댮 09:32 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 06:32:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:12 Air anxiety in Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151524</link><description>游댮 09:12 Air anxiety in Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kirovograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 06:12:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:12 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151523</link><description>游댮 09:12 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 06:12:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:12 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151522</link><description>游댮 09:12 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 06:12:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:12 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151521</link><description>游댮 09:12 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 06:12:21 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>