<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 13:32 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133353</link><description>游댮 13:32 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:32:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:32 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133352</link><description>游댮 13:32 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kirovograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:32:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:32 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133351</link><description>游댮 13:32 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:32:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:32 Air Alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133350</link><description>游댮 13:32 Air Alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Cherkasy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:32:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 13:31 The threat of artobrats to Pokrovskaya territorial community. Considerates, anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133349</link><description>游리 13:31 The threat of artobrats to Pokrovskaya territorial community. Considerates, anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region#Pokrovskaya_T territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:31:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:30 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133348</link><description>游댮 13:30 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:30:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:30 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133347</link><description>游댮 13:30 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:30:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:30 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133346</link><description>游댮 13:30 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:30:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:29 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133345</link><description>游댮 13:29 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:29:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:28 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133344</link><description>游댮 13:28 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:28:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:28 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133343</link><description>游댮 13:28 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:28 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133342</link><description>游댮 13:28 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:28 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133341</link><description>游댮 13:28 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:28:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:24 Driven anxiety in the Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133340</link><description>游릭 13:24 Driven anxiety in the Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:24:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:49 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133339</link><description>游댮 12:49 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 10:49:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:13 Reduce the threat of Artobstil to the Mirovskaya Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133338</link><description>游릭 12:13 Reduce the threat of Artobstil to the Mirovskaya Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 10:13:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:48 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133337</link><description>游릭 11:48 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 09:48:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:42 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133336</link><description>游릭 11:42 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 09:42:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:41 Close the threat of Artobstil to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133335</link><description>游릭 11:41 Close the threat of Artobstil to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 09:41:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:25 Failure to alarm to the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133334</link><description>游릭 11:25 Failure to alarm to the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 09:25:21 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>