<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>?</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142959</link><description>? This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 11:04:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:02 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142958</link><description>游 14:02 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 11:02:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:46 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142957</link><description>游릭 13:46 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 10:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:27 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142956</link><description>游댮 13:27 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 10:27:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:17 Air alarm to the Donetsk region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142955</link><description>游댮 13:17 Air alarm to the Donetsk region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 10:17:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:11 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region.COC</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142954</link><description>游릭 13:11 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region.COC This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 10:11:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:10 Drawing anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142953</link><description>游릭 13:10 Drawing anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 10:10:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:10 Draw an alarm to Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142952</link><description>游릭 13:10 Draw an alarm to Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporozhye This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 10:10:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:58 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142951</link><description>游릭 12:58 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 09:58:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:53 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142950</link><description>游릭 12:53 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 09:53:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:38 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142949</link><description>游릭 12:38 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 09:38:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:35 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142948</link><description>游댮 12:35 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 09:35:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:35 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142947</link><description>游댮 12:35 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.#Sinelnikov. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 09:35:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:14 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142946</link><description>游댮 12:14 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 09:14:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:09 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142945</link><description>游댮 12:09 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 09:09:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:02 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142944</link><description>游댮 12:02 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 09:02:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 10:52 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetsky territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142943</link><description>游리 10:52 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetsky territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 07:52:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:52 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142942</link><description>游릭 10:52 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 07:52:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:21 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142941</link><description>游릭 10:21 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 07:21:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:21 Drive the threat of percussion bplavidbium threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142940</link><description>游릭 10:21 Drive the threat of percussion bplavidbium threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 07:21:45 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>