<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 03:19 Dumping anxiety in the Kyiv region. Further in further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131392</link><description>游릭 03:19 Dumping anxiety in the Kyiv region. Further in further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 01:19:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:04 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131391</link><description>游댮 03:04 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 01:04:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:01 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131390</link><description>游릭 03:01 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 01:01:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:01 WARNING !!! DONE ASKRIGHT OF USEED AVIRTED AVIRT BOMB (Kabiv).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131389</link><description>游릭 03:01 WARNING !!! DONE ASKRIGHT OF USEED AVIRTED AVIRT BOMB (Kabiv).#Zaporizhzhia. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 01:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:01 Driven the alarm to Sumy region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131388</link><description>游릭 03:01 Driven the alarm to Sumy region.Creat by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 01:01:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:00 plout alarm to Donetsk region. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131387</link><description>游릭 03:00 plout alarm to Donetsk region. Stop by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 01:00:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:52 Air anxiety in the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131386</link><description>游댮 02:52 Air anxiety in the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 00:52:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:44 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131385</link><description>游릭 02:44 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further reports.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 00:44:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:44 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Observe by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131384</link><description>游릭 02:44 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Observe by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 00:44:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:44 Driven anxiety in the Kherson region. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131383</link><description>游릭 02:44 Driven anxiety in the Kherson region. Stop by further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 00:44:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:43 Driven anxiety in the Kiev region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131382</link><description>游릭 02:43 Driven anxiety in the Kiev region.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 00:43:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:43 Driven the alarm in Kyiv. Investigate by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131381</link><description>游릭 02:43 Driven the alarm in Kyiv. Investigate by subsequent messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 00:43:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:59 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131380</link><description>游댮 01:59 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 23:59:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:59 Air alarm in Zvenigorod district to care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131379</link><description>游댮 01:59 Air alarm in Zvenigorod district to care for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 23:59:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:32 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131378</link><description>游댮 01:32 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 23:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:31 Air anxiety in the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131377</link><description>游댮 01:31 Air anxiety in the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 23:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:23 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131376</link><description>游댮 00:23 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kirovograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 22:23:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:22 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131375</link><description>游릭 23:22 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 21:22:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:20 Driven Alarm to Kherson Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131374</link><description>游릭 23:20 Driven Alarm to Kherson Oblast.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 21:20:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:20 The threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131373</link><description>游댮 23:20 The threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 21:20:02 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>