<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 08:24 The threat of shelling in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Solid by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149424</link><description>游릭 08:24 The threat of shelling in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Solid by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 05:24:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:31 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149423</link><description>游릭 07:31 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creat by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 04:31:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:24 Pleasure in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149422</link><description>游릭 07:24 Pleasure in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 04:24:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:24 Plow anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149421</link><description>游릭 07:24 Plow anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 04:24:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 07:24 The threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149420</link><description>游리 07:24 The threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 04:24:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:04 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149419</link><description>游댮 07:04 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 04:04:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:44 Driven anxiety in the Odesa region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149418</link><description>游릭 06:44 Driven anxiety in the Odesa region.Creck on further messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 03:44:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:43 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149417</link><description>游릭 06:43 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 03:43:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:43 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149416</link><description>游릭 06:43 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 03:43:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:40 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149415</link><description>游릭 06:40 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 03:40:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:23 Drive alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149414</link><description>游릭 06:23 Drive alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 03:23:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:21 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149413</link><description>游댮 06:21 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 03:21:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:20 Air alarm to the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149412</link><description>游댮 06:20 Air alarm to the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 03:20:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:06 Air anxiety in the Kherson Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149411</link><description>游댮 06:06 Air anxiety in the Kherson Oblast follow the following messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 03:06:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 05:49 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149410</link><description>游 05:49 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 02:49:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:40 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149409</link><description>游댮 05:40 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 02:40:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:36 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhia region follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149408</link><description>游댮 05:36 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhia region follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 02:36:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:32 Drive alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149407</link><description>游릭 05:32 Drive alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 02:32:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:32 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149406</link><description>游리 05:32 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 02:32:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:59 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149405</link><description>游댮 04:59 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 01:59:27 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>