<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 08:36 Return the threat of artebors in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147732</link><description>游릭 08:36 Return the threat of artebors in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 05:36:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:36 WARNING! DROVIA DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147731</link><description>游릭 08:36 WARNING! DROVIA DRONNES-Kamikadze #M_Nikopol_ti_nikopol_ Territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 05:36:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:24 The threat of shelling in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Solid by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147730</link><description>游릭 08:24 The threat of shelling in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Solid by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 05:24:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 08:04 Attack Dronov -Kamikadzerin Novopavlivka - Transport</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147729</link><description>游 08:04 Attack Dronov -Kamikadzerin Novopavlivka - Transport #M_Nikopol_that_nikopol_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 05:04:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:03 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147728</link><description>游댮 08:03 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 05:03:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:13 Drive anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147727</link><description>游릭 07:13 Drive anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 04:13:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:12 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147726</link><description>游릭 07:12 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 04:12:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 07:11 A.cain alarm.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147725</link><description>游리 07:11 A.cain alarm. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 04:11:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:11 pm alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147724</link><description>游릭 07:11 pm alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 04:11:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:00 Threat of Artbuster! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147723</link><description>游댮 07:00 Threat of Artbuster! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:46 Pleasure the threat of Artobstil to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147722</link><description>游릭 06:46 Pleasure the threat of Artobstil to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 03:46:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:38 PM The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147721</link><description>游릭 06:38 PM The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 03:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:37 Attention! Droze Dronov-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147720</link><description>游릭 06:37 Attention! Droze Dronov-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 03:37:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:11 pm alarm to the Chernihiv region.Creck on subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147719</link><description>游릭 06:11 pm alarm to the Chernihiv region.Creck on subsequent messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 03:11:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:02 The threat of shelling! Pokrovskaya territorial community is artillery firing.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147718</link><description>游댮 06:02 The threat of shelling! Pokrovskaya territorial community is artillery firing. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 03:02:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:36 Failure to alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147717</link><description>游릭 05:36 Failure to alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 02:36:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:36 Return the threat of the use of cards the threat of application</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147716</link><description>游릭 05:36 Return the threat of the use of cards the threat of application This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 02:36:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:14 Air Alarm to Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147715</link><description>游댮 05:14 Air Alarm to Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Chernihiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 02:14:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:02 Drive alarm to Kryvyi Rih District.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147714</link><description>游릭 05:02 Drive alarm to Kryvyi Rih District.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 02:02:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:56 Flow to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147713</link><description>游릭 04:56 Flow to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 01:56:28 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>