<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 15:48 Return of the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143770</link><description>游릭 15:48 Return of the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:48:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:43 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143769</link><description>游댮 15:43 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:43:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:40 Dreaming of anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143768</link><description>游릭 15:40 Dreaming of anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:40 Draw alarm to Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143767</link><description>游릭 15:40 Draw alarm to Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporozhye This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:38 Driven the alarm to the Uman district. Stop by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143766</link><description>游릭 15:38 Driven the alarm to the Uman district. Stop by subsequent messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:38:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:38 Drawing of anxiety in Zvenigorod district.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143765</link><description>游릭 15:38 Drawing of anxiety in Zvenigorod district.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 15:38 Dumping anxiety in the Cherkasy region. Find out, the alarm is still in:- Uman district- Zvenigorod district- Cherkasy district- Zolotonsky district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143764</link><description>游리 15:38 Dumping anxiety in the Cherkasy region. Find out, the alarm is still in:- Uman district- Zvenigorod district- Cherkasy district- Zolotonsky district#Cherkasy_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:38 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143763</link><description>游댮 15:38 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:38:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:38 Air alarm to Cherkasy district care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143762</link><description>游댮 15:38 Air alarm to Cherkasy district care for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:38 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143761</link><description>游릭 15:38 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:38:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:38 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143760</link><description>游댮 15:38 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:38:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:38 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143759</link><description>游릭 15:38 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:38:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:38 Driven Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143758</link><description>游릭 15:38 Driven Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:38:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 15:38 Drawing of anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lipetsk territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143757</link><description>游리 15:38 Drawing of anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lipetsk territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community#Kharkiv_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:38:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 15:38 Drawing of anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Sinelnikovsky rayon- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143756</link><description>游리 15:38 Drawing of anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Sinelnikovsky rayon- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:38:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:38 Air anxiety in Zvenigorod district care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143755</link><description>游댮 15:38 Air anxiety in Zvenigorod district care for further reports.#Zvenigorod_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:38:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:38 Drive alarm to Poltava region.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143754</link><description>游릭 15:38 Drive alarm to Poltava region.Creck on further reports.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:38:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:33 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143753</link><description>游릭 15:33 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Watch for further messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:33:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:23 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143752</link><description>游릭 15:23 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on subsequent messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:23:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:15 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143751</link><description>游댮 15:15 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:15:46 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>