<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 17:55 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154450</link><description>游 17:55 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 14:55:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:49 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154449</link><description>游댮 17:49 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 14:49:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:47 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154448</link><description>游댮 17:47 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporozhye_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 14:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:47 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154447</link><description>游댮 17:47 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 14:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:40 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154446</link><description>游릭 17:40 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 14:40:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:39 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154445</link><description>游릭 17:39 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADze #M_Nikopol_ti_nikopol_ Territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 14:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:22 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154444</link><description>游댮 17:22 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 14:22:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 17:00 The threat of use of the copecreal application</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154443</link><description>游 17:00 The threat of use of the copecreal application This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 14:00:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:59 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154442</link><description>游댮 16:59 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 13:59:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:56 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154441</link><description>游댮 16:56 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 13:56:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:37 Air Alarm to Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154440</link><description>游댮 16:37 Air Alarm to Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Chernihiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 13:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 16:36 Dronov-Kamikadze attack! Movement on city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154439</link><description>游 16:36 Dronov-Kamikadze attack! Movement on city#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 13:36:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:35 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154438</link><description>游댮 16:35 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 13:35:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:33 Reduce the threat of Artobstil to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154437</link><description>游릭 16:33 Reduce the threat of Artobstil to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 13:33:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:24 The threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154436</link><description>游릭 16:24 The threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 13:24:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:24 WARNING! DROVIA DRONNE-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154435</link><description>游릭 16:24 WARNING! DROVIA DRONNE-Kamikadze#m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 13:24:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:18 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154434</link><description>游댮 16:18 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 13:18:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:36 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154433</link><description>游댮 15:36 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 12:36:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 15:06 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154432</link><description>游 15:06 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:39 Driven anxiety in the Odesa region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154431</link><description>游릭 14:39 Driven anxiety in the Odesa region. Watch for further messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 11:39:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>