<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 10:19 Threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131595</link><description>游댮 10:19 Threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 08:19:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131594</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 08:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 09:47 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131593</link><description>游리 09:47 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 07:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:03 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131592</link><description>游댮 09:03 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 07:03:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:58 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131591</link><description>游댮 08:58 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 06:58:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:55 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131590</link><description>游댮 08:55 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 06:55:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:51 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131589</link><description>游댮 08:51 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 06:51:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:37 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131588</link><description>游릭 08:37 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 06:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:09 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131587</link><description>游댮 08:09 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 06:09:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:54 The threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131586</link><description>游릭 06:54 The threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 04:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:29 WARNING !!! DONE ASKRIGHT OF USEED AVIRTED AVIRT Bombs (Kabiv).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131585</link><description>游릭 05:29 WARNING !!! DONE ASKRIGHT OF USEED AVIRTED AVIRT Bombs (Kabiv).#Zaporizhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 03:29:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:28 WARNING !!! DONE ASKRIGHT AVIRTED AVIRT BOMB (Kabiv).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131584</link><description>游릭 05:28 WARNING !!! DONE ASKRIGHT AVIRTED AVIRT BOMB (Kabiv). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 03:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:28 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131583</link><description>游릭 05:28 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 03:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:28 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131582</link><description>游리 05:28 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 03:28:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:27 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia region. Find out, anxiety continues in:- Pologovsky district- Zaporizhzhya district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131581</link><description>游리 05:27 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia region. Find out, anxiety continues in:- Pologovsky district- Zaporizhzhya district#Zaporizhzhia_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 03:27:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:26 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131580</link><description>游릭 05:26 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 03:26:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:26 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131579</link><description>游릭 05:26 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on subsequent messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 03:26:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:26 Flashing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-mirorsk territorial community-Nikopol and Nikopol territorial community-Chervono-Grigoriva territorial community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131578</link><description>游리 05:26 Flashing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-mirorsk territorial community-Nikopol and Nikopol territorial community-Chervono-Grigoriva territorial community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 03:26:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:21 Drive the threat of use of the Cabinet of Construction by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131577</link><description>游릭 05:21 Drive the threat of use of the Cabinet of Construction by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 03:21:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 05:04 The threat of use of the copecreal use of managed aircraft bombs</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131576</link><description>游 05:04 The threat of use of the copecreal use of managed aircraft bombs This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 03:04:42 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>