<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 14:35 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140513</link><description>游릭 14:35 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 11:35:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:35 WARNING! DROPS DRONNIA-KAMKADze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140512</link><description>游릭 14:35 WARNING! DROPS DRONNIA-KAMKADze #M_Nikopol_ti_nikopol_ Territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 11:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:00 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140511</link><description>游 14:00 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:46 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140510</link><description>游릭 13:46 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region. Since further messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 10:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:37 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140509</link><description>游릭 13:37 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 10:37:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:13</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140508</link><description>游댮 13:13 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 10:33:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:29 Driven anxiety in the Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140507</link><description>游릭 13:29 Driven anxiety in the Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 10:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:24 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140506</link><description>游릭 13:24 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 10:24:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:51 attack drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140505</link><description>游 12:51 attack drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 09:51:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:50 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140504</link><description>游댮 12:50 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 09:50:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:49 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140503</link><description>游 12:49 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 09:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:49 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140502</link><description>游댮 12:49 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 09:49:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:46 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140501</link><description>游댮 12:46 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 09:46:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:41 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140500</link><description>游릭 12:41 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 09:41:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:41 Draw an alarm to the Zaporizhzhia region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140499</link><description>游릭 12:41 Draw an alarm to the Zaporizhzhia region. Since further messages.#Zaporizhzhia_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 09:41:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:29 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140498</link><description>游댮 12:29 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 09:29:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:29 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140497</link><description>游댮 12:29 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 09:29:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:01 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140496</link><description>游릭 12:01 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 09:01:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:00 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140495</link><description>游릭 12:00 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 09:00:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:50 pm alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140494</link><description>游릭 11:50 pm alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 08:50:52 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>