<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 19:22 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153862</link><description>游댮 19:22 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 16:22:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:14 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153861</link><description>游댮 19:14 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 16:14:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 19:12 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin Novopavlivka</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153860</link><description>游 19:12 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin Novopavlivka #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 16:12:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:12 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153859</link><description>游댮 19:12 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 16:12:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:43 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153858</link><description>游릭 18:43 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 15:43:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:42 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikovsky District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153857</link><description>游릭 18:42 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikovsky District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 15:42:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:28 The threat of shelling! The Chervonohrigor Territorial Community is now Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153856</link><description>游댮 18:28 The threat of shelling! The Chervonohrigor Territorial Community is now Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 15:28:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:16 Reduce the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153855</link><description>游릭 18:16 Reduce the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 15:16:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:16 WARNING! DRAWE DRONNIA-KAMKADze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153854</link><description>游릭 18:16 WARNING! DRAWE DRONNIA-KAMKADze #M_Nikopol_ti_nikopol_ Territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 15:16:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:12 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153853</link><description>游댮 18:12 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 15:12:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:11 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153852</link><description>游댮 18:11 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 15:11:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 17:43 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153851</link><description>游리 17:43 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 14:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 17:06 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153850</link><description>游 17:06 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 14:06:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:58 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153849</link><description>游댮 16:58 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 13:58:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:57 Dumping anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153848</link><description>游릭 16:57 Dumping anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 13:57:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 16:56 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153847</link><description>游 16:56 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 13:56:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:56 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153846</link><description>游댮 16:56 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 13:56:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:10 Return the threats of the shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take the following reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153845</link><description>游릭 16:10 Return the threats of the shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take the following reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 13:10:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:10 Attention! Droze Dronov-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153844</link><description>游릭 16:10 Attention! Droze Dronov-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 13:10:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 15:27 Attack drones, dumping ammunition district LDC</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/153843</link><description>游 15:27 Attack drones, dumping ammunition district LDC#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 12:27:52 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>