<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 12:49 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152140</link><description>游릭 12:49 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:49:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:49 Alarm in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152139</link><description>游릭 12:49 Alarm in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:49:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:32 Driven anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152138</link><description>游릭 12:32 Driven anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:32:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:32 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152137</link><description>游릭 12:32 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:32:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:32 Dumping anxiety in Kryvyi Rih District.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152136</link><description>游릭 12:32 Dumping anxiety in Kryvyi Rih District.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:32:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:32 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152135</link><description>游릭 12:32 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District. Solve for further reports.#Pavlograd_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:32 MAKALABIBIBIUM ALREADY AVIRTION AVIRIABLE BOMB (Kabiv).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152134</link><description>游릭 12:32 MAKALABIBIBIUM ALREADY AVIRTION AVIRIABLE BOMB (Kabiv). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:32:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:31 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152133</link><description>游릭 12:31 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:31:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:31 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152132</link><description>游릭 12:31 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:31 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152131</link><description>游릭 12:31 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:31 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152130</link><description>游리 12:31 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district#Zaporizhzhya_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:31:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:31 Driven the alarm to Poltava region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152129</link><description>游릭 12:31 Driven the alarm to Poltava region.Creck on further messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:31:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:31 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152128</link><description>游리 12:31 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:31:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:30 plowing anxiety in the Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152127</link><description>游릭 12:30 plowing anxiety in the Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:30:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:30 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152126</link><description>游댮 12:30 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:30:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:29 Air alarm in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152125</link><description>游댮 12:29 Air alarm in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:29:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:19 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152124</link><description>游댮 12:19 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:19:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:19 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152123</link><description>游댮 12:19 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:19:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:18 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152122</link><description>游댮 12:18 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:18:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:18 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152121</link><description>游댮 12:18 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>