<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 16:25 Driven the alarm to the Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151023</link><description>游릭 16:25 Driven the alarm to the Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 13:25:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 16:21 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the old part</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151022</link><description>游 16:21 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the old part This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 13:21:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:21 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151021</link><description>游댮 16:21 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 13:21:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:19 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151020</link><description>游릭 16:19 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 13:19:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:19 Return the threat of shock bplavidbium threat of percussion UAV</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151019</link><description>游릭 16:19 Return the threat of shock bplavidbium threat of percussion UAV#M_Kharkiv_that_harkivskay This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 13:19:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 15:58 The threat of shock UAVs The threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151018</link><description>游 15:58 The threat of shock UAVs The threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 12:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:57 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151017</link><description>游댮 15:57 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 12:57:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:24 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151016</link><description>游댮 15:24 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 12:24:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:06 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151015</link><description>游댮 15:06 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 12:06:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:57 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151014</link><description>游댮 14:57 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 11:57:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:09 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151013</link><description>游릭 14:09 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 11:09:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:09 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151012</link><description>游릭 14:09 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 11:09:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:01 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151011</link><description>游 14:01 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#KUDYANSKY This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 11:01:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 13:37 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151010</link><description>游 13:37 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:37:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:37 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151009</link><description>游댮 13:37 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:30 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151008</link><description>游릭 13:30 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:30:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:47 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151007</link><description>游댮 12:47 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 09:47:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:40 WARNING !!! DONE ASKRIGHT ACCEPTED AVIRTEVER BOMB (Kabiv).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151006</link><description>游릭 12:40 WARNING !!! DONE ASKRIGHT ACCEPTED AVIRTEVER BOMB (Kabiv). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 09:40:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:39 WARNING !!! DONE ASKRIGHT OF USEED AVIRTED AVIRT BOMB (Kabiv).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151005</link><description>游릭 12:39 WARNING !!! DONE ASKRIGHT OF USEED AVIRTED AVIRT BOMB (Kabiv).#Zaporizhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 09:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:39 Threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Manganese territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151004</link><description>游댮 12:39 Threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Manganese territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 09:39:50 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>