<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 14:07 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149476</link><description>游 14:07 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 11:07:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:02 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149475</link><description>游댮 14:02 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 11:02:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:51 WARNING !!! DONE ASKRIGHT OF USEED AVIRTED AVIRIAL Bombs (Kabiv).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149474</link><description>游릭 13:51 WARNING !!! DONE ASKRIGHT OF USEED AVIRTED AVIRIAL Bombs (Kabiv). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:51:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:44 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149473</link><description>游릭 13:44 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:44:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 13:40 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149472</link><description>游리 13:40 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:40:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Air alarm supports the collection</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149471</link><description>Air alarm supports the collection # 13 to protect the sky from enemy drones 九괴TLAS Festival and the "Come back alive" fund for the sake of a joint mission - to protect the sky over Ukrainian cities. We collect 100 million hryvnias to support the Dronopad project. Do you and you. Together we can more! http://bit.ly/4kvwsqm This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:33 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149470</link><description>游릭 13:33 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:33 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149469</link><description>游릭 13:33 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADze #M_Nikopol_t.Nikopol_ Territorial_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:33:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:25 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149468</link><description>游릭 13:25 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:25:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 13:25 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149467</link><description>游리 13:25 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district#Zaporizhzhya_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:25:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 13:11 Attack drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149466</link><description>游 13:11 Attack drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:11:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:11 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149465</link><description>游댮 13:11 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:11:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:07 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149464</link><description>游댮 13:07 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:07:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:23 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149463</link><description>游 12:23 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 09:23:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:18 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149462</link><description>游댮 12:18 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 09:18:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:57 Clease the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149461</link><description>游릭 11:57 Clease the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 08:57:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:48 Threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149460</link><description>游댮 11:48 Threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 08:48:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:40 PM threats of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149459</link><description>游릭 11:40 PM threats of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 08:40:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:37 Close the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149458</link><description>游릭 11:37 Close the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 08:37:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:36 Driven the alarm to Sumy region.Creat for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149457</link><description>游릭 11:36 Driven the alarm to Sumy region.Creat for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 08:36:16 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>