<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 01:17 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129058</link><description>游댮 01:17 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 23:17:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:02 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129057</link><description>游댮 01:02 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 23:02:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:37 Air anxiety in Zvenigorod district care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129056</link><description>游댮 00:37 Air anxiety in Zvenigorod district care for further messages.#Zvenigorod_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 22:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:36 Air anxiety in the Zhytomyr Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129055</link><description>游댮 00:36 Air anxiety in the Zhytomyr Oblast follow the following messages.#Zhytomyr_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 22:36:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00.00</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129054</link><description>游릭 00.00 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 22:00:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:27 WARNING !!! Draft threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129053</link><description>游릭 23:27 WARNING !!! Draft threat#Zaporizhia_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 21:27:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 23:26 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129052</link><description>游리 23:26 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya district#Zaporizhzhia_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 21:26:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:25 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129051</link><description>游릭 23:25 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 21:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:16 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129050</link><description>游댮 23:16 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kirovograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 21:16:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:12 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129049</link><description>游댮 23:12 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 21:12:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:54 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129048</link><description>游릭 22:54 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 20:54:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:54 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129047</link><description>游릭 22:54 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 20:54:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:32 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129046</link><description>游댮 22:32 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 20:32:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:12 Driven the alarm to the Uman District. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129045</link><description>游릭 22:12 Driven the alarm to the Uman District. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 20:12:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:12 Drawing anxiety in Zvenigorod district.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129044</link><description>游릭 22:12 Drawing anxiety in Zvenigorod district.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 20:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 22:12 Dumping anxiety in the Cherkasy region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Uman district- Zvenigorod district- Cherkasy district- Zolotonsky district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129043</link><description>游리 22:12 Dumping anxiety in the Cherkasy region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Uman district- Zvenigorod district- Cherkasy district- Zolotonsky district#Cherkasy_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 20:12:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:12 Drive alarm to Vinnytsia region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129042</link><description>游릭 22:12 Drive alarm to Vinnytsia region. Watch for further messages.#Vinnytsia_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 20:12:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:12 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Stop by further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129041</link><description>游릭 22:12 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Stop by further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 20:12:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:12 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129040</link><description>游댮 22:12 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 20:12:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:12 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129039</link><description>游댮 22:12 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 20:12:11 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>