<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 11:57 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144408</link><description>游댮 11:57 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 08:57:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:38 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144407</link><description>游댮 11:38 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 08:38:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:37 Reduce threatening the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144406</link><description>游릭 11:37 Reduce threatening the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 08:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:37 Flowing anxiety in the Zaporizhzhia region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144405</link><description>游리 11:37 Flowing anxiety in the Zaporizhzhia region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district#Zaporizhzhya_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 08:37:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:03 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144404</link><description>游릭 11:03 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 08:03:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:03 Attention! Droze Dronov-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144403</link><description>游릭 11:03 Attention! Droze Dronov-Kamikadze #M_Nikopol_ti_nikopol_ Territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 08:03:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:46 Frame alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144402</link><description>游릭 10:46 Frame alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 07:46:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:43 Driven anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144401</link><description>游릭 10:43 Driven anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 07:43:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 10:42 pursuance of anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144400</link><description>游리 10:42 pursuance of anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 07:42:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 10:42 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144399</link><description>游리 10:42 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 07:42:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:42 Drive alarm to Poltava region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144398</link><description>游릭 10:42 Drive alarm to Poltava region. Watch for further messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 07:42:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:42 Driven Alarm in Kyiv. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144397</link><description>游릭 10:42 Driven Alarm in Kyiv. Salt for further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 07:42:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:42 Driven Alarm to Kyiv Oblast. Since Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144396</link><description>游릭 10:42 Driven Alarm to Kyiv Oblast. Since Further Messages.#Kyiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 07:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:41 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144395</link><description>游릭 10:41 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 07:41:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:41 Dumping anxiety in the Cherkasy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144394</link><description>游릭 10:41 Dumping anxiety in the Cherkasy region.Creck on further messages.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 07:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:41 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144393</link><description>游릭 10:41 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 07:41:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:41 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144392</link><description>游릭 10:41 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 07:41:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:19 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144391</link><description>游댮 10:19 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 07:19:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:16 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144390</link><description>游댮 10:16 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 07:16:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:16 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144389</link><description>游댮 10:16 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 07:16:22 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>