<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游리 14:02 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137449</link><description>游리 14:02 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 11:02:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:01 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137448</link><description>游릭 14:01 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 11:01:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:01 Draw an alarm to the Zaporizhzhia region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137447</link><description>游릭 14:01 Draw an alarm to the Zaporizhzhia region. Since further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:00 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137446</link><description>游릭 14:00 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 11:00:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:00 Driven to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137445</link><description>游릭 14:00 Driven to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 11:00:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:00 Driven to the Poltava region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137444</link><description>游릭 14:00 Driven to the Poltava region. Watch for further messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 11:00:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:00 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137443</link><description>游 14:00 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 11:00:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 14:00 alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marhanetsky Territorial Community- Mirorivska Territorial Community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivska Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137442</link><description>游리 14:00 alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marhanetsky Territorial Community- Mirorivska Territorial Community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivska Territorial Community This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 11:00:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:59 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137441</link><description>游릭 13:59 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 10:59:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:57 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137440</link><description>游댮 13:57 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 10:57:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 13:06 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137439</link><description>游리 13:06 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 10:06:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:56 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137438</link><description>游댮 12:56 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 09:56:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:39 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137437</link><description>游댮 12:39 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 09:39:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:38 Threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marhanetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137436</link><description>游댮 12:38 Threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marhanetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 09:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:36 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137435</link><description>游댮 12:36 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kirovograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 09:36:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:36 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137434</link><description>游댮 12:36 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 09:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:30 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137433</link><description>游댮 12:30 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 09:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:30 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137432</link><description>游댮 12:30 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 09:30:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:28 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137431</link><description>游댮 12:28 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 09:28:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:26 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137430</link><description>游릭 12:26 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 09:26:06 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>