<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 02:25 Air anxiety in the Dnieper District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140765</link><description>游댮 02:25 Air anxiety in the Dnieper District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 23:25:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:25 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140764</link><description>游댮 02:25 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 23:25:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:54 Air alarm to Cherkasy district observe further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140763</link><description>游댮 01:54 Air alarm to Cherkasy district observe further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 22:54:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:54 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140762</link><description>游댮 01:54 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 22:54:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:51 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140761</link><description>游댮 01:51 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 22:51:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:50 Air Alarm to Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140760</link><description>游댮 01:50 Air Alarm to Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.#Pavlograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 22:50:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:21 Driven anxiety in Kyiv. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140759</link><description>游릭 01:21 Driven anxiety in Kyiv. Stop by further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 22:21:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:13 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140758</link><description>游댮 01:13 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.#Sinelnikov. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 22:13:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:11 plowing anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creb</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140757</link><description>游릭 01:11 plowing anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creb This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 22:11:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:10 Failure to alarm to Cherkasy district.This followed by further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140756</link><description>游릭 01:10 Failure to alarm to Cherkasy district.This followed by further reports.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 22:10:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:10 Drawing anxiety in the Uman District.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140755</link><description>游릭 01:10 Drawing anxiety in the Uman District.Creck on Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 22:10:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:10 Failure to alarm in Zvenigorod district.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140754</link><description>游릭 01:10 Failure to alarm in Zvenigorod district.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 22:10:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:08 Flow to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140753</link><description>游릭 01:08 Flow to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 22:08:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:08 Dumping anxiety in the Zhytomyr region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140752</link><description>游릭 01:08 Dumping anxiety in the Zhytomyr region.Creck on further messages.#Zhytomyr_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 22:08:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 00:22 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140751</link><description>游 00:22 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 21:22:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:22 Air Air Anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140750</link><description>游댮 00:22 Air Air Anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 21:22:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:20 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140749</link><description>游댮 00:20 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.#M_kiiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 21:20:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:49 Air Alarm to Zhytomyr Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140748</link><description>游댮 23:49 Air Alarm to Zhytomyr Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zhytomyr_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 20:49:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:19 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140747</link><description>游댮 23:19 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 20:19:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:16 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140746</link><description>游릭 23:16 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 20:16:28 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>