<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 10:24 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154349</link><description>游댮 10:24 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 07:24:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:19 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154348</link><description>游댮 10:19 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 07:19:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:03 Attack drones, possible discharges of ammunition district of the old part</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154347</link><description>游 10:03 Attack drones, possible discharges of ammunition district of the old part #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 07:03:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:03 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154346</link><description>游릭 10:03 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 07:03:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:03 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154345</link><description>游댮 10:03 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 07:03:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154344</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 07:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:38 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154343</link><description>游릭 09:38 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Watch for further messages.#Kherson_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:38:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:35 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154342</link><description>游댮 09:35 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:30 Threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154341</link><description>游댮 09:30 Threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:26 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154340</link><description>游릭 09:26 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:26:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:11 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154339</link><description>游댮 09:11 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:11:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:09 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154338</link><description>游댮 09:09 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:09:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:06 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154337</link><description>游댮 09:06 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:06:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:58 Air anxiety in the Kherson Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154336</link><description>游댮 08:58 Air anxiety in the Kherson Oblast follow the following messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 05:58:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:23 Return the threat of artobrats in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154335</link><description>游릭 08:23 Return the threat of artobrats in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 05:23:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:02 Return the threat of arteblow to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154334</link><description>游릭 08:02 Return the threat of arteblow to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 05:02:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:54 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154333</link><description>游릭 07:54 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 04:54:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 07:50 PM Anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154332</link><description>游리 07:50 PM Anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 04:50:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:50 PM of anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154331</link><description>游릭 07:50 PM of anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 04:50:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:50 The threat of percussion bplavidbium threat of percussion UAV</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154330</link><description>游릭 07:50 The threat of percussion bplavidbium threat of percussion UAV#M_Kharkiv_tha_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 04:50:25 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>