<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 09:51 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147377</link><description>游댮 09:51 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:51:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:44 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147376</link><description>游릭 09:44 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:44:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:44 Attention! Drown Dronov-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147375</link><description>游릭 09:44 Attention! Drown Dronov-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:44:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:42 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsk District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147374</link><description>游릭 09:42 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsk District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:42:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:34 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147373</link><description>游댮 09:34 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:34:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:34 Dumping anxiety in Pavlograd District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147372</link><description>游릭 09:34 Dumping anxiety in Pavlograd District. Watch for further reports.#Pavlograd_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:34:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:34 Driven anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147371</link><description>游릭 09:34 Driven anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:34:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:34 Pleasure in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147370</link><description>游릭 09:34 Pleasure in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:34:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:34 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147369</link><description>游릭 09:34 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Follow the following messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 09:34 Auxiliary in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Pavlograd district-Sinelnikovsky rayon- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community- Nikopol and Nikopol territorial community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147368</link><description>游리 09:34 Auxiliary in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Pavlograd district-Sinelnikovsky rayon- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community- Nikopol and Nikopol territorial community This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:34:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:34 Dumping anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creb</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147367</link><description>游릭 09:34 Dumping anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creb This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:34 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147366</link><description>游릭 09:34 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region. Watch for further messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:34:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:32 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147365</link><description>游릭 09:32 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Watch for further messages.#Odessa_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:32:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:32 Driven anxiety in the Transcarpathian region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147364</link><description>游릭 09:32 Driven anxiety in the Transcarpathian region.Creat by further messages.#Transcarpathian_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:32:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:32 Driven anxiety in the Ivano-Frankivsk region.Crete on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147363</link><description>游릭 09:32 Driven anxiety in the Ivano-Frankivsk region.Crete on further reports.#Ivano-Frankivsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:32:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:32 Driven the alarm to the Rivne region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147362</link><description>游릭 09:32 Driven the alarm to the Rivne region.Creck on further messages.#Rivne_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:32:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:32 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147361</link><description>游릭 09:32 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:32:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:32 Driven the alarm to Lviv region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147360</link><description>游릭 09:32 Driven the alarm to Lviv region.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:32 Drive alarm to the Volyn region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147359</link><description>游릭 09:32 Drive alarm to the Volyn region.Creat by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:32:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:32 Drive alarm to the Khmelnytsky region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147358</link><description>游릭 09:32 Drive alarm to the Khmelnytsky region. Watch for further messages.#Khmelnitskaya This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:32:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>