<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 00:15 Drive anxiety in the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144900</link><description>游릭 00:15 Drive anxiety in the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 21:15:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:15 Drive anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creck on subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144899</link><description>游릭 00:15 Drive anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creck on subsequent messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 21:15:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:15 Drive anxiety in Cherkasy district.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144898</link><description>游릭 00:15 Drive anxiety in Cherkasy district.Creck on further reports.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 21:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:09 Air anxiety in Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Posts.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144897</link><description>游댮 00:09 Air anxiety in Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Posts.#Kryvyi Rih This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 21:09:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:07 Air alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144896</link><description>游댮 00:07 Air alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.#Nikopol. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 21:07:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:46 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144895</link><description>游댮 23:46 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad Oblast follow the following messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:46:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:44 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144894</link><description>游댮 23:44 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:44:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:44 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District to follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144893</link><description>游댮 23:44 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District to follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:44:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:39 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144892</link><description>游댮 23:39 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:39:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:38 Air alarm to Dniprovskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144891</link><description>游댮 23:38 Air alarm to Dniprovskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:38:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:34 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144890</link><description>游댮 23:34 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:34:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:12 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144889</link><description>游댮 23:12 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:12:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:12 Air alarm to Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144888</link><description>游댮 23:12 Air alarm to Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.#Pavlograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:12:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:11 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsk District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144887</link><description>游댮 23:11 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsk District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:11:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:09 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144886</link><description>游댮 23:09 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:09:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:56 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144885</link><description>游댮 22:56 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 19:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 22:50 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144884</link><description>游 22:50 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 19:50:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:49 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144883</link><description>游댮 22:49 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 19:49:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:57 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144882</link><description>游댮 21:57 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 18:57:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:55 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144881</link><description>游댮 21:55 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 18:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>