<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 14:29 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149132</link><description>游댮 14:29 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 11:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:00 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149131</link><description>游 14:00 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:49 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149130</link><description>游릭 13:49 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:49:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:35 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149129</link><description>游릭 13:35 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:35:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:35 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149128</link><description>游릭 13:35 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:35:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:16 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149127</link><description>游댮 13:16 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:16:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:01 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149126</link><description>游릭 13:01 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:01:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:01 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149125</link><description>游릭 13:01 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:01:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:58 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149124</link><description>游릭 12:58 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 09:58:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:41 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149123</link><description>游댮 12:41 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 09:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:12 Return the threat of artebing to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149122</link><description>游릭 12:12 Return the threat of artebing to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 09:12:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:02 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149121</link><description>游릭 12:02 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 09:02:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:02 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast. Since Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149120</link><description>游릭 12:02 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast. Since Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 09:02:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:02 Driven anxiety in the Ivano-Frankivsk region.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149119</link><description>游릭 12:02 Driven anxiety in the Ivano-Frankivsk region.Creck on further reports.#Ivano-Frankivsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 09:02:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:02 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149118</link><description>游릭 12:02 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 09:02:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:02 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149117</link><description>游릭 12:02 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 09:02:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:02 Drive alarm to the Volyn region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149116</link><description>游릭 12:02 Drive alarm to the Volyn region.Creck on further messages.#Volyn_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 09:02:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:01 Driven the alarm to Vinnytsia region.Crete on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149115</link><description>游릭 12:01 Driven the alarm to Vinnytsia region.Crete on further messages.#Vinnytsia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 09:02:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:01 Dumping anxiety in Ternopil region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149114</link><description>游릭 12:01 Dumping anxiety in Ternopil region. Watch for further messages.#Ternopil_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 09:01:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:01 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149113</link><description>游리 12:01 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 09:01:39 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>