<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 06:54 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin of the old part</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149235</link><description>游 06:54 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin of the old part #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 03:54:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:41 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149234</link><description>游댮 06:41 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 03:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:32 Air anxiety in Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149233</link><description>游댮 06:32 Air anxiety in Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.#Pavlograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 03:32:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:32 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149232</link><description>游댮 06:32 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 03:32:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:23 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149231</link><description>游댮 06:23 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 03:23:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 06:03 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149230</link><description>游 06:03 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 03:03:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:55 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149229</link><description>游댮 05:55 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.#Sinelnikov. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 02:55:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:55 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149228</link><description>游댮 05:55 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 02:55:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:26 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149227</link><description>游릭 05:26 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 02:26:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:26 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149226</link><description>游릭 05:26 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 02:26:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:25 Drive alarm to Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149225</link><description>游릭 05:25 Drive alarm to Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 02:25:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:25 Failure to alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149224</link><description>游릭 05:25 Failure to alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 02:25:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:25 Return the threat of shock Blividbium threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149223</link><description>游릭 05:25 Return the threat of shock Blividbium threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 02:25:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:25 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149222</link><description>游릭 05:25 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District. Solve for further reports.#Pavlograd_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 02:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:25 Driven anxiety in the Kherson region. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149221</link><description>游릭 05:25 Driven anxiety in the Kherson region. Stop by further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 02:25:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:25 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsky District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149220</link><description>游릭 05:25 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsky District. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 02:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:25 Drive alarm to Poltava region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149219</link><description>游릭 05:25 Drive alarm to Poltava region. Watch for further reports.#Poltava_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 02:25:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:25 Failure to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Novomoskovsky Ralolograd R. Manganese and Marganets Territorial Community and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Graborovskaya Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149218</link><description>游리 05:25 Failure to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Novomoskovsky Ralolograd R. Manganese and Marganets Territorial Community and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Graborovskaya Territorial Community This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 02:25:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:25 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149217</link><description>游릭 05:25 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 02:25:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:25 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Observe by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149216</link><description>游릭 05:25 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Observe by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 02:25:22 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>