<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 01:05 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132609</link><description>游댮 01:05 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 23:05:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:05 Air alarm in Zvenigorod district to care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132608</link><description>游댮 01:05 Air alarm in Zvenigorod district to care for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 23:05:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:58 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132607</link><description>游댮 00:58 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 22:58:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:57 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132606</link><description>游댮 00:57 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 22:57:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:51 Air anxiety in the Kirovohrad Oblast follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132605</link><description>游댮 00:51 Air anxiety in the Kirovohrad Oblast follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 22:51:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:39 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132604</link><description>游댮 23:39 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.#M_kiiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 21:39:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:07 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132603</link><description>游릭 23:07 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 21:07:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:04 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132602</link><description>游댮 23:04 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 21:04:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:51 Air alarm to Cherkasy district care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132601</link><description>游댮 22:51 Air alarm to Cherkasy district care for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 20:51:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:51 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132600</link><description>游댮 22:51 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 20:51:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:29 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132599</link><description>游댮 22:29 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 20:29:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:04 Driven anxiety in the Odesa region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132598</link><description>游릭 22:04 Driven anxiety in the Odesa region. Since further messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 20:04:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:03 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132597</link><description>游릭 22:03 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 20:03:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 21:47 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132596</link><description>游 21:47 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 19:47:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:46 Air alarm to the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132595</link><description>游댮 21:46 Air alarm to the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 19:46:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:45 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132594</link><description>游댮 21:45 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 19:45:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:36 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132593</link><description>游댮 21:36 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 19:36:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:26 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132592</link><description>游댮 21:26 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 19:26:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:25 Air alarm to the Donetsk region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132591</link><description>游댮 21:25 Air alarm to the Donetsk region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 19:25:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 20:52 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/132590</link><description>游 20:52 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 18:52:23 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>