<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 09:55 Drive alarm to Cherkasy district.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143916</link><description>游릭 09:55 Drive alarm to Cherkasy district.Creck on further reports.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 06:55:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:55 Dumping anxiety in Uman District.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143915</link><description>游릭 09:55 Dumping anxiety in Uman District.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 06:55:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:55 Failure to alarm in Zvenigorod district.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143914</link><description>游릭 09:55 Failure to alarm in Zvenigorod district.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 06:55:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:55 Flow to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143913</link><description>游릭 09:55 Flow to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 06:55:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:54 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143912</link><description>游릭 09:54 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 06:54:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:53 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143911</link><description>游릭 09:53 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 06:53:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:53 Flow alarms to Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143910</link><description>游릭 09:53 Flow alarms to Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporozhye This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 06:53:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:53 Driven anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143909</link><description>游릭 09:53 Driven anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 06:53:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:53 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143908</link><description>游릭 09:53 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 06:53:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 09:53 Driven anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143907</link><description>游리 09:53 Driven anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 06:53:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:44 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143906</link><description>游댮 09:44 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 06:44:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:40 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143905</link><description>游릭 09:40 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Watch for further messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 06:40:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:23 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143904</link><description>游댮 09:23 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 06:23:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:23 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143903</link><description>游댮 09:23 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 06:23:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:23 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143902</link><description>游댮 09:23 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 06:23:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:23 Air anxiety in the Kherson Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143901</link><description>游댮 09:23 Air anxiety in the Kherson Oblast follow the following messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 06:23:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:23 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143900</link><description>游댮 09:23 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 06:23:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:23 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143899</link><description>游댮 09:23 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 06:23:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:19 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143898</link><description>游릭 09:19 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region. Since further reports.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 06:19:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:11 pleasure anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143897</link><description>游릭 09:11 pleasure anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 06:11:09 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>