<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>🔴 21:25 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148801</link><description>🔴 21:25 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow the following messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 18:25:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:25 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148800</link><description>🔴 21:25 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 18:25:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:25 Air alarm in Zvenigorod District to care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148799</link><description>🔴 21:25 Air alarm in Zvenigorod District to care for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 18:25:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:22 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148798</link><description>🔴 21:22 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 18:22:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:22 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148797</link><description>🔴 21:22 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 18:22:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:06 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148796</link><description>🔴 21:06 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.#M_kiiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 18:06:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:01 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148795</link><description>🔴 21:01 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 18:01:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:01 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148794</link><description>🔴 21:01 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 18:01:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 21:01 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148793</link><description>🟠 21:01 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 18:01:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:01 Air anxiety in the Novomoskovskiy District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148792</link><description>🔴 21:01 Air anxiety in the Novomoskovskiy District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 18:01:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:01 Air alarm to Dniprovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148791</link><description>🔴 21:01 Air alarm to Dniprovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 18:01:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:01 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148790</link><description>🔴 21:01 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.#Kryvyi Rih. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 18:01:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:01 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148789</link><description>🔴 21:01 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 18:01:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:00 Air Alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148788</link><description>🔴 21:00 Air Alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.#Nikopol_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 18:00:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:00 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148787</link><description>🔴 21:00 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 18:00:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 20:44 Air alarm to Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148786</link><description>🔴 20:44 Air alarm to Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.#Pavlograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 17:44:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 20:43 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148785</link><description>🔴 20:43 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 17:43:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 20:29 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148784</link><description>🔴 20:29 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 17:29:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 20:29 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District to follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148783</link><description>🔴 20:29 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District to follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 17:29:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 20:23 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148782</link><description>🔴 20:23 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 17:23:06 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>