<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 18:37 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151036</link><description>游댮 18:37 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 15:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:16 Failure to alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151035</link><description>游릭 18:16 Failure to alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 15:16:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:16 Drives the threat of shock bpadbius threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151034</link><description>游릭 18:16 Drives the threat of shock bpadbius threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 15:16:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 18:15 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151033</link><description>游리 18:15 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 15:15:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:55 Driven alarm to Sinelnikov District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151032</link><description>游릭 17:55 Driven alarm to Sinelnikov District. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 14:55:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:54 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151031</link><description>游릭 17:54 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 14:54:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:23 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District to follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151030</link><description>游댮 17:23 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District to follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 14:23:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:03 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151029</link><description>游릭 17:03 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 14:03:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:03 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151028</link><description>游릭 17:03 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADze #M_Nikopol_ti_nikopol. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 14:03:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:55 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151027</link><description>游댮 16:55 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 13:55:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 16:55 The threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151026</link><description>游 16:55 The threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"#m_harkiv_that_tha_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 13:55:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:54 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151025</link><description>游댮 16:54 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 13:54:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 16:41 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151024</link><description>游리 16:41 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 13:41:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:25 Driven the alarm to Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151023</link><description>游릭 16:25 Driven the alarm to Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 13:25:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 16:21 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the old part</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151022</link><description>游 16:21 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the old part This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 13:21:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:21 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151021</link><description>游댮 16:21 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 13:21:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:19 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151020</link><description>游릭 16:19 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 13:19:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:19 Return the threat of shock bplavidbium threat of percussion UAV</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151019</link><description>游릭 16:19 Return the threat of shock bplavidbium threat of percussion UAV#M_Kharkiv_that_harkivskay This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 13:19:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 15:58 Threat of percussion UAV The threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151018</link><description>游 15:58 Threat of percussion UAV The threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 12:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:57 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151017</link><description>游댮 15:57 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 12:57:13 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>