<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 14:09 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151013</link><description>游릭 14:09 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 11:09:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:09 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151012</link><description>游릭 14:09 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 11:09:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:01 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151011</link><description>游 14:01 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#KUDYANSKY This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 11:01:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 13:37 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151010</link><description>游 13:37 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:37:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:37 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151009</link><description>游댮 13:37 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:30 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151008</link><description>游릭 13:30 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:30:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:47 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151007</link><description>游댮 12:47 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 09:47:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:40 WARNING !!! DONE ASKRIGHT ACCEPTED AVIRTEVER BOMB (Kabiv).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151006</link><description>游릭 12:40 WARNING !!! DONE ASKRIGHT ACCEPTED AVIRTEVER BOMB (Kabiv). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 09:40:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:39 WARNING !!! DONE ASKRIGHT OF USEED AVIRTED AVIRT BOMB (Kabiv).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151005</link><description>游릭 12:39 WARNING !!! DONE ASKRIGHT OF USEED AVIRTED AVIRT BOMB (Kabiv).#Zaporizhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 09:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:39 Threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Manganese territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151004</link><description>游댮 12:39 Threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Manganese territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 09:39:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:39 WARNING !!! Drive the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151003</link><description>游릭 12:39 WARNING !!! Drive the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 09:39:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:37 Flow to the Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district- Zaporizhzhya district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151002</link><description>游리 12:37 Flow to the Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district- Zaporizhzhya district#Zaporizhzhya_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 09:37:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:37 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151001</link><description>游릭 12:37 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 09:37:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:37 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151000</link><description>游릭 12:37 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 09:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:27 Reduce the threat of Artobstil to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150999</link><description>游릭 12:27 Reduce the threat of Artobstil to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 09:27:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:13 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150998</link><description>游릭 12:13 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 09:13:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:13 Attention! Sleep Dronov-Kamikadze's attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150997</link><description>游릭 12:13 Attention! Sleep Dronov-Kamikadze's attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 09:13:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:01 Return the threat of artobstil in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150996</link><description>游릭 12:01 Return the threat of artobstil in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 09:01:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:54 A. Run in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150995</link><description>游릭 11:54 A. Run in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 08:54:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:49 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150994</link><description>游릭 11:49 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Watch for further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 08:49:22 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>