<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 13:24 Driven anxiety in the Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133340</link><description>游릭 13:24 Driven anxiety in the Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:24:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:49 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133339</link><description>游댮 12:49 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 10:49:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:13 Reduce the threat of Artobstil to the Mirovskaya Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133338</link><description>游릭 12:13 Reduce the threat of Artobstil to the Mirovskaya Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 10:13:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:48 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133337</link><description>游릭 11:48 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 09:48:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:42 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133336</link><description>游릭 11:42 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 09:42:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:41 Close the threat of Artobstil to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133335</link><description>游릭 11:41 Close the threat of Artobstil to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 09:41:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:25 Failure to alarm to the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133334</link><description>游릭 11:25 Failure to alarm to the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 09:25:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:05 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133333</link><description>游댮 11:05 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 09:05:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:54 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133332</link><description>游댮 10:54 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 08:54:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:32 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast. Since Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133331</link><description>游릭 10:32 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast. Since Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 08:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133330</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 08:00:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:51 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133329</link><description>游댮 09:51 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 07:51:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:22 Drive alarm to the Kiev region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133328</link><description>游릭 09:22 Drive alarm to the Kiev region. Since further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 07:22:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:21 Driven the alarm in Kyiv. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133327</link><description>游릭 09:21 Driven the alarm in Kyiv. Stop by further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 07:21:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:02 Air anxiety in the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133326</link><description>游댮 09:02 Air anxiety in the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 07:02:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:00 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133325</link><description>游댮 09:00 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 07:00:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:51 Return the threat of artobrats in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Solid by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133324</link><description>游릭 08:51 Return the threat of artobrats in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Solid by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 06:51:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:18 Air anxiety in the Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133323</link><description>游댮 08:18 Air anxiety in the Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Chernihiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 06:18:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:14 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133322</link><description>游댮 08:14 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 06:14:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:15 Failure of the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133321</link><description>游릭 06:15 Failure of the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 04:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>