<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 20:08 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143555</link><description>游 20:08 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 19:27 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region. Follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143554</link><description>游릭 19:27 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region. Follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:27:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 19:11 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack continues</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143553</link><description>游 19:11 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack continues This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:11:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:58 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143552</link><description>游릭 18:58 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 15:58:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:57 Return the threat of artobrats in the Bilenkovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143551</link><description>游릭 18:57 Return the threat of artobrats in the Bilenkovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 15:57:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:44 Driven anxiety in the Sinelnikov District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143550</link><description>游릭 18:44 Driven anxiety in the Sinelnikov District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 15:44:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 18:41 Dumping anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143549</link><description>游리 18:41 Dumping anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 15:41:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 18:40 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143548</link><description>游 18:40 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 15:40:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:40 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143547</link><description>游댮 18:40 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:40 The threat of shelling! Now in the Belenkovsky territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143546</link><description>游댮 18:40 The threat of shelling! Now in the Belenkovsky territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:38 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143545</link><description>游댮 18:38 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 15:38:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:30 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143544</link><description>游릭 18:30 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.#Of Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 15:30:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:14 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143543</link><description>游댮 18:14 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 15:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:02 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143542</link><description>游댮 18:02 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 15:02:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:44 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143541</link><description>游댮 17:44 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 14:44:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:16 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143540</link><description>游릭 17:16 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 14:16:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 17:15 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143539</link><description>游리 17:15 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 14:15:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:57 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143538</link><description>游릭 16:57 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 13:57:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:57 Show the threat of percussion bplavidbium threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143537</link><description>游릭 16:57 Show the threat of percussion bplavidbium threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 13:57:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 16:49 threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143536</link><description>游 16:49 threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 13:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>