<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 14:42 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138298</link><description>游댮 14:42 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 11:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:40 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138297</link><description>游댮 14:40 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 11:40:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:31 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138296</link><description>游댮 14:31 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 11:31:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:22 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack is ongoing!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138295</link><description>游 14:22 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack is ongoing! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 11:22:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>?</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138294</link><description>? This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 11:10:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 14:06 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138293</link><description>游댮 14:06 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 11:06:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 14:00 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138292</link><description>游 14:00 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 11:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 13:59 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh in the direction</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138291</link><description>游 13:59 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh in the direction This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 10:59:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 13:51 Attack drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138290</link><description>游 13:51 Attack drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 10:51:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 13:50 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138289</link><description>游 13:50 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 10:50:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:49 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138288</link><description>游댮 13:49 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 10:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:48 Drive alarm to the Odesa region. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138287</link><description>游릭 13:48 Drive alarm to the Odesa region. Stop by further messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 10:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:33 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138286</link><description>游댮 13:33 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 10:33:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:33 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138285</link><description>游댮 13:33 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 10:33:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:32 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138284</link><description>游릭 13:32 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 10:32:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:32 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138283</link><description>游릭 13:32 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADze#M_Nikopol_t.Nikopol_ Territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 10:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:04 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138282</link><description>游댮 13:04 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 10:04:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 13:04 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138281</link><description>游 13:04 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 10:04:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:03 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138280</link><description>游댮 13:03 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 10:03:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:46 plout anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/138279</link><description>游릭 12:46 plout anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 09:46:05 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>