<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 21:47 Air alarm to Dniprovskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144493</link><description>游댮 21:47 Air alarm to Dniprovskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 18:47:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:47 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144492</link><description>游댮 21:47 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 18:47:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 21:47 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144491</link><description>游 21:47 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 18:47:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:46 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144490</link><description>游댮 21:46 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 18:46:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 21:42 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144489</link><description>游릭 21:42 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 18:42:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:34 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsk District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144488</link><description>游댮 21:34 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsk District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 18:34:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:34 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144487</link><description>游댮 21:34 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.#Kryvyi Rih Ri This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 18:34:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:15 Air alarm to Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144486</link><description>游댮 21:15 Air alarm to Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.#Pavlograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 18:15:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:15 Air Alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144485</link><description>游댮 21:15 Air Alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.#Nikopol. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 18:15:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮11</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144484</link><description>游댮11 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 18:13:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:12 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144483</link><description>游댮 21:12 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 18:12:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:54 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144482</link><description>游댮 20:54 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 17:54:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:45 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144481</link><description>游댮 20:45 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 17:45:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:38 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144480</link><description>游댮 20:38 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 17:38:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:37 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky district to care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144479</link><description>游댮 20:37 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky district to care for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 17:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:37 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144478</link><description>游댮 20:37 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 17:37:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:16 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144477</link><description>游댮 20:16 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 17:16:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:01 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144476</link><description>游릭 20:01 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 17:01:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:01 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144475</link><description>游릭 20:01 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 17:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 19:49 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144474</link><description>游릭 19:49 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat on further reports.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 16:49:16 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>