<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 00:17 Flashing of anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147026</link><description>游릭 00:17 Flashing of anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 21:17:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:17 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147025</link><description>游릭 00:17 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 21:17:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 00:</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147024</link><description>游리 00: This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 21:17:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:15 Air anxiety in Vinnytsia region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147023</link><description>游댮 00:15 Air anxiety in Vinnytsia region follow the following messages.#Vinnytsia_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 21:15:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 23:20 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147022</link><description>游 23:20 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 20:20:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:16 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147021</link><description>游댮 23:16 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 20:16:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:16 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147020</link><description>游댮 23:16 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 20:16:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 23:09 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV indefinite type</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147019</link><description>游 23:09 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV indefinite type#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 20:09:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:08 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial COMMUNICATIONS FALSE.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147018</link><description>游댮 23:08 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial COMMUNICATIONS FALSE. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 20:08:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:51 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147017</link><description>游댮 22:51 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 19:51:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:37 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147016</link><description>游댮 22:37 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.#Kryvyi Rih. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 19:37:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 21:30 Pleasure for the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147015</link><description>游릭 21:30 Pleasure for the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 18:30:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:28 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147014</link><description>游댮 21:28 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 18:28:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:27 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147013</link><description>游댮 21:27 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 18:27:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:26 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147012</link><description>游댮 21:26 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 18:26:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:15 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147011</link><description>游댮 21:15 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 18:15:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:03 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147010</link><description>游댮 21:03 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 18:03:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:03 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147009</link><description>游댮 21:03 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 18:03:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:22 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147008</link><description>游릭 20:22 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 17:22:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:22 Driven alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147007</link><description>游릭 20:22 Driven alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 17:22:13 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>