<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 02:45 Air anxiety in the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140236</link><description>游댮 02:45 Air anxiety in the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 23:45:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:43 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140235</link><description>游댮 02:43 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 23:43:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:20 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140234</link><description>游댮 02:20 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 23:20:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:20 Air alarm to Cherkasy district to care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140233</link><description>游댮 02:20 Air alarm to Cherkasy district to care for further messages.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 23:20:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 02:10 The threat of artobrats to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Cont attention, anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140232</link><description>游리 02:10 The threat of artobrats to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Cont attention, anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region#Pokrovskaya_T territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 23:10:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:04 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140231</link><description>游댮 02:04 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 23:04:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:02 Air anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140230</link><description>游댮 02:02 Air anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 23:02:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:35 Driven the alarm in Kyiv. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140229</link><description>游릭 01:35 Driven the alarm in Kyiv. Salt for further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 22:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:34 Dumping anxiety in the Kiev region. Follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140228</link><description>游릭 01:34 Dumping anxiety in the Kiev region. Follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 22:34:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 01:32 Flashing anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140227</link><description>游리 01:32 Flashing anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 22:32:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:32 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region. Follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140226</link><description>游릭 01:32 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region. Follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 22:32:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:52 Air anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140225</link><description>游댮 00:52 Air anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 21:52:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:45 Drive anxiety in Zolotonsky District. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140224</link><description>游릭 00:45 Drive anxiety in Zolotonsky District. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 21:45:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:45 Failure to alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140223</link><description>游릭 00:45 Failure to alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 21:45:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:45 Failure to be alarmed in Cherkasy district.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140222</link><description>游릭 00:45 Failure to be alarmed in Cherkasy district.Creck on further reports.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 21:45:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:45 Failure to alarm to Uman district.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140221</link><description>游릭 00:45 Failure to alarm to Uman district.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 21:45:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:45 Alarm in Zvenigorod district. Stop after further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140220</link><description>游릭 00:45 Alarm in Zvenigorod district. Stop after further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 21:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:42 Threat of Arteball! Pokrovskaya Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140219</link><description>游댮 00:42 Threat of Arteball! Pokrovskaya Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 21:42:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:38 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Follow the subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140218</link><description>游릭 00:38 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Follow the subsequent messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 21:38:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:37 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140217</link><description>游릭 00:37 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 21:37:37 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>