<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 18:22 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141513</link><description>游댮 18:22 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 15:22:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 18:12 The threat of a shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141512</link><description>游리 18:12 The threat of a shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 15:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 18:12 Attention! Please note that anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141511</link><description>游리 18:12 Attention! Please note that anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 15:12:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:44 Air alarm to the Zolotonsky district to care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141510</link><description>游댮 17:44 Air alarm to the Zolotonsky district to care for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 14:44:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:44 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141509</link><description>游댮 17:44 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 14:44:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:25 Driven anxiety in Kyiv. Investigate by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141508</link><description>游릭 17:25 Driven anxiety in Kyiv. Investigate by subsequent messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 14:25:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:21 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141507</link><description>游릭 17:21 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 14:21:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:21 Drive alarm to Cherkasy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141506</link><description>游릭 17:21 Drive alarm to Cherkasy region.Creck on further messages.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 14:21:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:21 Driven the alarm to the Kiev region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141505</link><description>游릭 17:21 Driven the alarm to the Kiev region. Since further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 14:21:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 17:14 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141504</link><description>游 17:14 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 14:14:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:14 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141503</link><description>游댮 17:14 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 14:14:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:01 Air alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141502</link><description>游댮 17:01 Air alarm to Cherkasy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Cherkasy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 14:01:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:01 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141501</link><description>游댮 17:01 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 14:01:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:01 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141500</link><description>游댮 17:01 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow the following messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 14:01:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:01 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141499</link><description>游댮 17:01 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 14:01:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:00 Air alarm in Kyiv Investigate by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141498</link><description>游댮 17:00 Air alarm in Kyiv Investigate by further messages.#M_kiiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 14:00:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:12 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141497</link><description>游댮 16:12 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 13:12:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:12 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141496</link><description>游댮 16:12 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 13:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:59 Air anxiety in Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141495</link><description>游댮 15:59 Air anxiety in Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.#Pavlograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 12:59:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:47 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141494</link><description>游댮 15:47 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 12:47:45 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>