<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 11:36 Driven the alarm to Sumy region.Creat for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133218</link><description>游릭 11:36 Driven the alarm to Sumy region.Creat for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 09:36:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133217</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 08:00:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:36 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133216</link><description>游댮 08:36 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 06:36:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:17 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marhanetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133215</link><description>游댮 08:17 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marhanetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 06:17:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:15 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133214</link><description>游댮 08:15 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 06:15:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:54 The threat of a shelling in Marganets and Manganese Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133213</link><description>游릭 07:54 The threat of a shelling in Marganets and Manganese Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 05:54:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:53 Return the threat of Artobhstil to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133212</link><description>游릭 07:53 Return the threat of Artobhstil to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 05:53:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 07:23 Fragrant anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Marganets and Marganets Territorial Community- Mirorsk Territorial Community- Chervonohrigor Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133211</link><description>游리 07:23 Fragrant anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Marganets and Marganets Territorial Community- Mirorsk Territorial Community- Chervonohrigor Territorial Community#of Dnipropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 05:23:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:23 Attention !!! Drives the threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133210</link><description>游릭 07:23 Attention !!! Drives the threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 05:23:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 07:22 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133209</link><description>游리 07:22 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district#Zaporizhzhia_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 05:22:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:07 Plowing of anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133208</link><description>游릭 07:07 Plowing of anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creat by further messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 05:07:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:02 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133207</link><description>游릭 07:02 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 05:02:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:01 Drive anxiety in the Poltava region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133206</link><description>游릭 07:01 Drive anxiety in the Poltava region.Creck on further messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 05:01:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:01 Drive anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133205</link><description>游릭 07:01 Drive anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 05:01:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 06:58 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133204</link><description>游리 06:58 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 04:58:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:40 The threat of shelling! Now in the Mirovsky territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133203</link><description>游댮 06:40 The threat of shelling! Now in the Mirovsky territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 04:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 06:29 The threat of artobrats to Pokrovskaya territorial community. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133202</link><description>游리 06:29 The threat of artobrats to Pokrovskaya territorial community. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region#Pokrovskaya_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 04:29:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:12 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133201</link><description>游릭 06:12 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 04:12:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 06:12 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133200</link><description>游리 06:12 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community#Kharkiv_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 04:12:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:12 Drive the threat of shock bplas.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/133199</link><description>游릭 06:12 Drive the threat of shock bplas. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 04:12:07 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>