<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 17:11 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150257</link><description>游 17:11 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 14:11:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:07 Return the threat of artebing to Pokrovskaya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150256</link><description>游릭 17:07 Return the threat of artebing to Pokrovskaya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 14:07:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:07 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150255</link><description>游댮 17:07 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 14:07:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:01 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150254</link><description>游릭 17:01 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 14:01:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 17:01 Drawing of anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150253</link><description>游리 17:01 Drawing of anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 14:01:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:01 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150252</link><description>游댮 17:01 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 14:01:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:39 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150251</link><description>游댮 16:39 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 13:39:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:38 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150250</link><description>游댮 16:38 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 13:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 16:32 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150249</link><description>游 16:32 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 13:32:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 16:29 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150248</link><description>游 16:29 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 13:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:23 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150247</link><description>游댮 16:23 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 13:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:23 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150246</link><description>游댮 16:23 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 13:23:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:17 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150245</link><description>游릭 16:17 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 13:17:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:17 WARNING! DRAWING DRONIV-Kamikadze!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150244</link><description>游릭 16:17 WARNING! DRAWING DRONIV-Kamikadze! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 13:17:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:00 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150243</link><description>游댮 16:00 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 13:00:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 15:56 Dronov-Kamikadze Attack! Movement on the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150242</link><description>游 15:56 Dronov-Kamikadze Attack! Movement on the city#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 12:56:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:56 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150241</link><description>游댮 15:56 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 12:56:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:07 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150240</link><description>游릭 15:07 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 12:07:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:07 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150239</link><description>游릭 15:07 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 12:07:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 14:59 Return the threat of artobrats in the Chervonohrigor territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150238</link><description>游릭 14:59 Return the threat of artobrats in the Chervonohrigor territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 11:59:58 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>