<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 23:19 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140747</link><description>游댮 23:19 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 20:19:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:16 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140746</link><description>游릭 23:16 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 20:16:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:14 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140745</link><description>游릭 23:14 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 20:14:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:14 Driven the threat of shock bpadbius threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140744</link><description>游릭 23:14 Driven the threat of shock bpadbius threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 20:14:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:10 pm a alarm to Nikopol district.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140743</link><description>游릭 23:10 pm a alarm to Nikopol district.Creck on further reports.#Nikopol_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 20:10:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:10 pm a alarm to Kryvyi Rih District.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140742</link><description>游릭 23:10 pm a alarm to Kryvyi Rih District.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 20:10:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:10 pm a alarm to the Dnieper district.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140741</link><description>游릭 23:10 pm a alarm to the Dnieper district.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 20:10:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:10 pm a alarm to Kamyansky district.Creck on subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140740</link><description>游릭 23:10 pm a alarm to Kamyansky district.Creck on subsequent messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 20:10:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:08 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Stop after further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140739</link><description>游릭 23:08 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Stop after further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 20:08:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 22:44 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140738</link><description>游릭 22:44 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 19:44:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:40 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140737</link><description>游댮 22:40 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 19:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:40 Air alarm in Zvenigorod District to care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140736</link><description>游댮 22:40 Air alarm in Zvenigorod District to care for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 19:40:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:20 Air alarm to Cherkasy district care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140735</link><description>游댮 22:20 Air alarm to Cherkasy district care for further messages.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 19:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:20 Air alarm to the Zolotonsky district to care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140734</link><description>游댮 22:20 Air alarm to the Zolotonsky district to care for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 19:20:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:11 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140733</link><description>游댮 22:11 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 19:11:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:51 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140732</link><description>游댮 21:51 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 18:51:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:43 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140731</link><description>游댮 21:43 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad Oblast follow the following messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 18:43:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:21 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140730</link><description>游댮 21:21 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 18:21:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:20 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140729</link><description>游댮 21:20 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 18:20:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:20 Air alarm in the Dnieper District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140728</link><description>游댮 21:20 Air alarm in the Dnieper District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 18:20:16 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>