<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 10:11 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144756</link><description>游댮 10:11 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 07:11:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:07 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144755</link><description>游댮 10:07 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 07:07:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:06 Attention! Drone attack! Perhaps discharges of explosive items!  Be in shelters!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144754</link><description>游 10:06 Attention! Drone attack! Perhaps discharges of explosive items!  Be in shelters! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 07:06:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:05 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144753</link><description>游댮 10:05 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 07:05:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:04 Plowing the threat of arteblow to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144752</link><description>游릭 10:04 Plowing the threat of arteblow to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 07:04:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:58 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144751</link><description>游 09:58 Free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 06:58:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:53 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144750</link><description>游댮 09:53 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 06:53:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:49 Threat of Artebric! Pokrovskaya Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144749</link><description>游댮 09:49 Threat of Artebric! Pokrovskaya Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 06:49:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:45 Driven anxiety in the Odesa region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144748</link><description>游릭 09:45 Driven anxiety in the Odesa region. Watch for further messages.#Odessa_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 06:45:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:43 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144747</link><description>游릭 09:43 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 06:43:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:43 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144746</link><description>游릭 09:43 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 06:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 9</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144745</link><description>游릭 9 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 06:43:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 09:43 Drawing anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144744</link><description>游리 09:43 Drawing anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 06:43:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:41 Driven anxiety in the Transcarpathian region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144743</link><description>游릭 09:41 Driven anxiety in the Transcarpathian region. Since further reports.#Transcarpathian This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 06:41:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:40 Driven Alarm to Lviv Oblast. Since Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144742</link><description>游릭 09:40 Driven Alarm to Lviv Oblast. Since Further Messages.#Lviv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 06:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:40 Driven anxiety in Chernivtsi region. Follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144741</link><description>游릭 09:40 Driven anxiety in Chernivtsi region. Follow the following messages.#Chernivtsi_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 06:40:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:37 Drive alarm to the Khmelnytsky region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144740</link><description>游릭 09:37 Drive alarm to the Khmelnytsky region. Watch for further messages.#Khmelnitskaya This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 06:37:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:37 Dumping anxiety in the Rivne region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144739</link><description>游릭 09:37 Dumping anxiety in the Rivne region.Creck on further messages.#Rivne_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 06:37:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:35 Drive alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144738</link><description>游릭 09:35 Drive alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creat by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 06:35:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:34 Dumping anxiety in the Vinnytsia region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144737</link><description>游릭 09:34 Dumping anxiety in the Vinnytsia region. Watch for further messages.#Vinnytsia_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 06:34:10 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>