<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 13:40 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152147</link><description>游릭 13:40 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Creat by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 10:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:30 Failure to the Dniprovsky District. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152146</link><description>游릭 13:30 Failure to the Dniprovsky District. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 10:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:20 Download of anxiety in Kamyansky District.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152145</link><description>游릭 13:20 Download of anxiety in Kamyansky District.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 10:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:19 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152144</link><description>游댮 13:19 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 10:19:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:14 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsk District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152143</link><description>游릭 13:14 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsk District. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 10:14:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 13:05 Drone attack, the old part of the old part</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152142</link><description>游 13:05 Drone attack, the old part of the old part #m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 10:05:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:05 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152141</link><description>游댮 13:05 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 10:05:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:49 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152140</link><description>游릭 12:49 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:49:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:49 a alarm in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152139</link><description>游릭 12:49 a alarm in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:49:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:32 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikovsky District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152138</link><description>游릭 12:32 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikovsky District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:32:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:32 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152137</link><description>游릭 12:32 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further reports.#Nikopol_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:32:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:32 Dumping anxiety in Kryvyi Rih District.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152136</link><description>游릭 12:32 Dumping anxiety in Kryvyi Rih District.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:32:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:32 Dumping anxiety in Pavlograd district. Stop after further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152135</link><description>游릭 12:32 Dumping anxiety in Pavlograd district. Stop after further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:32 MAKALABIBIBIUM ALREADY AVIRTED AVIRT BOMB (Kabiv).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152134</link><description>游릭 12:32 MAKALABIBIBIUM ALREADY AVIRTED AVIRT BOMB (Kabiv). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:32:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:31 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152133</link><description>游릭 12:31 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:31:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:31 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152132</link><description>游릭 12:31 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:31 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152131</link><description>游릭 12:31 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:31 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152130</link><description>游리 12:31 Flowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district#Zaporizhzhia_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:31:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:31 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152129</link><description>游릭 12:31 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region.Creck on further reports.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:31:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:31 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/152128</link><description>游리 12:31 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:31:15 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>