<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 22:50 The threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146824</link><description>游댮 22:50 The threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 19:50:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:48 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146823</link><description>游댮 22:48 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 19:48:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:48 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146822</link><description>游댮 22:48 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 19:48:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 22:46 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146821</link><description>游 22:46 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 19:46:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:39 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146820</link><description>游댮 22:39 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 19:39:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:39 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146819</link><description>游댮 22:39 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.#Kryvyi Rih. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 19:39:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:34 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146818</link><description>游댮 22:34 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 19:34:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:18 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District to care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146817</link><description>游댮 22:18 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District to care for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 19:18:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:18 Air alarm to Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146816</link><description>游댮 22:18 Air alarm to Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.#Pavlograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 19:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:18 Air alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146815</link><description>游댮 22:18 Air alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.#Nikopol_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 19:18:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:18 Air alarm to the Dniprovsky district to care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146814</link><description>游댮 22:18 Air alarm to the Dniprovsky district to care for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 19:18:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:18 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsk District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146813</link><description>游댮 22:18 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsk District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 19:18:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:18 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146812</link><description>游댮 22:18 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 19:18:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:55 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146811</link><description>游댮 21:55 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 18:55:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:54 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146810</link><description>游댮 21:54 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 18:54:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:54 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146809</link><description>游댮 21:54 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 18:54:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 21:42 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetsky territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146808</link><description>游리 21:42 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetsky territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 18:42:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:37 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146807</link><description>游댮 21:37 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 18:37:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 20:50 pm alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapets Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146806</link><description>游리 20:50 pm alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapets Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 17:50:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 20:49 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/146805</link><description>游릭 20:49 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 17:49:39 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>