<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 07:22 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137744</link><description>游댮 07:22 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 04:22:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:57 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137743</link><description>游댮 06:57 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 03:57:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 06:37 PM threats of artobstil to Pokrovskaya territorial community. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137742</link><description>游리 06:37 PM threats of artobstil to Pokrovskaya territorial community. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 03:37:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:26 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya region follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137741</link><description>游댮 06:26 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya region follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 03:26:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:26 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137740</link><description>游댮 06:26 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 03:26:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:38 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137739</link><description>游릭 05:38 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 02:38:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:25 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137738</link><description>游릭 05:25 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 02:25:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:25 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137737</link><description>游릭 05:25 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 02:25:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:23 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137736</link><description>游릭 05:23 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 02:23:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:23 Drawing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-mirorskaya territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivska Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137735</link><description>游리 05:23 Drawing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-mirorskaya territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivska Territorial Community# This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 02:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:23 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137734</link><description>游릭 05:23 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 02:23:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:23 Drive the threat of percussion bplas.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137733</link><description>游릭 05:23 Drive the threat of percussion bplas. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 02:23:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:22 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Laivpetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137732</link><description>游리 05:22 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Laivpetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 02:22:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:22 Driven the alarm to Poltava region. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137731</link><description>游릭 05:22 Driven the alarm to Poltava region. Salt for further messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 02:22:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:04 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137730</link><description>游댮 04:04 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 01:04:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:04 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137729</link><description>游댮 04:04 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 01:04:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 03:52 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137728</link><description>游 03:52 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_that_harkivskaya_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 00:52:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:49 Air Alarm to Poltava Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137727</link><description>游댮 03:49 Air Alarm to Poltava Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 00:49:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:43 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137726</link><description>游댮 03:43 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 00:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 03:01 Drawing anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky Territorial Community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivska Territorial Community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/137725</link><description>游리 03:01 Drawing anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky Territorial Community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivska Territorial Community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 00:01:31 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>