<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 08:22 Attack of drones-camikadzethip Prayer, traffic in the direction</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140083</link><description>游 08:22 Attack of drones-camikadzethip Prayer, traffic in the direction This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 05:22:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 08:22 Attack Drones-Camikadzethip Pracement</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140082</link><description>游 08:22 Attack Drones-Camikadzethip Pracement This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 05:22:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:21 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140081</link><description>游댮 08:21 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 05:21:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:12 Air anxiety in Zhytomyr Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140080</link><description>游댮 08:12 Air anxiety in Zhytomyr Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zhytomyr_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 05:12:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:04 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140079</link><description>游릭 08:04 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 05:04:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:04 Attention! Droze Dronov-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140078</link><description>游릭 08:04 Attention! Droze Dronov-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 05:04:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:59 Air anxiety in Vinnytsia Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140077</link><description>游댮 07:59 Air anxiety in Vinnytsia Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Vinnytsia_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 04:59:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:51 Return the threat of artebrow to Pokrovskaya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140076</link><description>游릭 07:51 Return the threat of artebrow to Pokrovskaya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 04:51:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 07:42 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh in the direction of the old part</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140075</link><description>游 07:42 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh in the direction of the old part This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 04:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:35 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140074</link><description>游댮 07:35 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 04:35:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 07:33 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140073</link><description>游 07:33 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 04:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:33 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140072</link><description>游댮 07:33 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 04:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:25 Air anxiety in the Zvenigorod district to care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140071</link><description>游댮 07:25 Air anxiety in the Zvenigorod district to care for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 04:25:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:17 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140070</link><description>游댮 07:17 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 04:17:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:00 plout alarm to Donetsk region. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140069</link><description>游릭 07:00 plout alarm to Donetsk region. Stop by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 04:00:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:51 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140068</link><description>游릭 06:51 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 03:51:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:51 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140067</link><description>游릭 06:51 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #M_Nikopol_that_nikopol_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 03:51:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 06:46 pm alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivka Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140066</link><description>游리 06:46 pm alarm to Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community of Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivka Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 03:46:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:40 Air alarm to Cherkasy District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140065</link><description>游댮 06:40 Air alarm to Cherkasy District Surveat for Further Messages.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 03:40:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:40 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140064</link><description>游댮 06:40 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 03:40:37 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>