<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 01:48 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151826</link><description>游댮 01:48 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 22:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:18 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151825</link><description>游릭 01:18 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 22:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:18 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151824</link><description>游댮 01:18 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 22:18:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:17 Driven anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151823</link><description>游릭 01:17 Driven anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 22:17:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:17 Dumping anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151822</link><description>游릭 01:17 Dumping anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 22:17:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:59 Driven anxiety in the Dnieper district.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151821</link><description>游릭 00:59 Driven anxiety in the Dnieper district.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 21:59:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 00:59 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151820</link><description>游 00:59 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_that_harkivskaya_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 21:59:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:58 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151819</link><description>游댮 00:58 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 21:58:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:56 Driven your alarm to Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151818</link><description>游릭 00:56 Driven your alarm to Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 21:56:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:35 Air anxiety in the Dnieper District care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151817</link><description>游댮 00:35 Air anxiety in the Dnieper District care for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 21:35:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:34 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151816</link><description>游댮 00:34 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 21:34:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:34 Air anxiety in the Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151815</link><description>游댮 00:34 Air anxiety in the Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.#Nikopol_ Region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 21:34:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:10 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151814</link><description>游댮 00:10 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 21:10:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:22 Driven the alarm to the Kyiv region. Further in further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151813</link><description>游릭 23:22 Driven the alarm to the Kyiv region. Further in further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 20:22:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:22 Driven Alarm to Chernihiv Oblast. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151812</link><description>游릭 23:22 Driven Alarm to Chernihiv Oblast. Salt for further messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 20:22:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:21 Driven the alarm in Kyiv. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151811</link><description>游릭 23:21 Driven the alarm in Kyiv. Salt for further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 20:21:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:06 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Make sure</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151810</link><description>游릭 23:06 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Make sure This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 20:06:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 23:06 Attention !!! Notice, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151809</link><description>游리 23:06 Attention !!! Notice, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya region#Pologovsky_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 20:06:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:57 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151808</link><description>游댮 22:57 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 19:57:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:35 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151807</link><description>游댮 22:35 Air alarm to the Kiev region follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 19:35:22 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>