<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 02:23 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149396</link><description>游릭 02:23 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 23:23:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:23 Run the threat of shock bplavidbium threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149395</link><description>游릭 02:23 Run the threat of shock bplavidbium threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 23:23:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:22 Driven the anxiety in the Dnieper district. Stop after further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149394</link><description>游릭 02:22 Driven the anxiety in the Dnieper district. Stop after further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 23:22:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:22 Driven Alarm to Kamyansky District.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149393</link><description>游릭 02:22 Driven Alarm to Kamyansky District.Creck on Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 23:22:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:52 Driven the alarm to the Nikopol District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149392</link><description>游릭 01:52 Driven the alarm to the Nikopol District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 22:52:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:50 plowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149391</link><description>游릭 01:50 plowing anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporozhye This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 22:50:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:50 Auxiliary alarm in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149390</link><description>游릭 01:50 Auxiliary alarm in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 22:50:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:49 Air anxiety in Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149389</link><description>游댮 01:49 Air anxiety in Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.#Pavlograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 22:49:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:24 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149388</link><description>游댮 01:24 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 22:24:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:23 Drive anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149387</link><description>游릭 01:23 Drive anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 22:23:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:13 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Follow the subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149386</link><description>游릭 01:13 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Follow the subsequent messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 22:13:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:52 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149385</link><description>游댮 00:52 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 21:52:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:49 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149384</link><description>游댮 23:49 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 20:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:36 Air alarm in the Dnieper District care for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149383</link><description>游댮 23:36 Air alarm in the Dnieper District care for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 20:36:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:36 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149382</link><description>游댮 23:36 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 20:36:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:22 Driven the alarm to the Kyiv region. Further in further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149381</link><description>游릭 23:22 Driven the alarm to the Kyiv region. Further in further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 20:22:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:22 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149380</link><description>游릭 23:22 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 20:22:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:22 Driven Alarm to the Chernihiv Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149379</link><description>游릭 23:22 Driven Alarm to the Chernihiv Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 20:22:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:22 Driven the alarm to Cherkasy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149378</link><description>游릭 23:22 Driven the alarm to Cherkasy region.Creck on further messages.#Cherkasy_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 20:22:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:19 Threat of Arteball! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149377</link><description>游댮 23:19 Threat of Arteball! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 20:19:46 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>