<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 06:44 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Stop after further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142711</link><description>游릭 06:44 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Stop after further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 03:44:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:40 Driven the alarm to the Zhytomyr region.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142710</link><description>游릭 06:40 Driven the alarm to the Zhytomyr region.Creck on further reports.#Zhytomyr_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 03:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:38 Driven the alarm in Kyiv. Investigate by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142709</link><description>游릭 06:38 Driven the alarm in Kyiv. Investigate by subsequent messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 03:38:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:33 Driven Alarm to Kamyansky District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142708</link><description>游릭 06:33 Driven Alarm to Kamyansky District.Creck on further reports.#Kamyan_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 03:33:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 06:32 Alarm to Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142707</link><description>游리 06:32 Alarm to Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 03:32:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:32 PM Anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142706</link><description>游릭 06:32 PM Anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 03:32:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:32 Drive alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142705</link><description>游릭 06:32 Drive alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 03:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:28 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142704</link><description>游댮 06:28 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 03:28:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:23 Return the threat of artobrats to the Bilenkovsky territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142703</link><description>游릭 06:23 Return the threat of artobrats to the Bilenkovsky territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 03:23:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:17 Dumping anxiety in the Vinnytsia region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142702</link><description>游릭 06:17 Dumping anxiety in the Vinnytsia region. Watch for further messages.#Vinnytsia_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 03:17:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:17 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142701</link><description>游릭 06:17 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 03:17:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:06 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142700</link><description>游댮 06:06 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 03:06:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:57 The threat of shelling! Now in the Belenkovsky territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142699</link><description>游댮 05:57 The threat of shelling! Now in the Belenkovsky territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 02:57:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:57 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142698</link><description>游릭 05:57 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 02:57:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:53 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142697</link><description>游댮 05:53 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.#Sinelnikov. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 02:53:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:42 Driven the alarm in Kyiv. Follow the subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142696</link><description>游릭 05:42 Driven the alarm in Kyiv. Follow the subsequent messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 02:42:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:01 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142695</link><description>游릭 05:01 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Watch for further messages.#Odessa_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 02:01:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:01 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Observe by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142694</link><description>游릭 05:01 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Observe by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 02:01:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:00 plout anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142693</link><description>游릭 05:00 plout anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 02:00:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:47 Dumping anxiety in Kryvyi Rih District. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142692</link><description>游릭 04:47 Dumping anxiety in Kryvyi Rih District. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 01:47:41 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>