<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 18:01 Draw an alarm to Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131063</link><description>游릭 18:01 Draw an alarm to Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporozhye This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 16:01:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 18:00 WARNING !!! Pay attention, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131062</link><description>游리 18:00 WARNING !!! Pay attention, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya region#Pologovsky_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 16:00:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:58 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131061</link><description>游릭 17:58 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 15:58:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 17:58 Failure to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganets Territorial Community- March Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131060</link><description>游리 17:58 Failure to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganets Territorial Community- March Territorial Community#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 15:58:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 17:35 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131059</link><description>游 17:35 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 15:35:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:31 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131058</link><description>游댮 17:31 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 15:31:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:21 Drive the threat of percussion bplas.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131057</link><description>游릭 17:21 Drive the threat of percussion bplas. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 15:21:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:21 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131056</link><description>游릭 17:21 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 15:21:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:10 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131055</link><description>游댮 17:10 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 15:10:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:37 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131054</link><description>游댮 16:37 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 14:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:36 Drive alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131053</link><description>游릭 16:36 Drive alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 14:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 16:35 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131052</link><description>游리 16:35 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 14:35:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:35 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131051</link><description>游릭 16:35 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region. Since further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 14:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 16:31 The threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131050</link><description>游 16:31 The threat of percussion Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"#m_harkiv_that_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 14:31:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:30 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131049</link><description>游댮 16:30 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 14:30:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:17 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131048</link><description>游릭 16:17 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 14:17:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:17 Drive the threat of use of the Cabinet of Construction by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131047</link><description>游릭 16:17 Drive the threat of use of the Cabinet of Construction by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 14:17:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:52 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131046</link><description>游릭 15:52 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 13:52:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 15:47 The threat of use of the cope proportion of the use</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131045</link><description>游 15:47 The threat of use of the cope proportion of the use This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 13:47:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 15:47 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131044</link><description>游댮 15:47 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 13:47:04 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>