<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 10:39 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142180</link><description>游릭 10:39 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 07:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:39 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142179</link><description>游릭 10:39 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 07:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142178</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#KUDYANSKY This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 07:00:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:45 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142177</link><description>游릭 09:45 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:36 Air anxiety in Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142176</link><description>游댮 09:36 Air anxiety in Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kirovograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:30 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142175</link><description>游댮 09:30 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:30:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:30 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142174</link><description>游댮 09:30 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:30:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:28 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142173</link><description>游 09:28 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:28:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:17 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142172</link><description>游댮 09:17 Air anxiety in Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:17:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:17 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142171</link><description>游 09:17 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:17:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:16 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142170</link><description>游댮 09:16 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:16:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:15 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142169</link><description>游댮 09:15 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:15:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:14 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142168</link><description>游댮 09:14 The threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:14:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:53 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142167</link><description>游릭 08:53 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 05:53:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:49 Driven the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142166</link><description>游릭 08:49 Driven the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 05:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:49 WARNING! DRAWE DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142165</link><description>游릭 08:49 WARNING! DRAWE DRONNES-Kamikadze #M_Nikopol_ti_nikopol_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 05:49:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:21 Return the threat of artebors in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142164</link><description>游릭 08:21 Return the threat of artebors in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 05:21:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:11 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142163</link><description>游댮 08:11 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 05:11:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 08:00 WARNING! Drone-Kamikadze Drone attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142162</link><description>游 08:00 WARNING! Drone-Kamikadze Drone attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 05:00:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 07:49 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, traffic in the direction of the city center</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142161</link><description>游 07:49 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, traffic in the direction of the city center #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 04:49:44 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>