<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 11:25 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151312</link><description>游릭 11:25 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 08:25:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:16 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151311</link><description>游댮 11:16 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 08:16:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:55 Failure to alarm to the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151310</link><description>游릭 10:55 Failure to alarm to the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 07:55:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:55 threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151309</link><description>游댮 10:55 threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 07:55:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:55 Threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151308</link><description>游댮 10:55 Threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 07:55:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:47 Air Alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151307</link><description>游댮 10:47 Air Alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 07:47:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:47 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151306</link><description>游 10:47 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 07:47:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:47 threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151305</link><description>游댮 10:47 threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 07:47:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:43 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151304</link><description>游릭 10:43 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 07:43:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:43 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151303</link><description>游릭 10:43 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADze #M_Nikopol_ti_nikopol_ Territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 07:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:42 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151302</link><description>游릭 10:42 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporozhye This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 07:42:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:41 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151301</link><description>游릭 10:41 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 07:41:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:31 Driven anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151300</link><description>游릭 10:31 Driven anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 07:31:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:31 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151299</link><description>游릭 10:31 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further reports.#Nikopol_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 07:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:31 Dumping anxiety in Kryvyi Rih District. Stop by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151298</link><description>游릭 10:31 Dumping anxiety in Kryvyi Rih District. Stop by subsequent messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 07:31:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:31 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151297</link><description>游릭 10:31 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District.Creck on further reports.#Pavlograd_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 07:31:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:31 Driven anxiety in the Dnieper district.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151296</link><description>游릭 10:31 Driven anxiety in the Dnieper district.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 07:31:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:31 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsk District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151295</link><description>游릭 10:31 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsk District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 07:31:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:31 Driven anxiety in Kamyansky District.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151294</link><description>游릭 10:31 Driven anxiety in Kamyansky District.Creck on further messages.#Kamian_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 07:31:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:31 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/151293</link><description>游릭 10:31 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 07:31:06 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>