<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 10:16 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130294</link><description>游댮 10:16 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 08:16:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:06 Air Alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130293</link><description>游댮 10:06 Air Alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 08:06:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 10:06 Fragrant anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130292</link><description>游리 10:06 Fragrant anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 08:06:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:05 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130291</link><description>游 10:05 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 08:05:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:02 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130290</link><description>游댮 10:02 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 08:02:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:00 Air alarm to Kupyansky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130289</link><description>游댮 10:00 Air alarm to Kupyansky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 08:00:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:57 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130288</link><description>游댮 09:57 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 07:57:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:54 Close the threat of Artobstil to Pokrovskaya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130287</link><description>游릭 09:54 Close the threat of Artobstil to Pokrovskaya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 07:54:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:21 Driven the alarm to the Zhytomyr region.Crete on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130286</link><description>游릭 09:21 Driven the alarm to the Zhytomyr region.Crete on further reports.#Zhytomyr This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 07:21:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:15 Flow to the Khmelnytsky region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130285</link><description>游릭 09:15 Flow to the Khmelnytsky region. Watch for further messages.#Khmelnitskaya This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 07:15:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:39 Dumping anxiety in the Kiev region. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130284</link><description>游릭 08:39 Dumping anxiety in the Kiev region. Stop by further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 06:39:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:30 Fragrant anxiety in Kyiv. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130283</link><description>游릭 08:30 Fragrant anxiety in Kyiv. Salt for further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 06:30:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:20 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130282</link><description>游댮 08:20 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 06:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:08 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region. Stop by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130281</link><description>游릭 08:08 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region. Stop by further messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 06:08:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:08 Drive alarm to Poltava region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130280</link><description>游릭 08:08 Drive alarm to Poltava region. Since further reports.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 06:08:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:08 Plowing of the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130279</link><description>游릭 08:08 Plowing of the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 06:08:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 07:48 pm alarm in Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-mirorskaya territorial community-Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130278</link><description>游리 07:48 pm alarm in Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-mirorskaya territorial community-Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 05:48:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:37 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130277</link><description>游릭 07:37 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region. Since further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 05:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:32 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130276</link><description>游릭 07:32 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 05:32:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:32 Drive the threat of shock bplavidbium threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130275</link><description>游릭 07:32 Drive the threat of shock bplavidbium threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 05:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>