<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 12:36 Driven your alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143182</link><description>游릭 12:36 Driven your alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 09:36:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:35 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143181</link><description>游릭 12:35 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 09:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:08 Pleasure for the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143180</link><description>游릭 12:08 Pleasure for the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 09:08:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:07 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143179</link><description>游댮 12:07 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 09:07:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:07 Dumping anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143178</link><description>游릭 12:07 Dumping anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 09:07:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:03 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143177</link><description>游릭 12:03 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 09:03:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:03 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143176</link><description>游릭 12:03 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporozhye This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 09:03:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:02 The threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143175</link><description>游리 12:02 The threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 09:02:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:02 Return the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143174</link><description>游릭 12:02 Return the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 09:02:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:50 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143173</link><description>游 11:50 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 08:50:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:50 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143172</link><description>游댮 11:50 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 08:50:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:45 Pleasure for the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143171</link><description>游릭 11:45 Pleasure for the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 08:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:42 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143170</link><description>游댮 11:42 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 08:42:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:25 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143169</link><description>游 11:25 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 08:25:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:21 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143168</link><description>游리 11:21 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 08:21:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:21 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143167</link><description>游릭 11:21 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 08:21:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:21 Return the threat of shock bpadbius threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143166</link><description>游릭 11:21 Return the threat of shock bpadbius threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 08:21:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:20 Return of the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143165</link><description>游릭 11:20 Return of the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 08:20:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:20 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143164</link><description>游릭 11:20 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 08:20:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:13 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143163</link><description>游 11:13 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).#Vasylivsky_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 08:13:10 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>