<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 08:52 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134079</link><description>游댮 08:52 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 06:52:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:22 Air Air In Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134078</link><description>游댮 08:22 Air Air In Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 06:22:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:18 Air anxiety in Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134077</link><description>游댮 08:18 Air anxiety in Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 06:18:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:57 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134076</link><description>游댮 07:57 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 05:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:17 Pleasure in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134075</link><description>游릭 07:17 Pleasure in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 05:17:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:17 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134074</link><description>游릭 07:17 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 05:17:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:05 Plowing the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134073</link><description>游릭 07:05 Plowing the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 05:05:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:48 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134072</link><description>游댮 06:48 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 04:48:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:48 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134071</link><description>游댮 06:48 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 04:48:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:43 Drawing anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky Territorial Community, Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Mirovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134070</link><description>游리 05:43 Drawing anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky Territorial Community, Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Mirovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 03:43:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:42 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134069</link><description>游릭 05:42 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 03:42:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:02 Drive alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134068</link><description>游릭 05:02 Drive alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 03:02:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:02 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134067</link><description>游릭 05:02 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 03:02:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:02 Drive the threat of shock bplas.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134066</link><description>游릭 05:02 Drive the threat of shock bplas. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 03:02:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:02 Fragrant anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134065</link><description>游리 05:02 Fragrant anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 03:02:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:10 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134064</link><description>游댮 04:10 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow further reports.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 02:10:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:01 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Follow the subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134063</link><description>游릭 03:01 Drive anxiety in the Odesa region. Follow the subsequent messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 01:01:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:47 Dumping anxiety in the Zhytomyr region.Crete on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134062</link><description>游릭 02:47 Dumping anxiety in the Zhytomyr region.Crete on further reports.#Zhytomyr This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 00:47:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:43 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134061</link><description>游댮 02:43 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 00:43:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:29 Drive alarm to the Khmelnytsky region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/134060</link><description>游릭 02:29 Drive alarm to the Khmelnytsky region. Watch for further messages.#Khmelnitskaya This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 00:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>