<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 04:08 Drive alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131115</link><description>游릭 04:08 Drive alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 02:08:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:14 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131114</link><description>游댮 03:14 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by subsequent messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 01:14:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:02 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131113</link><description>游릭 03:02 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 01:02:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:02 Run the threat of percussion Blividbium threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131112</link><description>游릭 03:02 Run the threat of percussion Blividbium threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 01:02:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 03:02 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131111</link><description>游리 03:02 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community#Kharkiv_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 01:02:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:57 Alarm in Zvenigorod district.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131110</link><description>游릭 02:57 Alarm in Zvenigorod district.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 00:57:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:57 Dumping anxiety in the Uman district.Creck on subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131109</link><description>游릭 02:57 Dumping anxiety in the Uman district.Creck on subsequent messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 00:57:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:57 Drive alarm to Cherkasy district.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131108</link><description>游릭 02:57 Drive alarm to Cherkasy district.Creck on further messages.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 00:57:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:57 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creck on subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131107</link><description>游릭 02:57 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creck on subsequent messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 00:57:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:39 Air anxiety in the Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131106</link><description>游댮 02:39 Air anxiety in the Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 00:39:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 02:38 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131105</link><description>游 02:38 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_tha_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 00:38:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:37 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131104</link><description>游댮 02:37 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 00:37:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:23 Drive alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131103</link><description>游릭 02:23 Drive alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 00:23:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:16 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131102</link><description>游댮 02:16 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 00:16:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:10 Draw a alarm to Vinnytsia region. Make sure</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131101</link><description>游릭 02:10 Draw a alarm to Vinnytsia region. Make sure This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 00:10:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:09 Dumping anxiety in the Zhytomyr region.Crete on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131100</link><description>游릭 02:09 Dumping anxiety in the Zhytomyr region.Crete on further reports.#Zhytomyr This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 00:09:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:02 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131099</link><description>游릭 02:02 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 00:02:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 02:02 Run the threat of shock Blividbium threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131098</link><description>游릭 02:02 Run the threat of shock Blividbium threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 00:02:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 02:02 Fragrant anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131097</link><description>游리 02:02 Fragrant anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 00:02:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:36 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131096</link><description>游릭 01:36 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 23:36:41 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>