<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 08:42 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136432</link><description>游댮 08:42 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 05:42:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 08:37 The threat of shock UAVs The threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136431</link><description>游 08:37 The threat of shock UAVs The threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 05:37:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:36 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136430</link><description>游댮 08:36 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 05:36:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:36 Air Alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136429</link><description>游댮 08:36 Air Alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 05:36:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:27 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136428</link><description>游릭 08:27 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 05:27:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:53 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136427</link><description>游댮 07:53 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 04:53:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:24 Plow anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136426</link><description>游릭 07:24 Plow anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Since further reports.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 04:24:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:23 Frame alarms in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136425</link><description>游릭 07:23 Frame alarms in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 04:23:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:18 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136424</link><description>游릭 07:18 Close the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 04:18:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 07:13 Drawing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136423</link><description>游리 07:13 Drawing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Consider that anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community#Kharkiv_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 04:13:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:13 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136422</link><description>游릭 07:13 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 04:13:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:11 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136421</link><description>游댮 07:11 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 04:11:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:11 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136420</link><description>游댮 07:11 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 04:11:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:09 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136419</link><description>游댮 07:09 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 04:09:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:08 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136418</link><description>游댮 07:08 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 04:08:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:30 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136417</link><description>游릭 06:30 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 03:30:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 06:30 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136416</link><description>游리 06:30 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 03:30:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:27 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region. Follow the subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136415</link><description>游릭 06:27 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region. Follow the subsequent messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 03:27:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 06:26 PM anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-mirovsk territorial community-Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136414</link><description>游리 06:26 PM anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-mirovsk territorial community-Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigoriva Territorial Community#Dnipropetrovsk. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 03:26:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:26 Frame alarm to Zaporizhzhia region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/136413</link><description>游릭 06:26 Frame alarm to Zaporizhzhia region. Since further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 03:26:50 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>