<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 21:19 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147474</link><description>游댮 21:19 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 18:19:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:18 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147473</link><description>游댮 21:18 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 18:18:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 21:10 PM threats of artebing to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Cont attention, anxiety is still in:- Nikopol district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147472</link><description>游리 21:10 PM threats of artebing to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Cont attention, anxiety is still in:- Nikopol district#Pokrovskaya_ territorial_ community This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 18:10:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:09 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147471</link><description>游댮 21:09 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 18:09:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:08 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147470</link><description>游댮 21:08 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 18:08:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:04 Air alarm in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147469</link><description>游댮 21:04 Air alarm in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 18:04:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:51 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147468</link><description>游댮 20:51 Air alarm to Kamyansky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 17:51:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:51 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147467</link><description>游댮 20:51 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.#Kryvyi Rih Ri This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 17:51:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:40 Air alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147466</link><description>游댮 20:40 Air alarm to Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.#Nikopol_ Region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 17:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:40 Air alarm to the Dnieper District Survene from further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147465</link><description>游댮 20:40 Air alarm to the Dnieper District Survene from further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 17:40:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:17 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147464</link><description>游댮 20:17 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 17:17:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:08 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147463</link><description>游댮 20:08 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 17:08:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:43 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147462</link><description>游댮 19:43 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:43:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 19:36 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147461</link><description>游릭 19:36 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:36:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 19:35 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147460</link><description>游 19:35 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:35 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147459</link><description>游댮 19:35 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:35:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:32 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147458</link><description>游릭 18:32 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:32:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 18:32 Flashing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147457</link><description>游리 18:32 Flashing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:32:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:32 Drive alarm to Poltava region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147456</link><description>游릭 18:32 Drive alarm to Poltava region. Watch for further reports.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:32:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:27 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147455</link><description>游댮 18:27 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:27:52 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>