<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 13:02 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154180</link><description>游릭 13:02 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 10:02:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:02 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154179</link><description>游릭 13:02 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporozhye This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 10:02:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 13:02 Attention !!! Note, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154178</link><description>游리 13:02 Attention !!! Note, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya region#Zaporizhzhya_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 10:02:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:02 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154177</link><description>游릭 13:02 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 10:02:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:02 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154176</link><description>游릭 13:02 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 10:02:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:41 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154175</link><description>游댮 12:41 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 09:41:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:35 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabins).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154174</link><description>游 12:35 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabins). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 09:35:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:28 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154173</link><description>游댮 12:28 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 09:28:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:09 Attack drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154172</link><description>游 12:09 Attack drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 09:09:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:51 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154171</link><description>游릭 11:51 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 08:51:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:51 Drawing of anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154170</link><description>游리 11:51 Drawing of anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 08:51:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:30 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. Walk to the shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154169</link><description>游댮 11:30 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. Walk to the shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 08:30:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:26 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154168</link><description>游릭 11:26 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District.Creck on further reports.#Pavlograd_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 08:26:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:26 Driven anxiety in the Dnieper District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154167</link><description>游릭 11:26 Driven anxiety in the Dnieper District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 08:26:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:26 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsk District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154166</link><description>游릭 11:26 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsk District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 08:26:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:25 Fragrant anxiety in the Poltava region.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154165</link><description>游릭 11:25 Fragrant anxiety in the Poltava region.Creck on further reports.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 08:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:09 Close the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154164</link><description>游릭 11:09 Close the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 08:09:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:59 threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154163</link><description>游댮 10:59 threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 07:59:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:50 PM The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154162</link><description>游릭 10:50 PM The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 07:50:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:36 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsk District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154161</link><description>游댮 10:36 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsk District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 07:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>