<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 05:28 Driven Alarm to Kamyansky District.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144147</link><description>游릭 05:28 Driven Alarm to Kamyansky District.Creck on Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 02:28:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:27 Driven anxiety in the Dnieper district.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144146</link><description>游릭 05:27 Driven anxiety in the Dnieper district.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 02:27:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:27 Drive alarm to Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144145</link><description>游릭 05:27 Drive alarm to Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 02:27:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:27 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144144</link><description>游릭 05:27 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 02:27:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:26 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144143</link><description>游릭 05:26 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 02:26:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:22 Air anxiety in the Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144142</link><description>游댮 05:22 Air anxiety in the Nikopol District Surveat for Further Messages.#Nikopol_ Region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 02:22:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:20 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144141</link><description>游댮 05:20 Air alarm to Kryvyi Rih District Surveat for Further Messages.#Kryvyi Rih Ri This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 02:20:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:16 Flashing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kamyansky district- Dniprovskyi district-Sinelnikovsky district- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community- Nikopol and Nikopol territorial community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144140</link><description>游리 05:16 Flashing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kamyansky district- Dniprovskyi district-Sinelnikovsky district- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community- Nikopol and Nikopol territorial community This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 02:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:12 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd district. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144139</link><description>游리 05:12 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd district. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region#Pavlograd_RAV This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 02:12:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:12 Driven anxiety in the Novomoskovsky District. Full attention, anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144138</link><description>游리 05:12 Driven anxiety in the Novomoskovsky District. Full attention, anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region#Novomoskovsk_RAVKOD This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 02:12:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:12 Driven the alarm to the Kiev region. Stop by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144137</link><description>游릭 05:12 Driven the alarm to the Kiev region. Stop by subsequent messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 02:12:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:12 Drive alarm to Cherkasy region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144136</link><description>游릭 05:12 Drive alarm to Cherkasy region. Watch for further messages.#Cherkasy_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 02:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:11 Fragrant anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144135</link><description>游릭 05:11 Fragrant anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 02:11:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:10 Download alarm in Kyiv. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144134</link><description>游릭 05:10 Download alarm in Kyiv. Salt for further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 02:10:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:09 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144133</link><description>游릭 05:09 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 02:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:09 Driven the anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144132</link><description>游릭 05:09 Driven the anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 02:09:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:08 Alarm to Kharkiv region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144131</link><description>游리 05:08 Alarm to Kharkiv region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 02:08:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:08 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144130</link><description>游릭 05:08 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 02:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:08 Show the threat of shock Blividbium threat of percussion UAV</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144129</link><description>游릭 05:08 Show the threat of shock Blividbium threat of percussion UAV#M_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 02:08:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:08 Drive alarm to Poltava region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/144128</link><description>游릭 05:08 Drive alarm to Poltava region. Watch for further reports.#Poltava_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 02:08:21 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>