<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 9</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139194</link><description>游댮 9 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 06:42:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:42 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139193</link><description>游댮 09:42 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 06:42:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:42 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139192</link><description>游댮 09:42 Air anxiety in the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 06:42:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:42 Air anxiety in the Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139191</link><description>游댮 09:42 Air anxiety in the Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kirovograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 06:42:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:42 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139190</link><description>游댮 09:42 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 06:42:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:41 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139189</link><description>游댮 09:41 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 06:41:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:41 Air anxiety in the Poltava region follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139188</link><description>游댮 09:41 Air anxiety in the Poltava region follow further reports.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 06:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:41 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139187</link><description>游댮 09:41 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 06:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:40 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139186</link><description>游댮 09:40 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 06:40:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:40 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139185</link><description>游댮 09:40 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 06:40:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:40 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139184</link><description>游댮 09:40 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 06:40:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:20 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139183</link><description>游댮 09:20 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 06:20:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:20 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139182</link><description>游댮 09:20 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 06:20:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:18 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, old part area!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139181</link><description>游 09:18 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack, old part area! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 06:18:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 09:11 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze Dronov Drohnia Type</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139180</link><description>游 09:11 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze Dronov Drohnia Type This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 06:11:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 08:54 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139179</link><description>游 08:54 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 05:54:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:53 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139178</link><description>游댮 08:53 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 05:53:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:51 Return the threat of artobrats in the Bilenkovskaya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139177</link><description>游릭 08:51 Return the threat of artobrats in the Bilenkovskaya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 05:51:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 08:49 Drawing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139176</link><description>游리 08:49 Drawing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 05:49:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:41 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139175</link><description>游댮 08:41 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 05:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>