<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 13:49 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141259</link><description>游댮 13:49 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:49 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141258</link><description>游댮 13:49 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:49:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:49 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141257</link><description>游댮 13:49 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:49:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:48 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141256</link><description>游댮 13:48 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:48:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:41 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141255</link><description>游댮 13:41 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:31 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141254</link><description>游릭 13:31 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:31:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:23 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141253</link><description>游릭 13:23 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:23:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:04 The threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141252</link><description>游릭 13:04 The threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:04:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:04 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141251</link><description>游릭 13:04 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:04:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:49 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141250</link><description>游댮 12:49 Air alarm to Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 09:49:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:49 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141249</link><description>游댮 12:49 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 09:49:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:33 Drawing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141248</link><description>游리 12:33 Drawing anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 09:33:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:24 Supervise threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141247</link><description>游릭 12:24 Supervise threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 09:24:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 12:24 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141246</link><description>游리 12:24 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district#Zaporizhzhya_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 09:24:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:22 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141245</link><description>游댮 12:22 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 09:22:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:22 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141244</link><description>游릭 12:22 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 09:22:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:13 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Survene from further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141243</link><description>游댮 12:13 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Survene from further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 09:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:02 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141242</link><description>游 12:02 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 09:02:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:58 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141241</link><description>游릭 11:58 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region.Creck on further messages.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:58:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:54 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/141240</link><description>游 11:54 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:28 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>