<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 06:44 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140439</link><description>游릭 06:44 Dumping anxiety in the Poltava region. Watch for further messages.#Poltava_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 03:44:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:41 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140438</link><description>游댮 06:41 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 03:41:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:39 Driven the anxiety in Zvenigorod district. Stop after further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140437</link><description>游릭 06:39 Driven the anxiety in Zvenigorod district. Stop after further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 03:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:39 Driven anxiety in the Uman District.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140436</link><description>游릭 06:39 Driven anxiety in the Uman District.Creck on Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 03:39:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:39 Driven anxiety in Cherkasy district.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140435</link><description>游릭 06:39 Driven anxiety in Cherkasy district.Creck on further reports.#Cherkasy_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 03:39:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:38 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creck on subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140434</link><description>游릭 06:38 Dumping anxiety in the Zolotonsky district.Creck on subsequent messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 03:38:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:38 Dumping anxiety in the Vinnytsia region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140433</link><description>游릭 06:38 Dumping anxiety in the Vinnytsia region. Since further messages.#Vinnytsia_e This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 03:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:38 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140432</link><description>游릭 06:38 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 03:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:50 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140431</link><description>游댮 05:50 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.#Sinelnikov. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 02:50:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 05:50 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140430</link><description>游 05:50 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 02:50:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:46 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140429</link><description>游댮 05:46 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 02:46:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:46 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140428</link><description>游댮 05:46 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 02:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:21 Drive anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140427</link><description>游릭 05:21 Drive anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 02:21:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:07 Air anxiety in Zhytomyr Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140426</link><description>游댮 05:07 Air anxiety in Zhytomyr Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zhytomyr_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 02:07:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:49 Driven the alarm in Kyiv. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140425</link><description>游릭 04:49 Driven the alarm in Kyiv. Salt for further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 01:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:46 Air alarm to Vinnytsia Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140424</link><description>游댮 04:46 Air alarm to Vinnytsia Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Vinnytsia_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 01:46:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:35 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140423</link><description>游댮 04:35 Air alarm in Kyiv -followed by further messages.#M_Kyev This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 01:35:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:17 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140422</link><description>游댮 04:17 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 01:17:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:17 Air Alarm in Zvenigorod District Survene from further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140421</link><description>游댮 04:17 Air Alarm in Zvenigorod District Survene from further messages.#Zvenigorod_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 01:17:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:07 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140420</link><description>游릭 03:07 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 00:07:51 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>