<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游리 08:16 The threat of a shelling in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Find out, the alarm is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143434</link><description>游리 08:16 The threat of a shelling in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Find out, the alarm is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region#m_ Marganets_ta_Ametskaya_Marganetska_The. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 05:16:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:11 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143433</link><description>游댮 08:11 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 05:11:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:11 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143432</link><description>游댮 08:11 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 05:11:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 08:11 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh in the direction of the old part</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143431</link><description>游 08:11 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh in the direction of the old part This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 05:11:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:11 Air Alarm in Zvenigorod District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143430</link><description>游댮 08:11 Air Alarm in Zvenigorod District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 05:11:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:11 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143429</link><description>游댮 08:11 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 05:11:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:10 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143428</link><description>游댮 08:10 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 05:10:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:10 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143427</link><description>游댮 08:10 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 05:10:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:10 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143426</link><description>游댮 08:10 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kirovograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 05:10:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:10 Air alarm to the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143425</link><description>游댮 08:10 Air alarm to the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 05:10:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:10 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143424</link><description>游댮 08:10 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 05:10:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:10 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143423</link><description>游댮 08:10 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 05:10:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:10 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143422</link><description>游댮 08:10 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast follow the following messages.#Kharkiv_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 05:10:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:10 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143421</link><description>游댮 08:10 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 05:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:09 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143420</link><description>游댮 08:09 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 05:09:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:05 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143419</link><description>游릭 08:05 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 05:05:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:05 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143418</link><description>游릭 08:05 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 05:05:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:00 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143417</link><description>游댮 08:00 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 05:00:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:00 Air Alarm to Cherkasy District Surveat as Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143416</link><description>游댮 08:00 Air Alarm to Cherkasy District Surveat as Further Messages.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 05:00:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:56 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143415</link><description>游릭 07:56 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 04:56:34 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>