<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 07:22 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148288</link><description>游릭 07:22 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 04:22:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:16 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148287</link><description>游릭 07:16 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 04:16:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:52 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148286</link><description>游릭 06:52 Driven the alarm to Sinelnikov District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 03:52:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:52 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148285</link><description>游릭 06:52 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhia region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 03:52:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:42 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148284</link><description>游댮 06:42 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 03:42:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:23 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148283</link><description>游댮 06:23 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 03:23:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 06:20 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148282</link><description>游댮 06:20 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 03:20:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 06:20 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148281</link><description>游릭 06:20 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 03:20:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:56 Failure to alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148280</link><description>游리 05:56 Failure to alarm to Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 02:56:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 05:53 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148279</link><description>游댮 05:53 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 02:53:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:15 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148278</link><description>游릭 04:15 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 01:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:15 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148277</link><description>游릭 04:15 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Of Zaporizhzhia_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 01:15:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:13 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148276</link><description>游릭 04:13 Driven anxiety in the Nikopol District. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 01:13:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:13 Drive anxiety in the Kryvyi Rih District. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148275</link><description>游릭 04:13 Drive anxiety in the Kryvyi Rih District. Watch for further messages.#Kryvyi Rih. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 01:13:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 04:08 Drawing of anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kryvyi Rih district-Nikopol district- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-Nikopol and Nikopol territorial community-Pokrovskaya territorial community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148274</link><description>游리 04:08 Drawing of anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kryvyi Rih district-Nikopol district- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community-Nikopol and Nikopol territorial community-Pokrovskaya territorial community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 01:08:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:07 Clease the threat of using Cabbaths The threat of application</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148273</link><description>游릭 04:07 Clease the threat of using Cabbaths The threat of application This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 01:07:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:07 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148272</link><description>游릭 04:07 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 01:07:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:07 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148271</link><description>游릭 04:07 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 01:07:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 04:07 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lajpetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148270</link><description>游리 04:07 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lajpetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 01:07:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:52 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148269</link><description>游댮 03:52 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 00:52:15 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>