<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>🔴 23:23 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad Oblast follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131273</link><description>🔴 23:23 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad Oblast follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 21:23:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 22:48 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131272</link><description>🟢 22:48 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 20:48:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 22:46 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131271</link><description>🟢 22:46 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Since further reports.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 20:46:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 22:44 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131270</link><description>🔴 22:44 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 20:44:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 22:44 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131269</link><description>🔴 22:44 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 20:44:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 22:32 The threat of shelling! The Chervonohrigor Territorial Community is now Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131268</link><description>🔴 22:32 The threat of shelling! The Chervonohrigor Territorial Community is now Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 20:32:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 22:31 Driven anxiety in the Kherson region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131267</link><description>🟢 22:31 Driven anxiety in the Kherson region. Since further reports.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 20:31:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 22:29 Driven anxiety in the Odesa region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131266</link><description>🟢 22:29 Driven anxiety in the Odesa region. Watch for further messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 20:29:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟢 22:28 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131265</link><description>🟢 22:28 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 20:28:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:49 Threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131264</link><description>🔴 21:49 Threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 19:49:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 21:28 🔴 Attention‼ The threat of using managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131263</link><description>🟠 21:28 🔴 Attention‼ The threat of using managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 19:28:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 21:14 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131262</link><description>🔴 21:14 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 19:14:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴11</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131261</link><description>🔴11 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 19:13:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 20:50 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131260</link><description>🔴 20:50 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 18:50:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 20:48 Air alarm to the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131259</link><description>🔴 20:48 Air alarm to the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 18:48:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 20:38 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131258</link><description>🔴 20:38 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 18:38:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🟠 20:37 The threat of shock UAVs The threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131257</link><description>🟠 20:37 The threat of shock UAVs The threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 18:37:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 20:37 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131256</link><description>🔴 20:37 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 18:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 20:36 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131255</link><description>🔴 20:36 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 18:36:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🔴 20:28 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/131254</link><description>🔴 20:28 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 18:28:23 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>