<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 3</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142148</link><description>游릭 3 This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:57:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:44 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142147</link><description>游댮 03:44 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:44:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:11 Dumply alarm to the Odesa region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142146</link><description>游릭 03:11 Dumply alarm to the Odesa region. Since further messages.#Odessa_e This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:11:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:10 Failure to alarm to the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142145</link><description>游릭 03:10 Failure to alarm to the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:10:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 03:09 Driven to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142144</link><description>游릭 03:09 Driven to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:09:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:52 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142143</link><description>游댮 02:52 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 23:52:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:07 Air anxiety in the Vinnytsia region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142142</link><description>游댮 02:07 Air anxiety in the Vinnytsia region follow the following messages.#Vinnytsia_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 23:07:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:42 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142141</link><description>游댮 01:42 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kirovograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 22:42:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:00 Air alarm to the Odesa region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142140</link><description>游댮 01:00 Air alarm to the Odesa region follow the following messages.#Odessa_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 22:00:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 00:47 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142139</link><description>游릭 00:47 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region.Creck on further messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 21:47:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:51 The threat of shelling! The Chervonohrigor Territorial Community is now Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142138</link><description>游댮 23:51 The threat of shelling! The Chervonohrigor Territorial Community is now Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 20:51:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:16 Attention !!! Range the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142137</link><description>游릭 23:16 Attention !!! Range the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 20:16:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:15 Attention !!! Drive the threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142136</link><description>游릭 23:15 Attention !!! Drive the threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 20:15:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:14 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142135</link><description>游릭 23:14 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 20:14:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 23:14 Draw an alarm to the Zaporizhzhya region. Please note, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district- Zaporizhzhya district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142134</link><description>游리 23:14 Draw an alarm to the Zaporizhzhya region. Please note, anxiety is still in:- Pologovsky district- Zaporizhzhya district#Zaporizhzhya_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 20:14:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:14 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142133</link><description>游릭 23:14 Driven Alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 20:14:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:07 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142132</link><description>游댮 23:07 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 20:07:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 22:38 Attack of drones-camikadzethip Prayer, traffic in the direction of prince</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142131</link><description>游 22:38 Attack of drones-camikadzethip Prayer, traffic in the direction of prince This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 19:38:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 22:37 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh in the direction of the 8th quarter</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142130</link><description>游 22:37 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh in the direction of the 8th quarter#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 19:37:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 22:34 Attack Dronov-Camikadzethip Prayer</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/142129</link><description>游 22:34 Attack Dronov-Camikadzethip Prayer This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 19:34:15 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>