<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 13:50 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/130000</link><description>游댮 13:50 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 11:50:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:30 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129999</link><description>游릭 13:30 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 11:30:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:09 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129998</link><description>游댮 13:09 Threat of Artbill! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 11:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:24 Dumping anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129997</link><description>游릭 12:24 Dumping anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 10:24:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:12 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129996</link><description>游댮 12:12 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 10:12:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:03 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129995</link><description>游릭 12:03 Return the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 10:03:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:27 Close the threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129994</link><description>游릭 11:27 Close the threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 09:27:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:26 Failure to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky Territorial Community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivska Territorial Community.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129993</link><description>游리 11:26 Failure to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Marganets and Marganetsky Territorial Community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Pokrovsk Territorial Community- Chervono-Grigorivska Territorial Community. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 09:26:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:26 Driven the alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129992</link><description>游릭 11:26 Driven the alarm to the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 09:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:25 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129991</link><description>游릭 11:25 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 09:25:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:25 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129990</link><description>游리 11:25 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District- Lypetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 09:25:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:25 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129989</link><description>游릭 11:25 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 09:25:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:12 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129988</link><description>游댮 11:12 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 09:12:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:59 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129987</link><description>游릭 10:59 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region.Creck on further messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 08:59:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:41 Drive alarm to Poltava region. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129986</link><description>游릭 10:41 Drive alarm to Poltava region. Watch for further messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 08:41:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:35 Auxiliary alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129985</link><description>游릭 10:35 Auxiliary alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 08:35:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:35 Drive the threat of shock bplas.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129984</link><description>游릭 10:35 Drive the threat of shock bplas. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 08:35:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:26 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129983</link><description>游댮 10:26 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 08:26:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:25 Air Alarm to Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129982</link><description>游댮 10:25 Air Alarm to Chernihiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Chernihiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 08:25:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:25 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/129981</link><description>游댮 10:25 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 08:25:17 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>