<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游 23:31 The threat of shock UAVs The threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139310</link><description>游 23:31 The threat of shock UAVs The threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 20:31:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:31 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139309</link><description>游댮 23:31 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 20:31:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:17 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139308</link><description>游댮 23:17 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 20:17:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:37 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139307</link><description>游댮 22:37 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 19:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:25 The threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139306</link><description>游댮 22:25 The threat of shelling! Now in the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 19:25:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:24 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139305</link><description>游댮 22:24 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 19:24:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:24 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139304</link><description>游댮 22:24 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 19:24:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:16 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139303</link><description>游댮 22:16 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 19:16:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:15 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139302</link><description>游댮 22:15 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 19:15:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:02 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139301</link><description>游댮 22:02 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 19:02:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:48 Threat of Artbill! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139300</link><description>游댮 21:48 Threat of Artbill! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 18:48:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 21:33 Reduce the threat of Artobstil to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139299</link><description>游릭 21:33 Reduce the threat of Artobstil to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 18:33:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:25 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139298</link><description>游댮 21:25 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 18:25:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 21:23 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze Drone-Type</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139297</link><description>游 21:23 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze Drone-Type This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 18:23:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:22 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139296</link><description>游댮 21:22 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 18:22:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:16 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139295</link><description>游댮 21:16 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 18:16:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 21:13 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139294</link><description>游댮 21:13 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 18:13:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>?</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139293</link><description>? This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 16:09:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 18:43 Drawing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Manganese and Marganets Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139292</link><description>游리 18:43 Drawing anxiety in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Manganese and Marganets Territorial Community#Dnepropetrovsk_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 15:43:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:42 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139291</link><description>游릭 18:42 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat by further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 15:42:54 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>