<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 01:35 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148252</link><description>游릭 01:35 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District.Creck on further reports.#Pavlograd_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 22:35:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:35 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148251</link><description>游릭 01:35 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 22:35:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:35 Return the threat of shock Blividbium threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148250</link><description>游릭 01:35 Return the threat of shock Blividbium threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 22:35:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:35 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsky District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148249</link><description>游릭 01:35 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsky District. Solve for further reports.#Novomoskovsky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 22:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:34 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148248</link><description>游댮 01:34 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 22:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 01:34 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148247</link><description>游댮 01:34 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 22:34:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:26 Drive alarm to the Poltava region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148246</link><description>游릭 01:26 Drive alarm to the Poltava region. Watch for further reports.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 22:26:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 01:25 Dumping anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148245</link><description>游릭 01:25 Dumping anxiety in Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 22:25:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:38 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148244</link><description>游댮 00:38 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 21:38:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:37 Air anxiety in Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148243</link><description>游댮 00:37 Air anxiety in Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.#Pavlograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 21:37:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:37 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148242</link><description>游댮 00:37 Air anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.#Sinelnikov. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 21:37:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 00:05 The threat of shock UAVs The threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148241</link><description>游 00:05 The threat of shock UAVs The threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 21:05:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 00:05 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148240</link><description>游댮 00:05 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 21:05:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:55 Driven Alarm to the Chernihiv Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148239</link><description>游릭 23:55 Driven Alarm to the Chernihiv Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 20:55:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:47 Reduce threatening the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148238</link><description>游릭 23:47 Reduce threatening the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). Salt for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 20:47:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:47 Driven the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148237</link><description>游릭 23:47 Driven the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 20:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:47 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148236</link><description>游릭 23:47 Driven the alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya territorial community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 20:47:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 23:47 Flow to the Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya district</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148235</link><description>游리 23:47 Flow to the Zaporizhzhya region. Find out, anxiety is still in:- Zaporizhzhya district#Zaporizhzhia_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 20:47:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:33 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148234</link><description>游댮 23:33 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 20:33:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:20 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148233</link><description>游댮 23:20 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 20:20:29 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>