<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 11:26 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154168</link><description>游릭 11:26 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd District.Creck on further reports.#Pavlograd_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 08:26:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:26 Driven anxiety in the Dnieper district.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154167</link><description>游릭 11:26 Driven anxiety in the Dnieper district.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 08:26:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:26 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsk District. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154166</link><description>游릭 11:26 Driven anxiety in Novomoskovsk District. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 08:26:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:25 Driven the alarm to the Poltava region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154165</link><description>游릭 11:25 Driven the alarm to the Poltava region. Since further reports.#Poltava_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 08:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:09 Close the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154164</link><description>游릭 11:09 Close the threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 08:09:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:59 threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154163</link><description>游댮 10:59 threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 07:59:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:50 PM The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154162</link><description>游릭 10:50 PM The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 07:50:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:36 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsk District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154161</link><description>游댮 10:36 Air anxiety in Novomoskovsk District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 07:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:35 Air alarm in the Dnieper District Surveat as Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154160</link><description>游댮 10:35 Air alarm in the Dnieper District Surveat as Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 07:35:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:35 Air anxiety in Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154159</link><description>游댮 10:35 Air anxiety in Pavlograd District Surveat for Further Messages.#Pavlograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 07:35:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:28 Auxiliary alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154158</link><description>游릭 10:28 Auxiliary alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 07:28:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:28 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154157</link><description>游댮 10:28 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 07:28:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:26 Driven the alarm to the Zolotonsky district.Creat for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154156</link><description>游릭 10:26 Driven the alarm to the Zolotonsky district.Creat for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 07:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 10:26 Driven anxiety in Cherkasy district.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154155</link><description>游릭 10:26 Driven anxiety in Cherkasy district.Creck on further messages.#Cherkasy This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 07:26:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:10 Air alarm to Cherkasy District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154154</link><description>游댮 10:10 Air alarm to Cherkasy District Surveat for Further Messages.#Cherkasy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 07:10:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:10 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154153</link><description>游댮 10:10 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 07:10:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154152</link><description>游 10:00 free evacuation will urgently evacuate from the war zone or dangerous territory of Kharkiv region. A 24 -hour free hotline for evacuation of civilian population - 0800339291#Kupyansky_ region This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 07:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:53 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154151</link><description>游댮 09:53 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 06:53:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:31 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154150</link><description>游릭 09:31 Dumping anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 06:31:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:18 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/154149</link><description>游댮 09:18 Air anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 06:18:25 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>