<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 12:15 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147422</link><description>游릭 12:15 Reduce the threat of artebors to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 09:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:10 Failure to alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147421</link><description>游릭 12:10 Failure to alarm to Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 09:10:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:06 Threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147420</link><description>游댮 12:06 Threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 09:06:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:01 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147419</link><description>游릭 12:01 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 09:01:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:01 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147418</link><description>游릭 12:01 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 09:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:54 Pleasure the threats of the Artobstil to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147417</link><description>游릭 11:54 Pleasure the threats of the Artobstil to Pokrovsk Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 08:54:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:51 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin Center city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147416</link><description>游 11:51 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin Center city #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 08:51:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:48 Threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147415</link><description>游댮 11:48 Threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 08:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 11:33 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147414</link><description>游 11:33 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 08:33:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 11:33 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147413</link><description>游댮 11:33 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 08:33:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:22 The threat of artobstil in Pokrovskaya territorial community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147412</link><description>游릭 11:22 The threat of artobstil in Pokrovskaya territorial community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 08:22:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:13 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147411</link><description>游릭 11:13 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Watch for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 08:13:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:13 Lock down the threat of the use of cards of the threat of use</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147410</link><description>游릭 11:13 Lock down the threat of the use of cards of the threat of use This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 08:13:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 11:13 Drawing of anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147409</link><description>游리 11:13 Drawing of anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 08:13:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:10 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147408</link><description>游릭 11:10 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 08:10:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:10 Attention! Droke Drone Attack</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147407</link><description>游릭 11:10 Attention! Droke Drone Attack#M_Nikopol_ti_nikopol_ Tertorial_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 08:10:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:08 Attention !!! Drive the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147406</link><description>游릭 11:08 Attention !!! Drive the threat of the use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 08:08:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:07 punch alarm to Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147405</link><description>游릭 11:07 punch alarm to Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 08:07:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 11:06 Frame alarms in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147404</link><description>游릭 11:06 Frame alarms in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Salt for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 08:06:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 10:59 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/147403</link><description>游댮 10:59 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 07:59:38 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>