<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 09:32 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139909</link><description>游댮 09:32 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 06:32:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:29 Driven the threat of artobrats to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139908</link><description>游릭 09:29 Driven the threat of artobrats to the Chervonohrigor Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 06:29:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 09:13 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139907</link><description>游댮 09:13 Air anxiety in the Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 06:13:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:03 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139906</link><description>游릭 09:03 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 06:03:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 09:03 WARNING! DRAWING DRONI-KAMKADze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139905</link><description>游릭 09:03 WARNING! DRAWING DRONI-KAMKADze #m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 06:03:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:58 Threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139904</link><description>游댮 08:58 Threat of shelling! Now in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community artillery shelling. Walk into shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 05:58:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 08:52 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139903</link><description>游리 08:52 Drawing of anxiety in Kharkiv region. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lauda territorial community- Vovchansk territorial community#Kharkiv_ This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 05:52:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 08:32 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139902</link><description>游댮 08:32 Air anxiety in Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 05:32:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 08:30 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139901</link><description>游 08:30 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 05:30:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 08:17 Return the threat of artobrats in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139900</link><description>游릭 08:17 Return the threat of artobrats in Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 05:17:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 08:11 Dronov-Kamikadzerukh attack from a paw to NPTZ</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139899</link><description>游 08:11 Dronov-Kamikadzerukh attack from a paw to NPTZ#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 05:11:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 08:10 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzenad City</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139898</link><description>游 08:10 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzenad City #M_Nikopol_ta_nikopol_ Tertorial_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 05:10:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 08:01 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack continues</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139897</link><description>游 08:01 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack continues This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 05:01:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 07:41 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139896</link><description>游 07:41 Attention! Dronov-Kamikadze attack lasts This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 04:41:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 07:34 Attack drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139895</link><description>游 07:34 Attack drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 04:34:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 07:30 Attack Drones-Camikadzethip Pracement</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139894</link><description>游 07:30 Attack Drones-Camikadzethip Pracement This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 04:30:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 07:30 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139893</link><description>游댮 07:30 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 04:30:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:22 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139892</link><description>游릭 07:22 The threat of shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Salt for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 04:22:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:22 WARNING! DRAWE DRONNIA-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139891</link><description>游릭 07:22 WARNING! DRAWE DRONNIA-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_ti_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 04:22:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 07:13 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Crete on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/139890</link><description>游릭 07:13 Driven the alarm to Donetsk region.Crete on further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 04:13:52 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>