<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 13:36 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149673</link><description>游댮 13:36 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 10:36:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 13:16 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin of the old part</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149672</link><description>游 13:16 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerin of the old part #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial_ community This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 10:16:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 13:16 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149671</link><description>游댮 13:16 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 10:16:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:09 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149670</link><description>游릭 13:09 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 10:09:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:09 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149669</link><description>游릭 13:09 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 10:09:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:01 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149668</link><description>游릭 13:01 Driven anxiety in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 10:01:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 13:01 Drive the threat of shock bplavidbium threat</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149667</link><description>游릭 13:01 Drive the threat of shock bplavidbium threat This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 10:01:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 13:01 Drawing of anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149666</link><description>游리 13:01 Drawing of anxiety in the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lapetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 10:01:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:45 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149665</link><description>游릭 12:45 Fragrant anxiety in Zaporizhzhya region.Creck on further messages.#Zaporozhye This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:45:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:45 Auxiliary alarm in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149664</link><description>游릭 12:45 Auxiliary alarm in Zaporozhye and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:45:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:43 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149663</link><description>游 12:43 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:43:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:42 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149662</link><description>游댮 12:42 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:42:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:29 Threat of Artebrach! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149661</link><description>游댮 12:29 Threat of Artebrach! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter! This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:29:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:29 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149660</link><description>游댮 12:29 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:29:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:29 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149659</link><description>游댮 12:29 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:29:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:26 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149658</link><description>游댮 12:26 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:26:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 12:26 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149657</link><description>游 12:26 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Prayer"#m_harkiv_that_harkivskaya_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:26:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 12:25 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149656</link><description>游댮 12:25 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:25:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:18 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149655</link><description>游릭 12:18 Dumping anxiety in the Donetsk region. Since further messages.#Donetsk_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:18:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 12:17 Dumping anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/149654</link><description>游릭 12:17 Dumping anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:17:54 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>