<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 20:06 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148388</link><description>游댮 20:06 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 17:06:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 20:05 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148387</link><description>游 20:05 The threat of shock Bplasagrasis of UAV type "Shahaned"#m_harkiv_that_harkivska_The territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 17:05:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 20:04 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148386</link><description>游댮 20:04 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 17:04:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:51 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148385</link><description>游댮 19:51 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 16:51:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:49 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148384</link><description>游댮 19:49 Air alarm to Sinelnikovsky District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 16:49:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:48 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148383</link><description>游댮 19:48 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 16:48:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:48 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148382</link><description>游댮 19:48 Air alarm to Donetsk Region follow the following messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 16:48:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:48 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148381</link><description>游댮 19:48 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 16:48:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 19:40 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148380</link><description>游릭 19:40 The threat of artobrats in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 16:40:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 19:40 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148379</link><description>游댮 19:40 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Sumy_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 16:40:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 19:09 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148378</link><description>游릭 19:09 Driven the alarm to the Donetsk region.Creat on further messages.#Donetsk This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 16:09:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 19:09 Driven anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148377</link><description>游릭 19:09 Driven anxiety in Sinelnikovsky District.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 16:09:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 18:54 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148376</link><description>游댮 18:54 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 15:54:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 18:05 Driven the alarm to the Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148375</link><description>游릭 18:05 Driven the alarm to the Sumy Oblast.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 15:05:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:56 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148374</link><description>游댮 16:56 Air alarm to Sumy Oblast follow the following messages.#Sumy_oblast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 13:56:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:39 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148373</link><description>游릭 16:39 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 13:39:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 16:39 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148372</link><description>游릭 16:39 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-Kamikadze #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 13:39:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 16:27 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148371</link><description>游 16:27 Attack Dronov-Kamikadzerukh on the city #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 13:27:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:11 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148370</link><description>游댮 16:11 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 13:11:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:59 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/148369</link><description>游릭 15:59 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 12:59:38 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>