<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游댮 00:15 Air anxiety in the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140581</link><description>游댮 00:15 Air anxiety in the Kirovohrad region follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 21:15:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:41 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Salt for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140580</link><description>游릭 23:41 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Salt for further messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 20:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:41 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140579</link><description>游릭 23:41 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 20:41:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:41 Driven anxiety in the Uman District.Creck on Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140578</link><description>游릭 23:41 Driven anxiety in the Uman District.Creck on Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 20:41:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:41 Driven anxiety in Zvenigorod district.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140577</link><description>游릭 23:41 Driven anxiety in Zvenigorod district.Creck on further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 20:41:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:41 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140576</link><description>游릭 23:41 Driven the alarm to the Kirovohrad region. Watch for further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 20:41:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:30 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140575</link><description>游댮 23:30 Air alarm to the Chernihiv region follow the following messages.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 20:30:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:29 Driven the alarm to the Kiev region. Since further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140574</link><description>游릭 23:29 Driven the alarm to the Kiev region. Since further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 20:29:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 23:29 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140573</link><description>游릭 23:29 Dumping anxiety in the Chernihiv region. Since further reports.#Chernihiv_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 20:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:12 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140572</link><description>游댮 23:12 Air alarm to Uman District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 20:12:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:12 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140571</link><description>游댮 23:12 Air alarm to the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 20:12:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:12 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140570</link><description>游댮 23:12 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 20:12:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:11 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140569</link><description>游댮 23:11 Air alarm to Kirovohrad Oblast follow further reports.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 20:11:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 23:11 Air alarm in Zvenigorod District Surveat for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140568</link><description>游댮 23:11 Air alarm in Zvenigorod District Surveat for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 20:11:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:50 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140567</link><description>游댮 22:50 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Citizen according to further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 19:50:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:50 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140566</link><description>游댮 22:50 Air alarm to Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 19:50:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 22:46 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin).</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140565</link><description>游 22:46 Attention !!! Threat of use of managed aviation bombs (cabin). This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 19:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:32 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140564</link><description>游댮 22:32 Air alarm to Zaporizhzhya Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Zaporozhye_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 19:32:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:14 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140563</link><description>游댮 22:14 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District Surveat for Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 19:14:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 22:14 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/140562</link><description>游댮 22:14 Air alarm in Cherkasy district to care for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 19:14:44 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>