<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游릭 05:01 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd district.Creck on further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143132</link><description>游릭 05:01 Driven anxiety in Pavlograd district.Creck on further reports.#Pavlograd_ district This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 02:01:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:00 plout anxiety in Novomoskovsk district. Stop after further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143131</link><description>游릭 05:00 plout anxiety in Novomoskovsk district. Stop after further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 02:00:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 05:00 plowing anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143130</link><description>游릭 05:00 plowing anxiety in the Sumy region.Creck on further messages.#Sumy_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 02:00:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:00 A.curely in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Novomoskovsk Rivhlograd district- Sinelnikovsky rayon- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Gravskaya Territorial.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143129</link><description>游리 05:00 A.curely in the Dnipropetrovsk region. Consider that the alarm is still in:- Novomoskovsk Rivhlograd district- Sinelnikovsky rayon- Marganets and Marganetsky territorial community- Nikopol and Nikopol Territorial Community- Chervono-Gravskaya Territorial. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 02:00:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 05:00 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143128</link><description>游리 05:00 Alarm to the Kharkiv region. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv District-Lipetsk Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 02:00:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:53 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region. Stop by subsequent messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143127</link><description>游릭 04:53 Driven anxiety in the Chernihiv region. Stop by subsequent messages.#Chernihiv This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 01:53:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:52 Driven Alarm to Kyiv Oblast. Since Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143126</link><description>游릭 04:52 Driven Alarm to Kyiv Oblast. Since Further Messages.#Kyiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 01:52:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:29 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143125</link><description>游릭 04:29 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 01:29:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 04:23 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143124</link><description>游댮 04:23 Air alarm to Kharkiv Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 01:23:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:11 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Since further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143123</link><description>游릭 04:11 Dumping anxiety in the Kherson region. Since further reports.#Kherson_ex This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 01:11:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:07 Fragrance in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143122</link><description>游릭 04:07 Fragrance in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community. Solve for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 01:07:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:07 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143121</link><description>游릭 04:07 Alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Community. Solve for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 01:07:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:07 Return the threat of the use of Cabbaths The threat of application</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143120</link><description>游릭 04:07 Return the threat of the use of Cabbaths The threat of application This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 01:07:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 04:07 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143119</link><description>游릭 04:07 Flow to the Zaporizhzhia Oblast. Watch for further messages.#Zaporizhzhia This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 01:07:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 04:07 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lajpetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143118</link><description>游리 04:07 Failure to the Kharkiv Oblast. Please note that the alarm is still in:- Kupyansky district- Kharkiv district- Lajpetskaya Territorial Community- Vovchansk Territorial Community#Kharkiv_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 01:07:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:44 Air anxiety in Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143117</link><description>游댮 03:44 Air anxiety in Kirovohrad Oblast Watch Further Messages.#Kirovograd_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 00:44:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 03:12 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143116</link><description>游댮 03:12 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 00:12:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:45 Air anxiety in the Kherson region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143115</link><description>游댮 02:45 Air anxiety in the Kherson region follow the following messages.#Kherson_Blast This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 23:45:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:31 Air alarm to Cherkasy district observe further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143114</link><description>游댮 02:31 Air alarm to Cherkasy district observe further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 23:31:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 02:31 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District to care for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/143113</link><description>游댮 02:31 Air alarm to Zolotonskyi District to care for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 23:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>