<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Translated Air Alert UA</title><link>https://t.me/s/air_alert_ua</link><description>Translated Alerts from Air Alert UA</description><item><title>游리 17:20 The threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150782</link><description>游리 17:20 The threat of artebors to Pokrovskaya territorial community. Consider, anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region#Pokrovskay This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 14:20:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 17:18 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150781</link><description>游릭 17:18 Driven anxiety in the Nikolaev area. Watch for further messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 14:18:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 17:12 The threat of a shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Find attention, the alarm is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150780</link><description>游리 17:12 The threat of a shelling in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Find attention, the alarm is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region#m_nikopol_that_nikopol. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 14:12:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游리 17:12 Attention! Please note that anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150779</link><description>游리 17:12 Attention! Please note that anxiety is still in:- Dnipropetrovsk region#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 14:12:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:10 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150778</link><description>游댮 17:10 The threat of shelling! Now in Pokrovskaya territorial community artillery shelling. Put in shelter!#Pokrovskaya_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 14:10:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:02 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150777</link><description>游댮 17:02 Air anxiety in the Nikolaev area follow further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 14:02:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:01 Air anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150776</link><description>游댮 17:01 Air anxiety in Dnipropetrovsk Oblast follow the following messages.#Dnepropetrovsk_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 14:01:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:01 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150775</link><description>游댮 17:01 Air alarm in Zaporizhzhia and Zaporizhzhya Territorial Community to Further Messages. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 14:01:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:01 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150774</link><description>游댮 17:01 Air anxiety in Zaporizhzhya Oblast follow further messages.#Zaporizhzhia_. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 14:01:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:01 Air alarm to Cherkasy region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150773</link><description>游댮 17:01 Air alarm to Cherkasy region follow the following messages.#Cherkasy_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 14:01:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:01 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150772</link><description>游댮 17:01 Air alarm to the Kirovohrad region follow the following messages.#Kirovograd This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 14:01:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:01 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150771</link><description>游댮 17:01 Air alarm to the Poltava region follow the following messages.#Poltava_Bost This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 14:01:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 17:00 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150770</link><description>游댮 17:00 Air alarm in Kharkiv and Kharkiv Territorial Citizen for further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 14:00:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 16:52 attack drones, possible discharges of ammunition by the 8th quarter-car station</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150769</link><description>游 16:52 attack drones, possible discharges of ammunition by the 8th quarter-car station#m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 13:52:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 16:50 AM attack of drones, possible discharges of ammunition to the bakery</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150768</link><description>游 16:50 AM attack of drones, possible discharges of ammunition to the bakery #m_nikopol_that_nikopol_ territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 13:50:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 16:45 Drone attack, Varus-Zhus-Zhd's ammunition is possible</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150767</link><description>游 16:45 Drone attack, Varus-Zhus-Zhd's ammunition is possible This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 13:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游댮 16:45 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150766</link><description>游댮 16:45 The threat of shelling! Now in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community Artillery Fire. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 13:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:51 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports.</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150765</link><description>游릭 15:51 Return the threat of Artobstil in Nikopol and the Nikopol Territorial Community. Take care of further reports. This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 12:51:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游릭 15:51 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADze</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150764</link><description>游릭 15:51 WARNING! DRAWING DRONNES-KAMKADze #M_Nikopol_ti_nikopol_ Territorial This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 12:51:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>游 15:41 Attack drones</title><link>https://t.me/air_alert_ua/150763</link><description>游 15:41 Attack drones This is a warning from the official Ukrainian Air Monitoring System and may indicate a potential or imminent airstrike or other threat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 12:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>